The	O
ATT	B-ORG
"	O
rebutal	O
"	O
commercials	O
don't	O
bother	O
to	O
address	O
their	O
short	O
comings	O
.	O
Just	O
like	O
weak	O
politicians	O
they're	O
reframing	O
the	O
argument	O
.	O

@LikeRealyPretty	B-PER
indeed	O
that	O
is	O
true	O
...	O
i	O
really	O
wish	O
i	O
could	O
hear	O
ur	O
voice	O
doe	O

Testing	O
going	O
well	O
for	O
this	O
undocumented	O
system	O
.	O
Learned	O
more	O
about	O
JUnit	B-MISC
CI	I-MISC
for	O
this	O
project	O
.	O

$15	O
For	O
$30	O
Worth	O
Of	O
Fine	O
Wines	O
,	O
Cocktails	O
And	O
Beer	O
At	O
Maeve	O
at	O
Maeve	O
http://bit.ly/k7588R	O
#HomeRun	O

@StrawberryJazzy	B-PER
#KompoundFridays	O
@clubadriannas	O
=	O
#Party	O
til	O
5am	O
.	O
#LadiesNiteLive	O
Ladies	O
FREE	O
til	O
12a	O
Fellas	O
,	O
$5	O
til	O
12a	O
Let	O
's	O
Party	O
PLZ	O
RT	O

Business/Medical/Consumer	O
Mailing	O
lists	O
|	O
REVIVAL	O
http://bit.ly/cQXuOe	O

Thursday	O
means	O
Chicago	B-LOC
magician	O
day	O
!	O
Check	O
out	O
Edd	B-PER
Fairman	I-PER
tonight	O
!	O
http://wp.me/pr8rS-WY	O

@pts52	B-PER
It	O
was	O
great	O
!	O
I	O
got	O
lucky	O
and	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
rain	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
caulking	O
the	O
walls	O
and	O
putting	O
in	O
insulation	O
:)	O

Google	B-ORG
Voice	O
available	O
to	O
all	O
,	O
for	O
FREE	O
!	O
http://ht.ly/21Qsu	O

@HeidiEKMassey	B-PER
Now	O
we	O
get	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
either	O
plan	O
passes	O
....	O
Personally	O
I'm	O
assuming	O
Congress	O
will	O
try	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
whatever	O
decisions	O
it	O
can	O
.	O

@hymnforrachel	O
That	O
's	O
what	O
we're	O
going	O
for	O
:)	O

The	O
Postelles	B-MISC
photo	O
essay	O
from	O
their	O
tour-ending	O
show	O
in	O
Chicago	B-LOC
@	O
Schubas	O
(	O
The	O
Dig	O
opening)	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/jUWguq	O
#The	O
Postelles	O
#	O
Schubas	O

@_beautifulghost	O
yeah	O
i	O
see	O
...	O
hmmmm	O
...	O
jerk	O
.	O

Video	O
and	O
the	O
Net	O
,	O
Web	O
1994	O
.	O
The	O
Guardia	O
n.A	O
decade	O
before	O
youtube	O
http://tinyurl.com/dyofyx	O

Remember	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
50	O
dollars	O
to	O
waste	O
on	O
a	O
webcam	O
?	O
#GoodTimes	O
#HateBeingBroke	O
#NeedAJob	O

We	O
miss	O
you	O
Elizabeth	B-PER
Taylor	I-PER
!	O
You	O
always	O
knew	O
how	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
world	O
sparkling	O
.	O
http://ht.ly/4nlSw	O

@TheSuniverse	O
You're	O
not	O
kidding	O
.	O
I'm	O
hungry	O
!	O

Economist	O
debate	O
on	O
Arab	B-MISC
revolutions	O
-	O
http://econ.st/eDvT9r	O
(	O
h/t	O
:	O
@dchatt2)	O
.	O
Cool	O
to	O
see	O
Angry	O
Arab	O
at	O
the	O
Economist	O
.	O

OUCH	O
:	O
http://ow.ly/59fZD	O

A	O
nice	O
intro	O
2	O
the	O
statistical	O
issues	O
behind	O
teacher	O
evaluations	O
.	O
Teacher	O
Rankings	O
,	O
Once	O
Internal	O
,	O
Are	O
Now	O
Questioned	O
http://nyti.ms/eqeyTN	O

@AlexPominville	B-PER
NOT	O
sad	O
!	O
Let	O
the	O
birthday	O
countdown	O
begin	O
!!!	O

Ha	O
!	O
RT	O
@heyppanda	B-PER
:	O
@MtropolisCoffee	O
you	O
have	O
befilthed	O
and	O
defiled	O
me	O
,	O
4square	O
strumpet	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
I	O
shan't	O
show	O
my	O
face	O
in	O
public	O
again	O
;)	O

@Sprinkz_Ontop	O
LOL	O
...	O
DATS	O
WHY	O
I	O
DONT	O
FUCK	O
WIT	O
DESE	O
HOES	O
...	O
LOL	O

Gorgeous	O
white	O
silence	O
.	O
http://picplz.com/mXZw	O

Bummer	O
....	O
RT	O
@mlbcubs	O
:	O
Pittsburgh	O
Pirates	O
6	O
-	O
#Chicago	B-LOC
#Cubs	B-MISC
3	O
Bot	O
9	O

@MonnMonn2789	O
Stop	O
paying	O
top	O
dollar	O
at	O
GC	O
,	O
check	O
us	O
out	O
:	O
http://ow.ly/lqsH	O
http://ow.ly/1c0ZEb	O

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JER2HiO02nY	O
http://fb.me/yeihFpmw	O

Special	B-MISC
Forces	I-MISC
Winter	B-MISC
Ball	I-MISC
tonight	O
!	O
So	O
thankful	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
men	O
and	O
women	O
who	O
have	O
served	O
or	O
are	O
currently	O
serving	O
..	O
from	O
bottom	O
of	O
my	O
heart	O
.	O

Surviving	O
Disruption	O
in	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
the	O
Customer	O
http://t.co/19yt4Mj	O
via	O
@adage	O

Honored	O
to	O
be	O
asked	O
to	O
serve	O
on	O
the	O
Council	O
on	O
Foundations	O
family	O
#philanthropy	O
committee	O
for	O
the	O
next	O
2	O
years	O
.	O
Can't	O
wait	O
for	O
Philly	B-LOC
4/10	O
!	O

wants	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
Pitchfork	B-MISC
this	O
weekend	O
?	O
And	O
who	O
are	O
you	O
excited	O
to	O
see	O
play	O
?	O
http://fb.me/ARj3j9IX	O

Articles	O
:	O
McDonald	O
's	O
National	O
Hiring	O
Day	O
Offers	O
50,000	O
Jobs	O
http://goo.gl/fb/lB98C	O

http://fb.me/wBgH9JAN	O

@eikcaJRobyn	B-PER
and	O
like	O
so	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
coming	O
!	O
I	O
don't	O
even	O
think	O
they'll	O
see	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
crowd	O

@_Wintervention	O
LINK	O

We	O
all	O
know	O
to	O
dress	O
our	O
bedrooms	O
in	O
soothing	O
colors	O
.	O
Question	O
is	O
,	O
what	O
counts	O
as	O
soothing	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
via	O
@AptTherapy	O
http://bit.ly/gHm3IA	O

Training	O
students	O
in	O
interdisciplinary	O
research	O
requires	O
teaching	O
new	O
ways	O
of	O
thinking	O
:	O
systemic	O
,	O
holistic	O
,	O
integrative	O
,	O
complex	O
#scitsconf	O

Thanks	O
!	O
Our	O
salads	O
are	O
over-sized	O
,	O
healthy	O
&	O
delicious	O
RT	O
@NetUpSports	O
:	O
@Midtown_Kitchen	B-ORG
is	O
a	O
great	O
eatery	O
.	O
Tell	O
us	O
about	O
your	O
specialties	O
?	O

@VetsPrevail	O
I	O
LOVE	O
what	O
you're	O
doing	O
for	O
our	O
troops	O
.	O
Thank	O
you	O
and	O
keep	O
it	O
up	O
!	O

Having	O
a	O
hard	O
time	O
understanding	O
the	O
#Facebook	O
privacy	O
poilcy	O
?	O
It	O
has	O
been	O
re-written	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
easy	O
to	O
understand	O
http://on.mash.to/dPEAzw	O

@RLBrown3	B-PER
those	O
two	O
are	O
forgiveable	O
.	O
:)	O

@djjazzyjeff215	B-PER
What	O
it	O
do	O
Fade	O
?	O
I	O
got	O
something	O
hot	O
that	O
i	O
need	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Do	O
me	O
a	O
favor	O
and	O
shoot	O
me	O
your	O
contact	O
info	O
to	O
my	O
inbox	O
.	O

Amazing	O
view	O
!	O
RT	O
@SupertravelSki	O
:	O
Not	O
a	O
bad	O
view	O
from	O
Courchevel	O
1850	O
today	O
-	O
even	O
nicer	O
in	O
the	O
winter	O
though	O
!	O
http://yfrog.com/h0b50csj	O

#BEARS	O
!	O
#BEARS	O
!	O
#BEARS	O
!	O
R	O
U	O
READY	O
FOR	O
SOME	O
FOOTBALL	O
!!!	O

@jaytem	B-PER
yes	O
it	O
is	O
strange	O
.	O
We're	O
glad	O
you	O
got	O
it	O
working	O
and	O
flattered	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
look-	O
Thanks	O
!	O

#WhosGoing	O
?	O
to	O
#O	O
.	O
co	O
Coliseum	O
for	O
#Mariners	O
vs	O
#Athletics	O
#happy4thofjuly	O
-	O
http://t.co/JJ5heWc	O

@crabold	O
OMG	O
.	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
there	O
.	O

@spressto	O
Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
opportunity	O
!	O
#learnapalooza	O

Reading	O
RCIA	O
:	O
Giving	O
Personal	O
Testimony	O
(	O
guidelines	O
)	O
on	O
Scribd	O
http://scr.bi/f4bxby	O
#readcast	O

Breast	O
Cancer	O
Deaths	O
Drop	O
2%	O
But	O
Deaths	O
Still	O
Higher	O
Among	O
Black	O
women	O
,	O
U.S.	B-LOC
Report	O
Says	O
http://bit.ly/3pykis	O
.	O

I	O
cannot	O
wait	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
cold	O
shower	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
AC	O
.	O
It	O
us	O
so	O
humid	O
out	O
.	O

I'll	O
admit	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
garbage	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
Still	O
some	O
soap	O
left	O
and	O
bottle	O
needs	O
to	O
be	O
recycled	O
;)	O
http://fb.me/19Nw5biqw	O

Another	O
Fly	O
Vintage	O
"	O
Fly	O
By	O
"	O
post	O
coming	O
tomorrow	O
!	O

I	O
posted	O
a	O
new	O
photo	O
to	O
Facebook	B-ORG
http://fb.me/PpQdGy9s	O

Declaration	O
1776	O
Release	O
Beautiful	O
New	O
Wood	O
iPhone	B-MISC
Cases	O
http://t.co/LMzoPrY	O
via	O
@iamthetrend	O
@declaration1776	O

There	O
are	O
still	O
some	O
seats	O
available	O
for	O
our	O
American	B-MISC
Girl	I-MISC
Dinner	B-MISC
&	I-MISC
Prvt	B-MISC
Cruise	I-MISC
-	O
call	O
877-247-5223	O
to	O
reserve	O
ur	O
spot	O
!	O
http://t.co/A2GdlA6	O

Cute	O
cartoon	O
about	O
how	O
everyone	O
(	O
even	O
other	O
browsers	O
)	O
hates	O
IE6	B-MISC
.	O
Even	O
IE7	B-MISC
.	O
http://bit.ly/14OeRN	O

Moon	O
moving	O
to	O
oppose	O
sun	O
:	O
Full	O
Moon	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
until	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
Find	O
FM	O
in	O
your	O
chart	O
to	O
see	O
where	O
it	O
lights	O
up	O
your	O
chart/issue	O
.	O
#astrology	O

New	O
Blog	O
Post	O
:	O
Hong	B-LOC
Kong	I-LOC
:	O
Gay	O
Rights	O
on	O
the	O
Horizon	O
?	O
http://mygaychicago.com/p4tp	O

@DriXander	B-PER
lol	O
right	O
?	O

CWS	O
:	O
Chicago	B-LOC
White	O
Sox	O
Echo	O
Desert	O
Dry	O
Polo	O
By	O
Antigua	B-LOC
http://bit.ly/kQgteN	O

"	O
RT	O
@EgyptianInspire	O
:	O
Check	O
out	O
my	O
new	O
range	O
of	O
organic	O
hemp	O
jewellery	O
http://t.co/h9VifHG	O
#pagan	O
#handmadebot	O
#ecofriendly	O
"	O

I	O
uploaded	O
a	O
YouTube	B-ORG
video	O
--	O
Wiggleworms	O
http://youtu.be/80iAuPunMdM?a	O

@jgharding	B-PER
You	O
need	O
a	O
Chargepod	B-MISC
.	O
Seriously	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
help	O
you	O
.	O

@jessica_gardner	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
#Rapture	O
missed	O
us	O
.	O
At	O
least	O
until	O
October	O
.	O

We	O
recommend	O
checking	O
out	O
khadijahxx	O
http://soc.li/6law1VR	O

@paigeworthy	B-PER
White	O
Wineicus	O

Captain	O
Random	O
mix	O
for	O
International	O
Sundays	O
on	O
Mac-Trax	B-MISC
http://sns.ly/I4bPy0	O

Heading	O
to	O
my	O
last	O
promotion	O
and	O
review	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
semester	O
.	O
The	O
worst	O
committee	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
it	O
is	O
over	O
.	O

@spiffiness03	B-PER
Wah	O
wah	O
.	O
I'm	O
going	O
next	O
Thursday	O
up	O
here	O
.	O
Looking	O
forward	O
to	O
it	O
!	O

$	O
139.00	O
gets	O
Six-Week	O
Teen	O
Sports	O
Camp	O
at	O
Progressive	O
Sports	O
Performance	O
...	O
http://goo.gl/Z9DN5	O

@NoahTheSiamese	O
we	O
heard	O
that	O
Siamese	O
named	O
Noah	B-PER
especially	O
rule	O

SALE	O
!!	O
SALE	O
!!	O
SALE	O
!!	O
Go	O
to	O
www.w3body.com	O
and	O
get	O
your	O
shop	O
on	O
!	O
All	O
items	O
40%	O
off	O
!	O
enter	O
coupon	O
code	O
:	O
OFF40	O
Treat	O
yourself	O
for	O
the	O
Holiday	O
!	O

new	O
blog	O
post	O
on	O
the	O
Illinois	B-LOC
GOP	O
political	O
scene	O
http://bit.ly/LAcMM	O

Working	O
on	O
medical	O
#interpreting	O
article	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
the	O
one	O
thing	O
you	O
wish	O
you	O
were	O
trained	O
on	O
before	O
stepping	O
into	O
patient	O
situation	O
?	O

Good	O
morning	O

I	O
usually	O
like	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
grocery	O
store	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
thought	O
of	O
going	O
today	O
is	O
just	O
....	O
exhausting	O
.	O

#NYC	B-LOC
#Groupon	B-ORG
#deal	O
Enjoy	O
Austrian-style	O
chocolates	O
!	O
$30	O
Worth	O
of	O
Treats	O
at	O
Aigner	B-ORG
Chocolates	I-ORG
in	O
Queens	B-LOC
http://bit.ly/etQzGB	O

Styrofoam	O
cup	O
reenacts	O
your	O
weekend	O
.	O
http://t.co/dFxazce	O
via	O
@HappyPlace	O
#funny	O

Why	O
Your	O
Next	O
Post	O
Should	O
Be	O
a	O
Short	O
One	O
http://t.co/jMe8esa	O

@SouthrnDivaRach	O
I'm	O
a	O
Chicagoan	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
watch	O
!	O
;)	O

Never	O
seen	O
this	O
before	O
.	O
RT	O
ALambertpics	O
Adam	B-PER
&	O
Cher	B-PER
.	O
http://twitpic.com/5n8b25	O

Michelle	B-PER
Wittenberg	I-PER
Playboy	O
Coed	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
November	O
Week	O
3	O
http://bit.ly/9ORdnh	O

New	O
Flash	O
Builder	O
eases	O
development	O
,	O
but	O
Flash	B-MISC
still	O
no-go	O
for	O
iPhone	B-MISC
,	O
iPad	B-MISC
http://?.co.cc/eaaKTN	O

See	O
you	O
soon	O
RT	O
@ekelly7	O
:	O
@MakisuSushi	O
Can't	O
tonight	O
unfortunately	O
!	O
Definitely	O
want	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
at	O
some	O
point	O
though	O
!	O

Teddybears	O
Ft	O
B	O
.	O
O	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
-Get	O
Mama	O
A	O
House	O
(	O
Remix)	O
.	O
mp3	O
http://hulkshare.com/f3iv1shlyj7x	O

@PFV0	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
w	O
;	O

Bing	O
Rankings	O
Cheat	O
Sheet	O
|	O
Search	O
Engine	O
Journal	O
http://t.co/SrX1r5I	O
via	O
@sejournal	O

@Zulkey	O
not	O
a	O
bad	O
lunch	O
for	O
a	O
Friday	B-MISC
.	O
Thanks	O
for	O
coming	O
in	O
!	O

Nice	O
creative	O
site	O
:	O
http://t.co/6obzhpT	O
<	O
--	O
Like	O
it	O
.	O

I	O
kinda	O
wanna	O
see	O
@Who_NiNiLegend	O

@RecruiterSource	O
just	O
sent	O
you	O
2	O
DM's.	O

"	O
The	O
Conspirator	O
":	O
A	O
Lesson	O
in	O
Integrity	O
From	O
America	B-LOC
's	O
History	O
http://www.integriousproject.com/?p=2154	O

I'm	O
at	O
Barcelona	B-LOC
w/	O
@drewdoleski	B-PER
http://4sq.com/oMAByL	O

THIS	O
=	O
OUR	O
seminar	O
forum	O
taking	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
@EXXXOTICA	O
convention	O
!	O
"	O
ADULT	O
Industry	O
vs	O
.	O
SEX	O
industry	O
"	O
http://t.co/UacdoZA	O
#sexwork	O
#porn	O

@GrayThom	O
Grace	O
!	O
Download	O
@BarelyBlind	O
's	O
new	O
song	O
,	O
"	O
Love	O
!	O
(	O
Isn't	O
Everything)	O
,"	O
for	O
FREE	O
at	O
http://t.co/YIX0iAm	O
!	O

We	O
got	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
weekly	O
playlist	O
on	O
SELECTOR	O
a	O
blog	O
from	O
Tijuana	B-LOC
,	O
Mexico	B-LOC
!	O
Saludos	O
!!!	O
http://fb.me/NTTamGjO	O

@KRICHENT	O
Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
link	O
.	O
You	O
should	O
register	O
on	O
our	O
sister	O
site	O
to	O
gain	O
more	O
exposure	O
;	O
just	O
launched	O
in	O
beta	O
:	O
http://www.goproorno.com	O

Topshop	O
Sets	O
Up	O
Instagram-Styled	B-ORG
Photoshoots	O
in	O
Stores	O
http://tiny.ly/TtEF	O

Civic	O
Job	O
:	O
Start	O
Your	O
Environmental	O
Career	O
,	O
Run	O
a	O
Campaign	O
to	O
Protect	O
Our	O
Oceans	O
(	O
Chicago	B-LOC
)	O
http://ow.ly/1bU6cs	O

YOU	O
GIVE	O
ME	O
SOMETHING	O
OR	O
I	O
WILL	O
BREAK	O
YOUR	O
FUCKING	O
JAW	O
#nowthisisgettinggood	O
#copsdontlikepeds	O
#lanoire	O

It	O
's	O
a	O
new	O
portmanteau	O
:	O
the	O
"	O
oncoheart	O
"	O
to	O
describe	O
the	O
impact	O
of	O
cancer	O
or	O
its	O
treatment	O
on	O
cardiac	O
function	O
.	O
#snm2011	O

@bellybummom	O
Sure	O
thing	O
!	O

Oh	O
that	O
sounds	O
lovely	O
...	O
Good	O
choice	O
.	O
RT	O
@jenstuart27	B-PER
Once	O
again	O
,	O
I'm	O
laying	O
by	O
my	O
pool	O
rather	O
than	O
cleaning	O
my	O
apartment	O
.	O

LOL	O
LOL	O
,	O
so	O
there	O
.	O
RT	O
@DadStreet	O
:	O
@kounselor57	O
lol	O

How	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
look	O
at	O
Google	B-ORG
's	O
new	O
...	O
Facebook	B-ORG
?	O
How	O
to	O
look	O
inside	O
Google+	O
without	O
an	O
invite	O
|	O
How	O
To	O
-	O
@cnet	O
http://t.co/z89OYMk	O
#in	O

Looking	O
for	O
jobs/work/careers	O
in	O
IL	O
?	O
Check	O
DHResume	O
's	O
Big	O
List	O
of	O
Career	O
Fairs	O
.	O
http://tinyurl.com/px5vvs	O

Security	O
Expert	O
:	O
Sony	B-ORG
Knew	O
Its	O
Software	O
Was	O
Obsolete	O
Months	O
Before	O
PSN	O
Breach	O
-	O
http://bit.ly/kMCXWk	O

xRobe	B-ORG
Media	I-ORG
is	O
pleased	O
to	O
announce	O
our	O
newest	O
iphone	B-MISC
app	O
"	O
PocketPresence	B-MISC
"	O
Check	O
it	O
out	O
...	O
www.xrobe.com	O

Crescendo	O
Wednesdays	O
:	O
Chicago	B-LOC
's	O
Hottest	O
Industry	O
Night	O
!!	O

Want	O
to	O
host	O
a	O
food	O
drive	O
?	O
Email	O
jenny@	B-PER
lakeviewpantry.org	O
!	O

@miriama59	B-PER
us	O
too	O
!	O
Any	O
special	O
plans	O
?	O

FYI	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
some	O
last	O
minute	O
changes	O
that	O
wickedly	O
munged	O
Continuity	O
on	O
the	O
iPad	O
.	O
Will	O
fix	O
them	O
shortly	O
.	O
Sorry	O
,	O
happy	O
thanksgiving	O
;P	O
-Adam	B-PER

20	O
new	O
attractions	O
to	O
visit	O
in	O
the	O
U.S.	B-LOC
and	O
Canada	B-LOC
!	O
Each	O
one	O
is	O
as	O
different	O
as	O
the	O
next	O
--	O
http://ow.ly/472Xa	O

Bowl	O
for	O
less	O
.	O
$9	O
for	O
two	O
games	O
and	O
shoe	O
rental	O
at	O
Whitestone	B-ORG
Lanes	I-ORG
in	O
#NYC	B-LOC
.	O
http://so-kt.tw/4yT	O
#bowling	O
#discounts	O

Bye	O
,	O
bye	O
bracket	O
.	O
See	O
you	O
next	O
year	O

TV	O
HISTORY	O
-	O
June	O
1,198	O
0	O
-	O
Cable	B-ORG
News	I-ORG
Network	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
CNN	B-ORG
)	I-ORG
made	O
its	O
debut	O
as	O
the	O
first	O
all-news	O
station	O
.	O
http://www.museum.tv	O

@UnoHype	O
@mysoulalamode	O
Yessir	O
.	O
u	O
still	O
recordin	O
?	O
im	O
bout	O
to	O
hit	O
you	O
up	O
when	O
im	O
done	O

Jeff	B-PER
aka	O
Batman	B-MISC
looks	O
ridiculous	O
with	O
his	O
mask	O
,	O
a	O
knit	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sterling	O
silver	O
chain	O
.	O
#bachelorette	B-MISC

@ChuyHeyZeus	O
I	O
hate	O
because	O
I	O
never	O
rode	O
.	O

Just	O
sent	O
out	O
"	O
Newbie	B-MISC
Niche	I-MISC
Site	B-MISC
Month	I-MISC
"	O
week	O
#1	O
e-mail	O
!	O
If	O
you're	O
on	O
my	O
list	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
getting	O
it	O
shortly	O
.	O

I	O
just	O
updated	O
my	O
Weebly	B-ORG
website	O
,	O
check	O
it	O
out	O
:	O
http://breeanelyse.weebly.com	O

Back	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
http://fb.me/E5zQvivk	O

?	O
Follow	O
ME	O
,	O
I'll	O
Follow	O
Back	O
?	O
@jaysymoneDGAF	O
@SBreeze_	O
@MyTimeNow__	O
@MRS17NISHA	O
@Spoeticah	O
@ViolateDatBxtch	O
@ayo_melbrown	O
@Reaso	O

I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
a	O
more	O
thought	O
provoking	O
or	O
beautiful	O
movie	O
.	O
#thetreeoflife	B-MISC

@ahachirunner	B-PER
It	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
hot	O
and	O
tough	O
out	O
there	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
When	O
it	O
does	O
,	O
remember	O
why	O
you	O
#runwithheart	O
and	O
keep	O
going	O
!	O

Should	O
Twitter	O
be	O
a	O
mandatory	O
tool	O
for	O
reporters	O
?	O
I	O
wonder	O
how	O
many	O
don't	O
use	O
Twitter	O
at	O
the	O
moment	O
...	O
http://ow.ly/3s9qb	O

@eventbrite	B-PER
Sure	O
thanks	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
has	O
happened	O
twice	O
now	O
.	O
Lucky	O
ducks	O
got	O
tickets	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
supposed	O
to	O
get	O
!	O
:)	O

@design006	O
Hey	O
thanks	O
.	O
What	O
a	O
nice	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
:-)	O

Get	O
10%	O
OFF	O
of	O
first	O
Office	O
assignment	O
!	O
Redeem	O
on	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
office	O
visit	O
!	O
(	O
See	O
FB	O
coupon	O
!	O
)	O

Ooooo	O
Canada	B-LOC
--	O
no	O
Stanley	O
Cup	O
for	O
theeeeeee	O
....	O
#bruins	B-ORG
#canucks	B-ORG
#vanbos	O

@life_iz_short	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
#FF	O
#GGMU	O

@melingaling	B-PER
r	O
u	O
at	O
the	O
airport	O
?	O

Had	O
a	O
few	O
Bridgeport	B-LOC
Summer	O
Squeezes	O
last	O
night	O
.	O
Lemongrass	O
flavor	O
was	O
nice	O
&	O
I	O
don't	O
know	O
WTF	O
yuzu	O
is	O
but	O
it	O
had	O
that	O
too	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
's	O
cool	O
.	O

@Playb0yRF4L	B-PER
http://plixi.com/p/83451431	O
thank	O
you	O
honey	O
!!!!!!!	O
:)	O

Lovely	O
day	O
in	O
#Chicago	B-LOC
http://instagr.am/p/HFuF6/	O

Thanks	O
to	O
@Entlinx	O
@StuartFilms	O
and	O
@mediamoiselle	O
for	O
taking	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
meet	O
and	O
show	O
us	O
around	O
#NYC	B-LOC
.	O
See	O
you	O
guys	O
real	O
soon	O
.	O

Chi	O
Coffee	O
round	O
2	O
:	O
DarkCloud	O
for	O
some	O
more	O
Intelli	O
and	O
some	O
Counter	O
Culture	O
#IGotTheShakes	O
(	O
cc	O
@stephenschuh	B-PER
)	O

Does	O
your	O
shower	O
head	O
fill	O
a	O
one-gallon	O
bucket	O
in	O
less	O
that	O
20	O
sec	O
?	O
Replace	O
the	O
showerhead	O
with	O
a	O
water-efficient	O
model	O
http://ow.ly/5gsBh	O

http://smbchicago7.eventbrite.com/	O
registration	O
is	O
now	O
open	O
!	O

@bsuthers	O
@salute24	O
yes	O
Becky	B-PER
,	O
they	O
are	O
standard	O
issued	O
for	O
Metro	O
staff	O
.	O

Google	B-ORG
+1	O
Button	O
on	O
More	O
Homepages	O
than	O
Tweet	O
Button	O
(	O
with	O
pretty	O
graphics	O
to	O
boot	O
!	O
)	O
http://ow.ly/5BzFk	O
^ag	O

nevershoutnever	O
video	O
premiere	O
.	O
Check	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
enter	O
my	O
contest	O
for	O
tix	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
!!	O
http://bit.ly/btVNB5	O

New	O
@GuideStarUSA	B-ORG
report	O
on	O
2010	O
fundraising	O
trends	O
.	O
#SpecialEvent	O
#Fundraising	O
grew	O
50%	O
for	O
organizations	O
using	O
them	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/j7vp7x	O

Don't	O
miss	O
this	O
opportunity	O
of	O
a	O
lifetime	O
!!!!	O
Register	O
now	O
for	O
the	O
Flip	O
and	O
Grow	O
Rich	O
Workshop	O
!	O
www.FlipandGrowRichIn2011.com	O
...	O

Cabot	O
Q3	O
Profit	O
Up	O
32%	O
-	O
Update	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
company	O
's	O
core	O
segment	O
which	O
makes	O
the	O
pigmenting	O
agent	O
carbon	O
black	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/nuocsR	O
#in	O

at	O
whistler	O
~@redaeroplane	O

Tired	O
of	O
tryin	O
...	O
Giving	O
up	O
...	O

Know	O
anyone	O
who	O
's	O
ever	O
planning	O
on	O
having	O
a	O
child	O
?	O
PLEASE	O
make	O
sure	O
they	O
read	O
this	O
very	O
important	O
post	O
by	O
@kristinebrite	B-PER
:	O
http://ht.ly/2yvnA	O

DH	O
will	O
be	O
bring	O
home	O
our	O
new/used	O
car	O
tonight	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
another	O
2002	O
Focus	O
.	O
#Excited	O

I'm	O
one	O
bad	O
relationship	O
away	O
from	O
having	O
30	O
cats	O
.	O

She	O
really	O
needs	O
to	O
jump	O
on	O
the	O
twitter	O
train	O
RT	O
@ALmConley	O
Lunch	O
with	O
Ash	B-PER
and	O
@annasawicki	B-PER
today	O
!	O
#imissyou	O
Ashley	B-PER
!	O

Morning	O
!	O

Beginning	O
tomorrow	O
through	O
August	O
15	O
,	O
the	O
State	O
of	O
Illinois	B-LOC
will	O
waive	O
its	O
5%	O
sales	O
tax	O
fee	O
on	O
school	O
supplies	O
,...	O
http://fb.me/BgXZDXyE	O

$15	O
Industry	O
tickets	O
to	O
These	O
Shining	O
Lives	O
this	O
Thursday-	O
go	O
to	O
http://bit.ly/jSqnz	O
and	O
use	O
code	O
INDUSTRY	O
for	O
discount	O
!	O

@ksenkowski	B-PER
we	O
had	O
a	O
10	O
point	O
lead	O
,	O
they	O
can't	O
get	O
sloppy	O
now	O

"	O
We're	O
not	O
out	O
there	O
thinking	O
we're	O
Mad	B-MISC
Men	I-MISC
.	O
We're	O
just	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
jackasses	O
."	O
Classic	O
@arnettwill	B-PER
in	O
@papermagazine	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/jTFJ6I	O

Packing	O
for	O
the	O
show	O
see	O
ya	O
there	O
Sat	O
.	O
May	O
,	O
2	O
Norfolk	B-LOC
,	O
CT	B-LOC
-	O
The	O
Buckinghams	O
-Infinity	O
Hall	O
http://www.infinityhall.com	O
Tickets	O
866.666	O
.	O
6306	O

Sweet	O
Business	O
Opportunity	O
For	O
Buffalo	B-LOC
Grove	I-LOC
And	O
Beyond	O
!	O
-	O
http://listpipe.info/7bg	O

+1	O
RT	O
@aaronesilvers	B-PER
:	O
#techwk	O
Pritzker	B-PER
makes	O
a	O
convincing	O
argument	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
vibrant	O
start-up	O
community	O
in	O
Chicago	B-LOC
.	O

@guiltysquid	O
Are	O
you	O
really	O
yelling	O
about	O
ham	O
?	O
http://heyerin.posterous.com/gorgeous-and-bronzed-ginger-glazed-ham	O
Like	O
zees	O
?	O

TY	O
4	O
RT	O
&	O
#FF	O
#EM	O
xx	O
@2morrowknight	O
@zbleumoon	B-PER
@myEARTH360	B-PER
@ecoleaders	O
@CargoRoyale	O
@LynnHasselbrgr	O
@HeidiEKMassey	O

Oh	O
...	O
no	O
....	O
what	O
color	O
will	O
the	O
accent	O
wall	O
be	O
...	O

@teniralCist	O
:	O
@jamesogarcia	B-PER
found	O
your	O
#missingiPhone	O
!	O
You're	O
at	O
#YOURSProject	O
right	O
now	O
...	O
so	O
you	O
won't	O
find	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
while	O
.	O

@kwiller	B-PER
thanks	O
for	O
coming	O
out	O
:)	O

Fiske	O
Interactive	O
Featured	O
on	O
ABC	O
Chicago	B-LOC
http://t.co/nfjzaHO	O
via	O
@Sourcebooks	O

Saudi	O
women	O
defy	O
ban	O
to	O
take	O
driver	O
's	O
seat	O
-	O
Middle	B-LOC
East	I-LOC
-	O
Al	O
Jazeera	O
English	O
-	O
Mozilla	O
Firefox	O
http://ow.ly/5kLF2	O

How	O
many	O
people	O
will	O
show	O
up	O
for	O
kickboxing	O
on	O
Memorial	O
Day	O
?	O
Guesses	O
?	O

@SADBblog	O
Aw	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
so	O
much	O
fun	O
!	O
I	O
think	O
we	O
could	O
talk	O
him	O
into	O
it	O
...	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
your	O
spare	O
time	O
,	O
mama	O
.	O
;)	O

Join	O
@cheftoddstein	B-PER
next	O
Thursday	O
@GreenCityMarket	B-ORG
for	O
the	O
Chef	O
BBQ	O
Benefit	O
.	O
Taste	O
local	O
,	O
seasonal	O
dishes	O
from	O
the	O
city	O
's	O
best	O
chefs	O
!	O

@pohlmedia	O
Whats	O
up	O
buddy	O
!	O
im	O
about	O
to	O
post	O
another	O
10	O
videos	O
onto	O
my	O
youtube	O
chanel	O
!	O
www.youtube.com/leoTVnow	O

@annsrants	O
Did	O
we	O
manage	O
to	O
lull	O
you	O
to	O
sleep	O
at	O
a	O
reasonable	O
hour	O
?	O

#Econ101withContessaBrewer	O
-	O
Gross	O
Domestic	O
Product	O
:	O
really	O
icky	O
things	O
that	O
some	O
companies	O
sell	O
.	O
Like	O
dirt	O
and	O
stuff	O
.	O

Chris	B-PER
Kennedy	I-PER
leaving	O
the	O
Merchandise	O
Mart	O
.	O
Mark	B-PER
Falanga	I-PER
to	O
replace	O
as	O
head	O
.	O
via	O
@chicagotribune	O
:...	O
http://fb.me/wigq61Jy	O

@Allergychefsinc	O
Thanks	O
,	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
show	O
.	O

(	O
70	O
)	O
Haworth	O
Improv	O
Task	O
Chairs	O
(	O
Red	O
)	O
http://dlvr.it/Mf8G0	O

Halftime	O
fun	O
in	O
Omaha	B-LOC
!	O
http://yfrog.com/hswcruj	O

@cuelight	O
@andgoodbye	O
mmmm	O
,	O
that	O
does	O
sound	O
good	O
!	O

@jpkirchmeier	O
Thanks	O
for	O
spreading	O
the	O
word	O
!	O

@oharris69	O
You've	O
found	O
it	O
a	O
productive	O
system	O
?	O

@AlliStolper	B-PER
oh	O
no	O
!	O
that	O
stinks	O
!	O

@markshaw	O
hello	O
would	O
you	O
please	O
check	O
out	O
my	O
website	O
,	O
jk	O
,	O
seriously	O
auto-dm	O
's	O
are	O
annoying	O

I'm	O
eager	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
our	O
Chief	O
Information	O
Officer	O
about	O
how	O
we	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
better	O
use	O
technology	O
to	O
offer	O
more	O
TIF	O
transparency	O
.	O

Enter	O
Digital	B-ORG
Innovation	I-ORG
's	O
Name	O
our	O
Technology	O
Contest	O
for	O
a	O
chance	O
to	O
WIN	O
Computer	O
Accessories	O
+	O
$250	O
.	O
Visit	O
http://bit.ly/fzwjRj	O

SO	O
excited	O
!	O
RT	O
@Cubs	O
:	O
The	O
wait	O
is	O
nearly	O
over	O
,	O
#Cubs	O
fans	O
.	O
#OpeningDay	O
is	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
Who	O
's	O
coming	O
out	O
to	O
Wrigley	B-LOC
?	O

Robert	B-PER
Ellis	I-PER
'	O
record	O
,	O
"	O
Photographs	B-MISC
"	O
comes	O
out	O
July5	O
.	O
Touring	O
now	O
,	O
residency	O
in	O
Portland	B-LOC
upcoming	O
.	O
Hear	O
track	O
free	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/mRKlDT	O

#America	B-LOC
!	O
Fuck	O
yeah	O
!	O

@toosunnyouthere	O
...	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
f-ing	O
bank	O
like	O
an	O
adult	O
...	O

saddle	O
up	O
your	O
zebras	O
,	O
tomorrow	O
's	O
Friday	O
!	O

Seeking	O
pleasure	O
with	O
your	O
friends	O
may	O
sound	O
like	O
a	O
great	O
idea	O
...	O
More	O
for	O
Libra	O
http://twittascope.com/?sign=7	O

Hey	O
Chicago	B-LOC
!	O
Tyrese	B-PER
called	O
us	O
personally	O
to	O
apologize	O
for	O
missing	O
the	O
Transformers	B-MISC
screening	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
got	O
a	O
good	O
reason	O
!	O
http://bit.ly/14mNwR	O

Can't	O
wait	O
!	O
RT	O
@WholeFoodsSCH	B-MISC
:	O
#GreenHalloween	O
party	O
at	O
our	O
store	O
on	O
Sat	O
10/16	O
,	O
We'll	O
have	O
a	O
costume	O
swap	O
,	O
a	O
trick	O
or	O
treat	O
trail	O
,	O
&	O
more	O
!	O

Top	O
of	O
the	O
4th	O
:	O
CWS	B-ORG
1	O
,	O
Cle	B-ORG
0	O

"	O
@Yahoo	B-ORG
:	O
Finding	O
city	O
w/good	O
jobs	O
,	O
cheap	O
housing	O
difficult	O
in	O
our	O
economy	O
,	O
not	O
impossible	O
:	O
http://t.co/rcAs0ZC	O
"	O
I	O
was	O
hoping	O
CA	B-LOC
was	O
on	O
list	O

Specials/Events	O
for	O
Today	O
:	O
PaulStar	B-PER
Jam/Open	O
Mic	O
.	O
Hosted	O
by	O
Paul	B-PER
Allodi	I-PER
-	O
8:30	O
pm	O
.	O
Free	O
8:30	O
p-	O
2:00	O
a	O

Mmmm	O
RT	O
@DMKBurgerBar	O
:	O
Check	O
out	O
the	O
new	O
website	O
(	O
with	O
new	O
menu)	O
!	O
www.dmkburgerbar.com	O

The	O
fact	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
is	O
the	O
Bulls	B-ORG
proved	O
a	O
point	O
this	O
season	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
still	O
denying	O
them	O
?	O

@jmloquist	B-PER
And	O
yeah	O
,	O
I	O
figured	O
if	O
they'd	O
reopened	O
the	O
gates	O
everyone	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
tizzy	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
what	O
I	O
get	O
for	O
logging	O
off	O
last	O
night	O
...	O

Google	B-ORG
Makes	O
a	O
QR	O
Code	O
Turnaround	O
With	O
New	O
M&A	O
Deal	O
-	O
When	O
Google	O
discontinued	O
support	O
for	O
QR	O
codes	O
in	O
its	O
Places	O
pr	O
...	O
http://ow.ly/1dKJlR	O

@tristanofvp	B-PER
lmao	O
,	O
yea	O
everything	O
after	O
that	O
year	O
when	O
down	O
hill	O
...	O

@Kevin_NoHart	O
Idk	O

@FouFouDog_Matt	O
Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
positive	O
comments	O
about	O
my	O
site	O
,	O
http://lovedogswithjac.com	O

Today	O
is	O
the	O
day	O
!	O
The	O
big	O
Gran	O
Fondo	O
!	O
Hope	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
there	O
!!	O
http://bit.ly/jMGCVA	O

Take	O
an	O
additional	O
25%	O
off	O
all	O
sale	O
items	O
at	O
Reebok	O
.	O
com	O
with	O
coupon	O
code	O
though	O
9/6	O
.	O
Use	O
link	O
http://cpnurl.com/t/2IGKS	O

Search	O
Platform	O
|	O
Mortgage	O
Real	O
Estate	O
Insurance	O
Financial	O
Lawyer	O
|	O
Professional	O
Guys	O
&	O
Gals	O
:	O
http://www.professionalguysandgals.com	O

Want	O
to	O
lend	O
your	O
skills	O
to	O
benefit	O
Between	O
Friends	O
Chicago	B-LOC
and	O
support	O
the	O
organization	O
's	O
mission	O
to	O
end	O
domestic	O
...	O
http://fb.me/VsRlA9mP	O

PR	O
Tip	O
:	O
Try	O
not	O
to	O
mispell	O
anything	O
,	O
espacially	O
items	O
the	O
public	O
or	O
clients	O
will	O
red	O
.	O
LOL	O
.	O

Happy	O
11th	O
Birthday	O
to	O
my	O
Hunter	B-PER
Bear	O
.	O
It	O
wasn't	O
long	O
ago	O
we	O
babysat	O
you	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
We	O
miss	O
you	O
and	O
love	O
you	O
.	O

Catching	O
up	O
on	O
#showtime	O
The	B-MISC
Big	I-MISC
C	I-MISC
:-)	O

Just	O
wanted	O
to	O
say	O
hey	O
to	O
all	O
of	O
my	O
new	O
followers	O
and	O
thanks	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
comments	O
!	O

@sosodexomc	O
Thnks	O
,	O
U	O
R	O
the	O
best	O
!	O
married	O
cples	O
spend	O
an	O
avg	O
of	O
2.5	O
hrs	O
daily	O
..."	O
4rm	O
blog	O
by	O
@hahe4	O
http://bit.ly/knowyourco	O

Greater	O
West	O
Town	O
Community	O
Development	O
Project	O
links	O
employment	O
with	O
local	O
development	O
efforts	O
and	O
small	O
business	O
needs	O
http://ow.ly/3E2sC	O

and	O
an	O
older	O
married	O
Dutch	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
also	O
dining	O
alone	O
bought	O
my	O
dessert	O
...	O

If	O
you	O
keep	O
the	O
Sabbath	B-MISC
,	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
break	O
from	O
social	O
media	O
?	O
(	O
Maybe	O
we	O
should	O
ask	O
this	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
)	O
http://bit.ly/KeepSabbath	O

We	O
are	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
RT	O
@JasonDeline	B-PER
@TRMK	O
well	O
you	O
guys	O
are	O
there	O
,	O
right	O
?	O
And	O
Ed	B-PER
is	O
still	O
tweeting	O
!	O

Andrew	B-PER
will	O
be	O
featured	O
on	O
the	O
PBS	O
program	O
Austin	O
City	O
Limits	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
October	O
24th	O
along	O
with	O
St	O
.	O
Vincent	O
-	O
check	O
your	O
local	O
listings	O
.	O

@LindsHudson	B-PER
yo	O
what	O
up	O

IS	O
HIGH	O
SCHOOL	O
BAD	O
FOR	O
TEENS	O
'	O
MENTAL	O
HEALTH	O
?	O
-	O
Every	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
a	O
teenager	O
in	O
America	B-LOC
takes	O
his	O
or	O
her	O
own	O
life	O
.	O
Sui	O
...	O
http://ow.ly/1cIQVP	O

@ydyang	O
why	O
?	O

@RTJournal	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
about	O
the	O
free	O
Catechist	O
webinar	O
?	O
More	O
information	O
http://bit.ly/bNQv55	O

Reiki	B-ORG
Magic	I-ORG
Hands	B-ORG
for	I-ORG
Children	I-ORG
-	O
Abington	B-LOC
Memorial	I-LOC
Hospital	I-LOC
http://bit.ly/puotBt	O

Shout	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Money	O
Team	O
Thirsty	O
-	O
Code	O
Red	O
M.T.S	O
-	O
http://goo.gl/46xk1	O
#cyphop	O

Happy	O
Friday	O
Merchandise	B-MISC
Mart	I-MISC
!!	O
Sweet	O
Ride	O
is	O
on	O
her	O
way	O
!	O
Will	O
post	O
when	O
we	O
land	O
.	O

@ellief716	B-PER
I	O
don't	O
like	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
taking	O
the	O
Fairy	O
story	O
line	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
liked	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Should	O
be	O
interesting	O
!	O
#trueblood	O

What	O
I'm	O
reading	O
on	O
twitter	O
today	O
is	O
out	O
!	O
http://bit.ly/fzcUoc	O

What	O
's	O
your	O
favorite	O
thing	O
about	O
Fashion	O
Focus	O
Chicago	O
?	O
The	O
shows	O
?	O
The	O
people	O
?	O
The	O
designers	O
?	O
The	O
tent	O
?	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
!!	O

Treat	O
mom	O
to	O
something	O
sweet	O
!	O
Our	O
cookies	O
are	O
an	O
easy	O
choices	O
&	O
might	O
we	O
add	O
,	O
delicious	O
!	O
On	O
special	O
and	O
already	O
packaged	O
!	O
http://ow.ly/4OM3O	O

@UrFavCharity	O
something	O
Hex	B-PER
said	O
.	O

Completed	O
the	O
fourth	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Leadership	O
and	O
Management	O
series	O
here	O
at	O
Northwestern	O
today	O
.	O
Always	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
lots	O
of	O
food	O
for	O
thought	O
.	O

@StephanieMaggie	B-PER
that	O
was	O
funny	O

Photo	O
:	O
http://tumblr.com/xwi3cbgl2e	O

@antwonomous	O
thx	O
for	O
the	O
hitting	O
compliment	O
!	O

If	O
you	O
have	O
an	O
#android	O
,	O
live	O
in	O
#chicago	B-LOC
and	O
frequent	O
cabs	O
...	O
you	O
might	O
like	O
this	O
#app	O
,	O
LMK	O
http://t.co/oDGiKMN	O
via	O
@djfedor	O

Toe	O
nail	O
casualty	O
.	O
#cm10	O
#runnerds	O

is	O
now	O
talking	O
Jon	B-PER
Taffer	I-PER
of	O
the	O
Spike	B-ORG
TV	I-ORG
show	O
"	O
Bar	B-MISC
Rescue	I-MISC
."	O
Chicago	B-LOC
's	O
very	O
own	O
Abbey	O
Pub	O
is	O
featured	O
on	O
this	O
...	O
http://fb.me/XB8NmXVE	O

Site	O
temporarily	O
down	O
while	O
transfering	O
from	O
temp	O
to	O
live	O
...	O
Keep	O
checking	O
....	O

Stanley	B-PER
McChrystal	I-PER
at	O
TED	O
-	O
http://bit.ly/eCfG5Q	O
(	O
via	O
:	O
@abumuqawama	B-PER
)	O

A	O
local	O
food	O
#FF	O
@thelocalbeet	O
@FamilyFarmed	O
@cityprovisions	O
@ediblechicago	O

Pictures	O
:	O
New	O
Ruby-Eyed	O
Pit	O
Viper	O
Discovered	O
:	O
http://on.natgeo.com/h2Vtob	O
via	O
@NatGeoSociety	B-ORG
#nature	O
#photo	O

I'm	O
at	O
Lakeshore	B-ORG
Athletic	I-ORG
Club	I-ORG
(	O
211	B-LOC
N	I-LOC
Stetson	B-LOC
Ave	I-LOC
,	B-LOC
Lake	I-LOC
St	B-LOC
.,	I-LOC
Chicago	I-LOC
)	O
http://4sq.com/ij2L9i	O

@sanleeann	B-PER
@toyaw	B-PER
lmao	O
.	O
xD	O
.	O
I'm	O
shocked	O
you	O
got	O
it	O
!	O
It	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
matching	O
top	O
.	O

More	O
social	O
media	O
(#sm)	O
,	O
food	O
trucks	O
ahead	O
in	O
2011	O
http://bit.ly/eQJbA0	O

@wolfarms	O
please	O
subscribe	O
me	O
to	O
your	O
140-character	O
film	O
review	O
column	O
.	O

There	O
is	O
no	O
separation	O
between	O
the	O
secular	O
and	O
the	O
sacred	O
,	O
God	B-PER
claims	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
your	O
work	O
,	O
your	O
relationships	O
,	O
even	O
ur	O
sleep	O
/via	O
@carlesims	B-PER

Is	O
Your	O
Twitter	B-ORG
Just	O
Retail	O
Junk	O
Mail	O
?	O
http://bit.ly/w1yvv	O

Stimulate	O
Creativity	O
with	O
the	O
SCAMPER	O
Mnemonic	O
-	O
@Lifehacker	O
http://t.co/34i4BQB	O

Summer	O
survey	O
#8	O
:	O
Own	O
the	O
Garden	B-MISC
State	I-MISC
soundtrack	O
?	O
You	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
Wicker	O
Park	O
Fest	O
this	O
weekend	O
.	O
http://avc.lu/nQtvZU	O

Checked	O
out	O
post	O
from	O
@ebertchicago	O
lead	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
up	O
music	O
by	O
t	B-PER
griffin	I-PER
&	O
heard	O
a	O
nice	O
song	O
here	O
http://www.shinylittlerecords.com/	O

New	O
Wiz	B-PER
Khalifa	I-PER
,	O
J	B-PER
.	I-PER
Cole	I-PER
,	O
Cam'ron	B-PER
&	O
Vado	B-PER
,	O
and	O
Young	B-PER
Jeezy	I-PER
Mixtapes	O
!	O

yes	O
i	O
do	O
!!	O
RT	O
@BeckyReyes	B-PER
:	O
@erikajanelle	B-PER
has	O
me	O
on	O
a	O
country	O
kick	O

Outside	O
markets	O
lift	O
commodities	O
,	O
but	O
US	B-LOC
weather	O
particularly	O
conducive	O
to	O
a	O
timely	O
planting	O
in	O
April	O
.	O

Is	O
FaceCash	O
the	O
future	O
of	O
mobile	O
payments	O
?	O
http://tnw.to/1A8az	O

#serotta	O
RT	O
@SharkJumper	O
:	O
loop	O
of	O
central	O
park	O
on	O
my	O
trusty	O
serotta	O
aka	O
the	O
orange	O
menace	O
.	O
so	O
far	O
so	O
good	O
,	O
my	O
hip	O
not	O
killing	O
me	O
...	O
yay	O
4	O
me	O
!	O

dear	O
girl	O
at	O
Jimmy	O
John's,	O
popping	O
a	O
birth	O
control	O
pill	O
in	O
front	O
of	O
a	O
slew	O
of	O
customers	O
might	O
be	O
bad	O
for	O
business	O
.	O
oh	O
ya	O
,	O
you	O
disgust	O
me	O
.	O

In	O
case	O
you	O
were	O
still	O
worried	O
,	O
you'll	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
our	O
power	O
is	O
BACK	O
,	O
our	O
refrigerated	O
items	O
survived	O
,	O
and	O
we're	O
back	O
at	O
it	O
!	O

At	O
Applebees	O
in	O
Milwaukee	B-LOC
.	O
My	O
friend	O
"	O
checked-in	O
"	O
here	O
,	O
the	O
popular	O
tip	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
says	O
"	O
worst	O
service	O
ever	O
!!".	O
The	O
tip	O
is	O
accurate	O
.	O

Ha	O
!	O
RT	O
@ChuckGarfien	B-PER
:	O
Here	O
are	O
the	O
White	B-ORG
Sox	I-ORG
throwback	O
uniforms	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
see(for	O
entertainment	O
purposes	O
only)	O
.	O
http://twitpic.com/5r8dq7	O

Faster	O
recovery	O
time	O
too	O
!	O
RT	O
@Athleticbiz	O
:	O
Surgeon	O
demonstrates	O
new	O
technique	O
to	O
repair	O
torn	O
ACLs	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/izP9hU	O

LOTR	B-MISC
Fans	O
-	O
Do	O
you	O
have	O
your	O
tickets	O
yet	O
?	O
http://bit.ly/KerasotesLOTR	O
If	O
not	O
,	O
CLICK	O
HERE	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/KerasotesComingSoon	O

@CafeBaBaReeba	B-MISC
I	O
can	O
only	O
pick	O
one	O
#tapas	O
?	O
I	O
Must	O
have	O
two	O
!	O
The	O
artisinal	O
cheese	O
plate	O
AND	O
the	O
spanish	O
olives	O
!	O
YUM	O
!!!!	O

LOL	O
@andreaszutenbac	O
!	O
Glad	O
I'm	O
not	O
the	O
only	O
one	O
!	O
A	O
friend	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
worst	O
dancer	O
he'd	O
ever	O
seen	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
imagine	O
what	O
I	O
look	O
like	O

Don't	O
forget	O
the	O
annual	O
Common	B-ORG
Threads	I-ORG
'	B-ORG
World	I-ORG
Festival	I-ORG
is	O
tonight	O
at	O
Soldier	O
Field	O
!	O

Halo	O
,	O
Ellen	B-PER
DeGeneres	I-PER
donate	O
1	O
million	O
meals	O
to	O
shelter	O
#pets	O
http://ow.ly/3yDOE	O
#animalrescue	O
#dog	O

@zakiyafola	B-PER
i	O
was	O
replying	O
to	O
your	O
tweet	O
about	O
it	O
being	O
shocking	O
that	O
i	O
have	O
a	O
twitter	O
.	O
that	O
was	O
from	O
April	O
i	O
think	O
.	O
late	O
response	O
!	O

@NanciFilipelli	B-PER
@d1sports	O
yea	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
not	O
a	O
tough	O
decision	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
dunk	O
tank	O
duh	O
!!	O

Physicians	O
'	O
group	O
releases	O
top	O
5	O
recommendations	O
for	O
improving	O
primary	O
care	O
http://bit.ly/irPVbo	O

So	O
that	O
last	O
tweet	O
also	O
updated	O
to	O
my	O
Facebook	B-ORG
lol	O

Looking	O
to	O
buy	O
or	O
trade	O
for	O
;	O
2	O
technic	O
1200	O
turntables	O
new	O
or	O
used	O
.	O
To	O
all	O
my	O
DJ	O
buds	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
,	O
thanks	O
!!	O

I	O
am	O
excited	O
to	O
be	O
attending	O
the	O
Willow	O
Creek	O
Community	O
Church	O
Leadership	O
Summit	O
on	O
Aug	O
.	O
5	O
&	O
6	O

4	O
Ways	O
to	O
Successfully	O
Negotiate	O
a	O
Job	O
Offer	O
http://ow.ly/56zbS	O
#jobsearch	O
#negotiation	O
#careercoach	O

@CHAMP_No25	O
Stop	O
paying	O
top	O
dollar	O
at	O
GC	O
,	O
check	O
us	O
out	O
:	O
http://ow.ly/lqsH	O
http://ow.ly/1c3VKF	O

@haterface	B-PER
eek	O
!	O
Dieting	O
is	O
scary	O
.	O

the	O
eagles	B-MISC
look	O
good	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
have	O
to	O
get	O
V	B-PER
.	I-PER
Young	I-PER
tho	O
?	O
They	O
coulda	O
let	O
a	O
team	O
who	O
needs	O
him	O
get	O
him	O
.	O

Is	O
it	O
frowned	O
upon	O
to	O
talk/swear	O
at	O
yourself	O
during	O
the	O
GMAT	O
exam	O
?	O
I	O
hope	O
not	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
don't	O
know	O
how	O
I'll	O
survive	O
this	O
thing	O
if	O
I	O
can't.	O

Where	O
is	O
my	O
Al	B-PER
Green	I-PER
's	O
greatest	O
hits	O
CD	O
?	O
I'm	O
in	O
the	O
mood	O
to	O
relax	O
to	O
some	O
soulful	O
soothing	O
music	O

is	O
calling	O
for	O
interns	O
for	O
our	O
two	O
latest	O
projects	O
:	O
The	B-MISC
Bod	I-MISC
Squad	I-MISC
and	O
Days	B-MISC
of	I-MISC
the	B-MISC
Living	I-MISC
Dead	I-MISC
!	O
Send	O
email	O
to	O
info@joonestudios	O
.	O
com	O

Brandon	B-PER
on	O
@nerdlocker	O
is	O
our	O
sporting	O
"	O
Long	O
Live	O
The	O
Monarch	O
"	O
Tee	O
:	O
http://ow.ly/4SszB	O
Watch	O
here	O
:	O
http://ow.ly/4SsxZ	O

So	O
yummy	O
!	O
Definitely	O
was	O
not	O
disappointed	O
by	O
my	O
first	O
visit	O
ever	O
!	O
@cfawatertower	O
http://img.ly/56Ke	O
no	O
food	O
because	O
I	O
ate	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
second	O
.	O

I	O
aint	O
gone	O
even	O
lie	O
oomf	O
ugly	O
as	O
fuck	O
i	O
mean	O
like	O
damn	O
shorty	O
...	O
dont	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
mirror	O
cause	O
u	O
gone	O
piss	O
the	O
mirror	O
off	O

Pollution	O
alert	O
today	O
,	O
heat	O
index	O
could	O
reach	O
100	O
degrees	O
:	O
An	O
air	O
pollution	O
"	O
action	O
day	O
"	O
alert	O
has	O
been	O
issued	O
f	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/qXi9Hv	O

@mynameisevan	B-PER
#WelcometoTwitter	O
start	O
following	O
@chicagobulls	O
@DerrickRoseNews	O
@scusentino	O
@ChiSportsNews	O
@bearsbuzztap	O
learn	O
how	O
2	O
#hashtag	O

Enjoying	O
the	O
vocal	O
stylings	O
of	O
a	O
one	O
Mister	O
Rod	O
Stewart	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
tonight	O
on	O
a	O
downtown	O
train	O
.	O

For	O
more	O
information	O
about	O
our	O
Chicago	B-LOC
car	O
insurance	O
policies	O
,	O
visit	O
our	O
AboutUs	O
page	O
at	O
http://www.aboutus.org/InsureOnTheSpot.com	O

I'm	O
at	O
Pepe	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
Mexican	B-ORG
Restaurant	I-ORG
(	O
14853	O
S	O
.	O
Bell	O
Road	O
,	O
Homer	O
Glen	O
)	O
http://4sq.com/eQjA5s	O

welp	O
!	O
There	O
goes	O
television	O
,	O
n	O
all	O
otha	O
electronics	O
.	O
That	O
last	O
round	O
of	O
thunderin	O
knocked	O
everything	O
off	O
track	O
.	O
Prolly	O
til	O
sunrise	O
-_-	O
great	O
.	O

Is	O
$GS	O
,	O
$C	O
,	O
$JPM	O
,	O
$MS	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
$XLF	O
reversing	O
the	O
course	O
&	O
becoming	O
a	O
buy	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
looking	O
get	O
short	O
,	O
read	O
more	O
here	O
:	O
http://t.co/po429AC	O
,	O
$$	O

@diiniramadhanti	B-PER
hello	O
,	O
Im	O
quite	O
humble	O
as	O
well	O
.	O
@erifortomorrow	O
@xbitexmllx	O
thank	O
you	O
!	O
How	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
this	O
weekend	O
?	O

Great	O
!	O
RT	O
@rosettathurman	B-PER
:	O
10	O
Reasons	O
Why	O
Every	O
Young	O
Professional	O
Should	O
Have	O
a	O
Blog	O
http://ow.ly/2HxIV	O

And	O
of	O
course	O
,	O
a	O
HUGE	O
Thank	O
You	O
to	O
@gbyehuda	O
for	O
being	O
an	O
amazing	O
chair	O
person	O
...	O
again	O
!!	O
It	O
is	O
always	O
a	O
pleasure	O
#smgov	O

@SarahAshleen	B-PER
:	O
what	O
's	O
your	O
favorite	O
feature	O
?	O

@robynne64	O
soon	O
,	O
i	O
hope	O
.	O
lots	O
of	O
needs	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
so	O
i'll	O
keep	O
you	O
posted	O
.	O

Mmmmmmm....Bobaks	O
's	O
Polish	O
Sausage	O
#summertimechi	O

I	O
liked	O
a	O
YouTube	O
video	O
--	O
T-Pain	B-PER
Feat	O
D	O
Dukes-Merry	O
Christmas	O
!	O
http://youtu.be/-q0gyLntjTE?a	O

Fonts	O
Inspiration	O
:	O
60	O
Awesome	O
Font	O
Typography	O
Designs	O
http://t.co/MR597Uc	O
#communitynews	O
#in	O
#webdesign	O

@laymonhicks	B-PER
Great	O
idea	O

@_HUAdrianX_	O
Go	O
to	O
Meharry	O
!	O
Lol	O

She	O
luv	O
my	O
smile	O

Creating	O
My	O
Own	O
Lane	O
!!!	O

Literally	O
laughing	O
out	O
loud	O
RT	O
@TuckerMax	B-PER
:	O
I	O
can't	O
believe	O
Pikachu	B-PER
scored	O
on	O
Han	O
Solo	O
's	O
daughter	O
.	O
Terrible	O
.	O

Committing	O
to	O
memory	O
now	O
...	O
"	O
The	O
New	O
Rules	O
of	O
Business	O
Etiquette	O
"	O
(	O
Yahoo	O
Finance	O
)	O
http://yhoo.it/9oGKYL	O

Heading	O
to	O
@dmbcaravan	O
in	O
#Chicago	B-LOC
?	O
Better	O
leave	O
now	O
to	O
catch	O
Sunday	O
's	O
show	O
.	O
What	O
a	O
cluster	O
!	O

@GG30000	O
nice	O
interview	O
http://t.co/klHPAnw	O

Stationed	O
@Rokaakorchi	O
and	O
@Bombayspicechi	O
for	O
photoshoots	O
and	O
practice	O
parties	O
!	O

@NonAmericanHero	B-PER
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
shout	O
out	O
in	O
your	O
post	O
.	O

Breaking	O
:	O
2011	O
Country	O
Thunder	O
Headliners	O
include	O
Rascal	B-MISC
Flatts	I-MISC
!	O

Weekly	O
Piano	O
Improvisation	O
40	O
-	O
http://bit.ly/54QUGM	O

Come	O
to	O
"	O
Aetiology	O
-	O
Live	O
at	O
Goose	B-LOC
Island	I-LOC
"	O
Friday	O
,	O
February	O
12	O
from	O
9:00	O
pm	O
to	O
1:00	O
am	O
.	O
Aetiology	O
is	O
hitting	O
up	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/coBvx1	O

@wrestlgurl	B-PER
thanks	O
!	O
:)	O
pass	O
it	O
on	O
to	O
your	O
friends	O
please	O

@susanamendoza10	O
:)	O

Another	O
"	O
If	O
you	O
can't	O
tone	O
it	O
...	O
tan	O
it	O
day	O
"	O
:(	O
(@	O
Ultimate	O
Exposure	O
)	O
http://4sq.com/lGbAgz	O

Know	O
your	O
own	O
worth	O
in	O
your	O
field	O
and	O
industry	O
.	O

It	O
's	O
better	O
this	O
way	O
.	O
Numbs	O
the	O
pain	O
.	O
RT	O
@justinyourmind	O
:	O
Drunk	O
.	O
Already	O
.	O
@melissabalsan	O
knows	O
.	O

@Wonderwoman0991	O
TONIGHT	O
#ALLNEWCOLLEGENIGHT	O
@	O
#ClubEstrada	O
(	O
2639	O
W	O
.	O
Peterson	O
)	O
[	O
18+	O
To	O
Enter	O
]	O
*LADIES	O
DISC	O
TILL	O
10:30	O
PM*	O
RETWEET	O

Elena	B-PER
Kagan	I-PER
was	O
a	O
softball	O
masher	O
at	O
Chicago	B-ORG
Law	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
.	O
If	O
she	O
doesn't	O
make	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
Cubs	B-ORG
are	O
desperate	O
for	O
a	O
third	O
baseman	O
.	O

@Pilgrim945	O
because	O
Ashton	B-PER
has	O
shared	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
Demi	B-PER
's	O
blood	O
,	O
thus	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
perpetually	O
a	O
1/2	O
man	O
!	O
Silver	O
bullets	O
,	O
silver	O
bullets	O
.	O

#WhiteSox	O
pounding	O
#Indians	O
6-1	O
,	O
foggy	O
night	O
at	O
Cellular	O
Field	O
!	O

@thugzRus_22	B-PER
wtf	O
do	O
you	O
eat	O
?	O

@BethRosen	B-PER
It	O
was	O
wonderful	O
working	O
with	O
you	O
today	O
at	O
the	O
new	O
diggs	O
.	O
Finally	O
,	O
added	O
The	O
Tektite	O
Group	O
Offices	O
to	O
Foursquare	O
.	O

@emilyolson80	O
you	O
might	O
enjoy	O
today	O
's	O
Trend	O
Central	O
newsletter	O
http://www.trendcentral.com/life/foraged-feasting/	O

At	O
#cocktailsforcauses	B-ORG
!!	O
Are	O
you	O
?	O

@suziwalks	O
@jazzpastord	O
since	O
we're	O
feeling	O
so	O
poor	O
,	O
we're	O
having	O
tuna	O
casserole	O
as	O
comfort	O
food	O
this	O
evening	O
.	O

@SteveDahlShow	O
For	O
the	O
record	O
,	O
I	O
accidentally	O
left	O
our	O
bat	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
When	O
are	O
you	O
gonna	O
come	O
do	O
play-by-play	O
?	O

Watch	O
out	O
while	O
you're	O
making	O
breakfast	O
!	O
Hamilton	O
Beach	O
2-Slice	O
Toaster	O
recalled	O
for	O
fire	O
risks	O
http://ow.ly/5wUMe	O

Chicagoist|	O
Today	O
's	O
Google	B-ORG
Doodle	O
Inspired	O
by	O
Trip	O
to	O
MCA	O
:	O
Today	O
's	O
Alexander	B-PER
Calder	I-PER
tribute	O
Google	O
doodle	O
had	O
i	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/o5opsQ	O

Chicago	O
Hotel	O
Deal	O
-	O
Summer	O
's	O
almost	O
over	O
-	O
Twitter	B-ORG
rate	O
at	O
Hotel	O
71	O
-	O
http://tinyurl.com/28dby8v	O
-	O
$129/$149	O
Sun/Mon/Tues	O
nights	O
till	O
8/31	O
.	O

@KKrafty	B-PER
@designerjillian	B-PER
indeed	O
!	O
Come	O
check	O
us	O
out	O
!	O

Sonorous	O
Shades	O
:	O
Warm	O
Tones	O
at	O
#HeavenGallery	B-ORG
on	O
May	O
18	O
:	O
http://t.co/i7Y607m	O

I'm	O
at	O
Go	O
Roma	O
(	O
848	O
N	O
State	O
Street	O
,	O
Chestnut	B-LOC
,	O
Chicago)	B-LOC
.	O
http://4sq.com/7AB5Pp	O

Just	O
wanted	O
to	O
check	O
in	O
and	O
say	O
hello	O
!	O
I'm	O
having	O
a	O
blast	O
in	O
sunny	O
Florida	B-LOC
so	O
far	O
:)	O
Also	O
check	O
out	O
these	O
great	O
...	O
http://fb.me/Nfd8BeUH	O

Livestock	O
Futures	O
Commentary	O
:	O
June	O
live	O
cattle	O
closed	O
down	O
$	O
0.67	O
at	O
$	O
108.32	O
yesterday	O
.	O
Prices	O
closed	O
near	O
...	O
http://tinyurl.com/3w4o2w5	O

So	O
excited	O
for	O
you	O
!	O
RT	O
@healthyashley	O
:	O
Follow	O
#healthywedding	O
on	O
Twitter	B-ORG
for	O
fun	O
wedding	O
updates	O
from	O
bridesmaids	O
and	O
guests	O
!	O

Lay	O
out	O
or	O
shop	O
??	O

Is	O
your	O
relationship	O
with	O
your	O
hiring	O
manager	O
creating	O
onboarding	O
delays	O
?	O
Check	O
out	O
out	O
#recruitment	O
#webinar	O
:	O
http://cb4me.com/QdAmGA	O

@ourkidsmom	O
What	O
a	O
good	O
idea	O
-	O
or	O
apple-picking	O
!	O
#RFComfortEmbrace	O

Chicago	B-LOC
's	O
Ramon	B-PER
deleon	I-PER
live	O
on	O
CNN	O
fo	O
...	O
-	O
Examiner	O
.	O
com	O
:	O
Chicago&#39	O
;	O
s	O
Ramon	O
deleon	O
live	O
on	O
CNN	O
for	O
Gravity	O
Summ	O
..	O
http://tinyurl.com/m8u5ce	O

@BowleggedTAURUS	O
lol	O
nice	O
*head	O
on	O
shoulder*	O
thanx	O

Im	O
drunk	O
already	O
lol	O

Prologue	O
::	O
07.05	O
.	O
11	O
-	O
http://eepurl.com/eA816	O

@jackmuldowney	B-PER
http://plixi.com/p/45706733	O
you're	O
in	O
East	B-LOC
Lansing	I-LOC
this	O
wknd	O
too	O
??	O

Watching	O
Let	O
Me	O
In	O
.	O

Thank	O
god	O
for	O
another	O
day	O

I	O
would	O
grow	O
a	O
ZZ	B-MISC
top	I-MISC
beard	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
#ZZTopWishes	O

@mpwdoyle	O
well	O
done	O
sir	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
don't	O
want	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O

Last	O
day	O
for	O
a	O
$32	O
Massage	O
.	O
Go	O
to	O
www.dealadayonline.com	O

Special	O
Event	O
Tuesday	O
w/LA	O
's	O
DJ	O
Steve	O
Prior(Avalon	O
)	O
at	O
Stone	B-LOC
Lotus	I-LOC
,	O
Tables	O
Text	O
773-459-8133	O
,	O
Say	O
Surreal	O
for	O
Comp	O
Before	O
12	O
,	O
Reduced	O
after	O
!	O

Special	O
report	O
on	O
social	O
networking	O
from	O
The	O
Economist	O
-	O
http://bit.ly/dASW4N	O

Event	O
#FollowFriday	O
@partybluprints	O
@camerontoth	O
@fftchicago	O
@1stFreshPhilly	O

All	O
year-round	O
on	O
Chicago	B-LOC
's	O
world	O
famous	O
Navy	O
Pier	O
Phil	O
&	O
Chris	O
are	O
roasting	O
their	O
Cinnamon	O
Sugar	O
Roasted	O
Almonds	O
,	O
http://twitpic.com/4zayem	O

@patrickreyes	B-PER
Thank	O
you	O
,	O
sir	O
!!	O
I	O
love	O
the	O
topic	O
.	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
cooool	O
!	O

Go	O
green	O
for	O
St	B-MISC
.	I-MISC
Patrick	B-MISC
's	I-MISC
Day	I-MISC
:	O
Elantra	B-MISC
only	O
non-Hybrid	O
in	O
"	O
Top	O
10	O
Most	O
Fuel-Efficient	O
Cars	O
"	O
http://fb.me/xoovODzn	O

@foxchicago	O
Chicagoland	B-LOC
Teens	O
Discover	O
their	O
Big	O
Screen	O
Talent	O
this	O
Columbus	O
Day	O
creating	O
short	O
film	O
,	O
today	O
only	O
,	O
to	O
debut	O
nationwide	O
!	O

@MsSlickCity	O
LOL	O
sounds	O
interesting	O
.	O
What	O
will	O
happen	O
after	O
you	O
have	O
kids	O
?	O

Everything	O
in	O
this	O
space	O
is	O
a	O
tactic	O
of	O
one	O
goal	O
-	O
how	O
do	O
we	O
get	O
our	O
information	O
?	O

Wanna	O
make	O
3,000	O
-	O
5,000	O
$	O
/	O
monthly	O
?	O
Then	O
check	O
this	O
out	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/gbTpUv	O

Bichon	B-MISC
Frise	I-MISC
with	O
Rosebuds	O
Wreath	O
Pandora	O
Polymer	O
by	O
nanjodogz	O
http://etsy.me/h6vqBr	O

In-depth	O
look	O
at	O
38	O
deals	O
in	O
Chicago	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
IL	I-LOC
for	O
June	O
8	O
,	O
2011	O
http://goo.gl/fb/7nIUy	O

@comcastcares	O
Not	O
a	O
happy	O
camper	O
.	O
My	O
bill	O
has	O
increased	O
$40/month	O
.	O
Online	O
rep	O
said	O
call	O
in	O
and	O
they'll	O
fix	O
it	O
.	O
Phone	O
rep	O
said	O
no	O
.	O

@OmniHotels	B-MISC
time	O
to	O
update	O
the	O
twitter	O
background	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
photo	O
.	O
welcome	O
@mcbridemikej	O

New	O
on	O
@GABblog	O
:	O
Respecting	O
LGBTQ	B-ORG
Youth	O
of	O
Color	O
:	O
Come	O
one	O
,	O
come	O
all	O
to	O
my	O
neighborhood	O
http://ow.ly/1dMCMt	O

@vinnieeffinv	O
I'll	O
throw	O
your	O
phone	O
into	O
a	O
puddle	O
if	O
you	O
don't	O
mute	O
those	O
keys	O
lol	O

@zakiyafola	O
watchu	O
on	O
miss	O
swag	O
?	O

#Chicago	B-LOC
,	O
please	O
RT	O
!	O
Join	O
us	O
for	O
a	O
DV	O
#demonstration	O
and	O
#vigil	O
in	O
memory	O
of	O
a	O
#RogersPark	B-LOC
woman	O
murdered	O
last	O
weekend	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/cKYiYc	O

Great	O
new	O
shop	O
.	O
@	O
Haymaker	O
http://instagr.am/p/FL5BW/	O

Just	O
had	O
dinner	O
...	O
@	B-MISC
Eastgate	I-MISC
Cafe	I-MISC
http://instagr.am/p/KWzV/	O

Asked	O
to	O
join	O
Literacy	O
Works	O
board	O
of	O
directors	O
.	O
Focus	O
on	O
mktg	O
,	O
digital	O
to	O
support	O
development	O
effort	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
an	O
honor	O
to	O
support	O
this	O
org	O
.	O

the	O
first	O
movie	O
for	O
this	O
year	O
's	O
movies	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
series	O
-	O
"	O
The	B-MISC
Dark	I-MISC
Knight	I-MISC
",	O
Thu	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
JAN	O
--	O
pretty	O
awesome	O
;	O
bring	O
blankets	O
and	O
snacks	O
,	O
kids	O

Thanks	O
for	O
spreading	O
the	O
word	O
@OasisDayCamp	O
!	O
It	O
's	O
much	O
appreciated	O
!	O

How	O
to	O
start	O
vermicomposting	O
http://bit.ly/dl7FLp	O

CFPB	B-ORG
Unveils	O
Simplified	O
Mortgage	O
Disclosure	O
Forms	O
http://t.co/yJUEQYy	O

Somebody	O
is	O
adjusting	O
to	O
city	O
life	O
just	O
fine	O
...	O
#doginthecity	O
http://t.co/QXHUXHq	O

Check	O
out	O
this	O
awesome	O
site	O
:	O
Interactive	O
Email	O
Signature	O
-	O
http://Sweeva.com/go/Gct	O
#Sweeva	O

23	O
&	O
40-Ton	O
Cranes	O
For	O
Sale	O
by	O
Mi-Jack	O
Select	O
Sales	O
&	O
Leasin	O
...	O
http://conta.cc/pqJQUR	O
via	O
#constantcontact	O

Our	O
good	O
friends	O
Angels	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Kings	B-ORG
Chicago	I-ORG
will	O
be	O
offering	O
anyone	O
with	O
a	O
ticket	O
stub	O
or	O
a	O
wrist	O
band	O
from	O
our	O
show	O
...	O
http://fb.me/Ejxz3TaM	O

Thanks	O
@DineInChicago	O
you	O
as	O
well	O
!	O
Have	O
a	O
great	O
weekend	O
!	O

You	O
change	O
your	O
life	O
by	O
changing	O
your	O
heart	O
~	O
Max	B-PER
Lucado	I-PER

sounds	O
delish	O
thx	O
4	O
stopping	O
by	O
!	O
RT	O
@djnathan	O
:	O
@joeschicago	O
thx	O
4	O
the	O
wonderful	O
meal	O
Got	O
crab	O
legs	O
,	O
lyonnaise	O
taters	O
&	O
bone-in	O
filet	O
so	O
good	O

@RightmerHomes	O
I	O
like	O
that	O
-	O
will	O
you	O
be	O
posting	O
updates	O
on	O
this	O
?	O

@CS999	O
@ebertchicago	O
haha	O
!	O
He	O
can	O
be	O
so	O
curmudgeon-like	O
sometimes	O
!	O

I'm	O
so	O
depressed	O
...	O
RT	O
@espn_bigten	O
:	O
Worst	O
day	O
in	O
Big	O
Ten	O
history	O
?	O
Check	O

EasyFollowers	O
.	O
com	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
website	O
out	O
to	O
gain	O
more	O
followers	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/9Wni63	O

This	O
year	O
marks	O
the	O
20th	O
anniversary	O
of	O
@lollapalooza	B-ORG
Be	O
the	O
first	O
to	O
hear	O
which	O
act	O
will	O
headline	O
GALApalooza	O
'	O
11	O
tonight	O
,	O
starting	O
@	O
6:30	O

I	O
hope	O
they	O
are	O
better	O
with	O
numbers	O
at	O
Chase	B-ORG
http://twitpic.com/26zvu9	O

@nottjmiller	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
transition	O
from	O
I	O
.	O
O	O
.	O
To	O
bigger	O
stuff	O
to	O
recommend	O
getting	O
an	O
agent	O
?	O
#jamesf	O

Wow	O
.	O
RT	O
@AP	O
:	O
BREAKING	O
:	O
Police	O
official	O
tells	O
AP	O
blast	O
is	O
more	O
Norway	B-LOC
's	O
"	O
Oklahoma	B-LOC
City	I-LOC
"	O
than	O
"	O
World	O
Trade	O
Center	O
"	O
-CJ	B-PER
#breakingnews	O

@FlirtyCupcakes	O
no	O
worries-	O
it	O
's	O
a	O
deal	O
!	O
We	O
love	O
a	O
good	O
curious	O
george	O
and	O
mcdreamy	O
around	O
here	O
:)	O

Bucket	O
list	O
:	O
sex	O
on	O
a	O
beanbag	O
.	O

The	O
Latest	O
News	O
About	O
Poker	O
From	O
Pokerwins	B-ORG
http://tinyurl.com/yh2mlrn	O

Third	O
aemmp	O
meeting	O
,	O
getting	O
things	O
done	O
!	O
How	O
is	O
everyone	O
's	O
Tuesday	O
going	O
?	O
:)	O

Their	O
egos	O
write	O
checks	O
their	O
talent	O
can't	O
cash	O
.	O
Erik	B-PER
Fulkerson	I-PER

Happy	O
Easter	O
everyone	O

CWS	O
:	O
Royals	B-ORG
win	O
in	O
11th	O
on	O
Santos	B-PER
'	O
wild	O
pitch	O
(	O
AP	O
)	O
http://bit.ly/qKBLuy	O

@RedYank_MUFC	O
I	O
feel	O
anything	O
I	O
tweet	O
may	O
be	O
used	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
OK	O
,	O
fine	O
...	O
yes	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
I	O
wouldn't	O
regret	O
it	O
.	O

Women	O
in	O
Business	O
,	O
Jobs	O
,	O
Women	O
Entrepreneurs	O
,	O
Women	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/bhrObP	O

Can	O
I	O
count	O
on	O
you	O
to	O
support	O
my	O
cause	O
?	O
See	O
more	O
,	O
at	O
http://davepardo.com	O
::	O
#chicagocubs	B-ORG
#wrigleyfield	B-LOC
#announcer	O
#davepardo	B-PER
#voice	O

Wrapping	O
up	O
our	O
trip	O
to	O
San	B-LOC
Fran	I-LOC
.	O
Good	O
to	O
see	O
so	O
many	O
brewers	O
crawling	O
over	O
this	O
town	O
.	O
Great	O
city	O
.	O

#London2012	B-LOC
travel	O
planning	O
can	O
be	O
tough	O
.	O
@Sports_Traveler	O
has	O
tips	O
for	O
first	O
time	O
fans	O
heading	O
to	O
the	O
#Olympics	B-ORG
!	O
http://ow.ly/5OQvu	O

@camogavero	B-PER
Any	O
of	O
these	O
would	O
be	O
good	O
!	O
http://t.co/YQlYhPt	O

thanks	O
for	O
the	O
support	O
&	O
well	O
wishes	O
!	O
@clarklincolnpk	O
@uppermidcoast	O
@fleetfeetchgo	O
@blfarris	O
@offshooter	O
cc	O
:	O
@crestodina	O
@barrettoms	O
^ag	O

@ethernat	O
can't	O
you	O
get	O
a	O
trial	O
version	O
of	O
MS	O
Project	O
online	O
?	O

1st	O
Inning	O
,	O
Fla	O
0	O
,	O
ChC	O
0	O

#Entrepreneur	B-ORG
Daily	I-ORG
is	O
out	O
!	O
http://bit.ly/jlQRb9	O
?	O
Top	O
stories	O
today	O
via	O
@andreapjensen	B-PER

@OBEYMEDIA	O
Thank	O
you	O
!	O
I	O
do	O
too	O
:)	O
.	O

@ArseChicago	O
Oh	O
that	O
's	O
a	O
great	O
idea	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
in	O
boats	O
but	O
slices	O
would	O
work	O
too	O
.	O
Lemme	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
like	O
it	O
!	O

Swimming	O
in	O
the	O
sky	O
.	O
Circa	O
2009	O
http://instagr.am/p/HD50I/	O

@tildarling	B-PER
Yay	O
,	O
check	O
it	O
out	O
now	O
!	O

@MoreYoutubeView	O
thanks	O
for	O
following	O
me	O
!	O

#FF	O
HOT	O
!!	O
@Erionna	B-PER
@TREASURE95	O
@xXRmaniXx	B-PER
@fuck_my_pussiee	O
@LALEEZY01	O
@Sexxy_Rican	B-PER
@sugaware	O

@ServinAiRbody	O
haha	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
dope	O
song	O

Just	O
got	O
carded	O
buying	O
NyQuil	B-MISC
and	O
my	O
ID	O
was	O
studied	O
pretty	O
damn	O
closely	O
.	O
Do	O
I	O
really	O
not	O
even	O
pass	O
for	O
18	O
?	O
#fb	O

Get	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
gloomy	O
weather	O
and	O
warm	O
up	O
with	O
our	O
delicious	O
hot	O
reuben	O
sandwich	O
,	O
served	O
with	O
homemade	O
potato	O
chips	O

Check	O
out	O
our	O
homie	O
@christophe312	B-PER
in	O
HI	O
FRUCTOSE	O
mag	O
!	O
Congrats	O
fam	O
!	O
http://plixi.com/p/90657948	O

Baseball	O
Apps	O
For	O
Mobile	O
:	O
EvriThing	O
Baseball	O
http://goo.gl/fb/qAHf7	O

Please	O
ReTweet	O
(	O
http://caltweet.com/o77	O
)	O
-	O
Neo-Soul	B-MISC
Cruise	I-MISC
feat	O
.	O
Kindred	B-MISC
Family	I-MISC
Soul	I-MISC
<	O
--	O
RSVP	O
HERE	O

SSC	O
Favorites	O
of	O
2010	O
:	O
The	B-MISC
Molly	I-MISC
Edition	I-MISC
http://bit.ly/gWxR8z	O

Post	O
Edited	O
:	O
Law	O
of	O
The	O
Garbage	O
Truck	O
http://cli.gs/qPJ1N	O

Keiichi	B-PER
Matsuda	I-PER
's	O
Augmented	O
(	O
hyper)Reality	O
:	O
Domestic	O
Robocop	O
http://j.mp/f4338t	O
via	O
@AddToAny	O

This	O
is	O
truly	O
good	O
news	O
:	O
God	B-MISC
's	O
holiness	O
demands	O
that	O
sin	O
be	O
punished	O
.	O
God	O
's	O
grace	O
provides	O
the	O
sacrifice	O
.	O
What	O
God	O
demands	O
,	O
He	O
supplies	O
.	O

@nns15	O
how'd	O
you	O
do	O
that	O
!?	O

Promising	O
#fashionista	O
ambassador	O
program	O
-	O
@CondeNast	O
Taps	O
Word-Of-Mouth	O
,	O
Social	O
Stars	O
for	O
Advertisers	O
'	O
Sake	O
|	O
Adweek	O
http://ow.ly/5EAJf	O

#TwitNewsNow	O
PBT	O
:	O
Derrick	B-PER
Rose	I-PER
admits	O
he	O
wore	O
down	O
in	O
playoffs	O
http://dlvr.it/ZwmZD	O
#NBA	O

Chicago	O
Deck	O
Builders	O
-	O
http://t.co/p0O6n9R	O
#chicago	O
#decks	O

Please	O
don't	O
eat	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
.	O
http://instagr.am/p/E6RNM/	O

Just	O
saw	O
#somethingborrowed	O
!	O
Not	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
but	O
still	O
good	O
.	O
Now	O
getting	O
ready	O
for	O
dinner	O
at	O
#luxbar	O
.	O

Getting	O
ready	O
to	O
open	O
Maroon	B-MISC
5	I-MISC
show	O
again	O
at	O
Ravinia	B-LOC
w	O
@1019MIXChicago	B-ORG
...	O
HOT	O
!	O
((	O
weather	O
and	O
Adam	O
Levine	O
))	O

@monicaobrien	B-PER
Still	O
on	O
for	O
dinner	O
tonight	O
at	O
6:00	O
?	O

Don't	O
just	O
live	O
...	O
live	O
with	O
passion	O
,	O
excitement	O
&	O
enthusiasm	O
in	O
everything	O
you	O
do	O
!	O
:)	O

Just	O
wondering	O
...	O
Who	O
invented	O
the	O
kiss	O
cam	O
!?!	O
It	O
is	O
brilliant	O
.	O

Feeling	O
very	O
blessed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
wonderful	O
family	O
.	O
My	O
bread	O
,	O
wine	O
,	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
whiskey	O
family	O
.	O

Come	O
one	O
,	O
come	O
all	O
!	O
RT	O
@RIAeats_Chi	O
:	O
@janetisabelli	B-PER
Next	O
time	O
!	O
And	O
I	O
may	O
just	O
crash	O
that	O
little	O
macaron	O
extravaganza	O
.	O

Boom	O
Times	O
http://dlvr.it/QW3lc	O

How	O
does	O
my	O
dad	O
still	O
manage	O
to	O
pocket	O
dial	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
smart	O
phone	O
?	O

180	O
W	O
.	O
Washington	O
&	O
131	O
S	O
.	O
Dearborn	O
open	O
Sat	O
10a-3p	O
.	O
All	O
stores	O
closed	O
Sun	O
&	O
Mon	O
.	O
Back	O
to	O
the	O
bretzel	O
on	O
Tues	O
.	O
Happy	O
holiday	O
wknd	O
all	O
!	O

Ever	O
since	O
the	O
1985	O
Sidd	B-PER
Finch	I-PER
Sports	B-ORG
Illustrated	I-ORG
article	O
I	O
am	O
skeptical	O
about	O
everything	O
I	O
read	O
on	O
April	O
1	O
#FanAuction	O
http://ht.ly/4rmOY	O

Presto	B-ORG
Caf	I-ORG
&	B-ORG
Grill	I-ORG
@ChiFrenchMarket	O
offers	O
delicious	O
Mediterranean	O
cuisine	O
from	O
Hummus	O
to	O
Chicken	O
Shawarma	O
to	O
Falafel	O
!	O
Stop	O
by	O
today	O
!	O

We're	O
not	O
ignoring	O
you	O
,	O
our	O
email	O
is	O
down	O
!	O
#lunchbreak	O

This	O
is	O
not	O
about	O
the	O
case	O
that	O
everyone	O
is	O
talking	O
about	O
this	O
week	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
different	O
case	O
with	O
a	O
binational	O
...	O
http://fb.me/AEdovJy0	O

Dreading	O
working	O
overnight	O
tonight	O
and	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
gughhhhh	O

$39	O
for	O
$100	O
Toward	O
Clothing	O
&	O
Jewelry	O
at	O
Teranz	O
Boutique	O
http://j.mp/qqo2Du	O
#chicago	B-LOC
#deals	O

First	O
West	O
Coast	O
Printer	O
Certified	O
by	O
SGP	O
http://bit.ly/9podnO	O
Printing	O
Impressions	O

Hey	O
New	B-LOC
York	I-LOC
moms	O
and	O
moms-to-be	O
!	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
Big	O
...	O
http://www.facebook.com/permalink.php?story_fbid=111118705574259&id=148970333358	O

@ScottfMurphy	B-PER
Here	O
's	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
mind	O
tonight	O
:	O
http://me.lt/3X0Hl	O
#myT	O
#goflyCAP	O
#CAP312	O

@Cnet	O
reviews	O
the	O
new	O
and	O
highly	O
anticipated	O
T-Mobile	B-ORG
G2x	O
Android	O
Phone	O
@cnet	O
http://bit.ly/fXmDUr	O

Are	O
plastic	O
Adirondack	O
chairs	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
the	O
real	O
thing	O
?	O
http://t.co/MASaVZh	O

does	O
anyone	O
else	O
have	O
trouble	O
saying	O
"	O
no	O
"	O
to	O
someone	O
if	O
they	O
need	O
help/a	O
favor	O
?	O

Heading	O
to	O
@TribChicagoLive	O
-	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
there	O

Breaking	O
:	O
St	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
Boniface	I-LOC
Developer	O
Changes	O
Plan	O
,	O
Opts	O
to	O
Keep	O
Church	O
Intact	O
http://t.co/bjaQKHP	O

Elizabeth	B-PER
Marxs	I-PER
Playboy	O
Cybergirl	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
May	O
30	O
2011	O
http://bit.ly/k28wmw	O

@WickerParkBuck	O
yep	O

@tyre504	B-PER
according	O
to	O
you	O
ima	O
FREAK	O
and	O
an	O
ALCOHOLIC	O
...	O
whats	O
next	O
?!?	O

Good	O
seats	O
still	O
available	O
for	O
all	O
Cubs	B-ORG
games	O
http://t.co/wF491nZ	O
#cubs	O

Debt	O
Ceiling	O
Talks	O
:	O
Democrats	B-ORG
,	O
Republicans	B-ORG
Face	O
Make-Or-Break	O
Week	O
http://bit.ly/mroaJ9	O

Looking	O
for	O
Home	O
Remodeling	O
In	O
Mount	B-LOC
Prospect	I-LOC
,	B-LOC
IL	I-LOC
?	O
Check	O
this	O
out	O
-	O
http://t.co/i6XP2hy	O
#home	O
#remodeling	O
#mount	O
#prospect	O

Makes	O
sense	O
actually	O
...	O
RT	O
@sgbz	O
:	O
A	O
Republican	O
loves	O
America	B-LOC
in	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
a	O
wife-beater	O
loves	O
his	O
wife	O
#p2	O
#tcot	O
#pX	O
#christian	O

@PhilJacquesNY	O
http://followe.rs/4rW	O
recommended	O
2	O
me	O
to	O
follow	O
U	O
.	O
Would	O
love	O
to	O
hookup	O
!	O

Austan	B-PER
Goolsbee	I-PER
-	O
Credit	O
Card	O
Bill	O
Kicks	O
in	O
Today	O
:	O
http://digg.com/d311Q7g?t	O

Eighty	O

Looking	O
for	O
a	O
manufacturer	O
of	O
Deep	O
Drawn	O
Parts	O
?	O
See	O
http://www.HubManufacturing.us	O
for	O
a	O
free	O
quote	O

Thanks	O
to	O
NBC	O
Chicago	B-LOC
for	O
mentioning	O
our	O
Anniversary	O
Party	O
tonight	O
!	O
Come	O
out	O
and	O
celebrate	O
with	O
us	O
!...	O
http://fb.me/uqS4jYhP	O

I	O
should	O
def	O
get	O
up	O
&&	O
gym	O
it	O
but	O
i	O
need	O
a	O
few	O
more	O
hours	O
of	O
sleep	O
lol	O

RSVP	O
on	O
Facebook	O
to	O
our	O
Dec	O
.	O
9	O
event	O
with	O
Al	B-PER
Gini	I-PER
!	O
What	O
's	O
Sing	O
Got	O
to	O
Do	O
with	O
It	O
?	O
An	O
Even	O
Deadlier	O
Book	O
Launch	O
http://bit.ly/6ck3fQ	O

#ihatewhenpeople	O
push	O
the	O
elevator	O
button	O
when	O
it	O
's	O
already	O
been	O
pushed	O
.	O

Rickard	B-PER
Bindery	I-PER
has	O
80	O
folders	O
that	O
help	O
us	O
fold	O
almost	O
any	O
printed	O
product	O
you	O
can	O
name	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/dZ5SVP	O

@John_Redfern	O
thanks	O
John	B-PER
I	O
appreciate	O
it	O
!	O

I	O
don't	O
get	O
how	O
mfs	O
,	O
have	O
a	O
job	O
.	O
But	O
nothing	O
to	O
show	O
for	O
it	O
.	O

Love	O
Debonair	B-MISC
so	O
happy	O
,	O
REHAB	O
(	O
Monday	O
's	O
@	O
Debonair	O
)	O
is	O
nominated	O
for	O
America	O
's	O
Best	O
Party	O
!	O
vote@	O
http://peoples-choice-awards09.papermag.com	O

@jeffmello	O
LOL	O
!	O
Yes	O
,	O
i	O
have	O
definitely	O
tried	O
sweetbread	O
in	O
Brazil	B-LOC
(	O
we	O
have	O
to	O
thank	O
Portugal	B-LOC
for	O
that	O
!	O
)	O
...	O
They	O
are	O
awesome	O
!!	O
;)	O

NO	O
WIZ	O
,	O
NO	O
WINS	O
.	O
RT	O
@CraigCustance	B-PER
No	O
deal	O
on	O
the	O
horizon	O
between	O
Wisniewski	B-ORG
and	O
Canadiens	B-ORG
.	O
Could	O
be	O
the	O
best	O
d-man	O
option	O
on	O
July	O
1	O
.	O

@toastcowboy	B-PER
Go	O
Bucs	O
!	O

Good	O
for	O
the	O
Kids	O
|	O
ParentSphere	O
New	O
post	O
on	O
my	O
ParentSphere	B-ORG
blog	O
http://bit.ly/mdNxiZ	O
via	O
@BlogGlue	O

China	B-LOC
,	O
U.S.	B-LOC
play	O
down	O
tensions	O
at	O
Asian	O
security	O
summit	O
-	O
The	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
and	O
China	B-LOC
moved	O
to	O
repair	O
strained	O
ties	O
...	O
http://ow.ly/1dV20z	O

thx	O
for	O
the	O
follow	O
@goodchildhomes	O
and	O
@aggieraup	O
Looking	O
fwd	O
to	O
your	O
tweets	O
!	O

Topshop	O
is	O
moving	O
to	O
Chicago	B-LOC
!	O
Are	O
you	O
as	O
thrilled	O
as	O
we	O
are	O
?!	O
http://ht.ly/2KYHR	O

The	B-MISC
History	I-MISC
of	B-MISC
Social	I-MISC
Media	I-MISC
[	O
INFOGRAPHIC	O
]	O
http://on.mash.to/gggnSN	O
#SocialMedia	O

@KenniceH	B-PER
omg	O
hahaha	O
..	O
father	O
and	O
son	O
?!?	O

#jazzfest	O
Weather	O
radar	O
looks	O
promising	O
(	O
via	O
@wwoz_neworleans	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
music	O
is	O
delivering	O
!!	O

I	O
see	O
drunk	O
people	O
...	O

Lord	O
...	O
RT	O
@steenfox	O
:	O
http://twitpic.com/5rvckc	O

The	B-MISC
Beast	I-MISC
of	B-MISC
Bodmin	I-MISC
Moor	I-MISC
:	O
Panther-like	O
sightings	O
,	O
reports	O
of	O
multi-slain	O
cattle	O
;	O
could	O
it	O
be	O
The	O
Beast	O
of	O
Bodmi	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/eoxFxU	O

Chocolate	O
and	O
fruit	O
never	O
paired	O
so	O
well	O
together	O
--	O
Our	O
Chocolate	O
Covered	O
Cherries	O
are	O
a	O
hit	O
of	O
the	O
season	O
!	O
http://ow.ly/5CAKn	O

Note	O
to	O
drunk	O
dudes	O
of	O
America	B-LOC
:	O
Don't	O
ask	O
the	O
DJ	O
where	O
the	O
bathroom	O
is	O
.	O
You're	O
a	O
big	O
boy	O
and	O
can	O
stumble	O
there	O
yourself	O
.	O

American	O
Journalism	O
-	O
Another	O
Case	O
of	O
CNN	B-ORG
Crap	O
http://wp.me/p6oaj-lG	O

Second	O
incredibly	O
embarrassing	O
blown	O
save	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
worst	O
teams	O
in	O
baseball	O
AT	O
HOME	O
this	O
season	O
.	O
God	O
dammit	O
.	O

Happy	O
#90210	O
day	O
!	O
Enjoy	O
this	O
'	O
lil	O
gem	O
:	O
http://ow.ly/2yvAB	O

@luzziuz	B-PER
glad	O
you	O
like	O
it	O
!	O
Wow	O
thats	O
so	O
awesome	O
@jadycaffaro	B-PER
your	O
from	O
Brazil	B-LOC
,	O
cheers	O
!	O

WE	O
HAVE	O
REACHED	O
3000+	O
RSVPS	O
!!	O
WE	O
HAVE	O
1500+	O
MABES	O
!!	O
WE	O
ARE	O
ONLY	O
LETTING	O
IN	O
4500+	O
FREAKZ	O
THE	O
REST	O
MIGHT	O
HAVE	O
TO	O
...	O
http://fb.me/yFvS0Zn5	O

#FF	O
@joeldavidbarnes	O
@kt_go	O
@chiboys	O
@stealx	O
@evolyte	O
@jeffreyryanwho	O
@seanmeverett	O
@kt1grand	O
@jaredkain	O
@arbiu	O
@drewdoleski	O
@BSLCTVE	O

Moms	O
in	O
Business	O
Unite	O
Conference	O
announces	O
award	O
finalists	O
-	O
San	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/cdYiW5	O

Let	O
me	O
create	O
a	O
snapshot	O
of	O
something	O
that	O
happened	O
to	O
your	O
ancestor	O
decades	O
ago	O
.	O
Contact	O
me	O
:	O
Nancy@	B-PER
artforyoursake.com	O
or	O
773-255-4677	O
.	O

Slogging	O
through	O
this	O
Friday	O
.	O
Mentally	O
gone	O
.	O
This	O
quote	O
about	O
sums	O
up	O
my	O
day	O
.	O
"	O
We	O
all	O
carry	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
our	O
weary	O
world	O
around	O
with	O
us	O
."	O

It	O
's	O
been	O
a	O
long	O
day	O
,	O
lost	O
for	O
a	O
couple	O
hrs	O
,	O
dark	O
winding	O
road	O
=	O
no	O
fun	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
have	O
now	O
arrived	O
at	O
the	O
hotel	O
Santa	B-LOC
Fe	I-LOC
safely	O
.	O

.	O
@hythrain	O
Though	O
Unleashed	O
has	O
the	O
best	O
3D	O
Sonic	O
engine	O
to	O
this	O
day	O
,	O
so	O
I'm	O
glad	O
that	O
they	O
implemented	O
that	O
into	O
Generations	O
.	O

Need	O
to	O
hustle	O
from	O
T3	O
to	O
T5	O
.	O
(@	B-LOC
London	I-LOC
Heathrow	B-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
(	O
LHR	O
)	O
w/	O
8	O
others	O
)	O
http://4sq.com/kuDC1g	O

Vote	O
on	O
massive	O
O'Hare	B-LOC
lease	O
postponed	O
again	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/fSrc5C	O

tomorrow	O
i	O
should	O
really	O
find	O
an	O
atm	O
and	O
a	O
payphone	O
.	O

"	O
Politically	O
active	O
stoners	O
are	O
the	O
worst	O
"	O
#LOL	O
Lounge	O
#jflchicago	B-LOC

http://vintageheavenchicago.blogspot.com/	O

these	O
money	O
back	O
girls	O
are	O
fine	O

It	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
as	O
well	O
,	O
Ali	B-PER
!	O
I'm	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
things	O
are	O
going	O
so	O
well	O
.	O
RT	O
@amontag	B-PER
Great	O
seeing	O
the	O
#WSCHI	O
crew	O
last	O
night	O
!	O

#Coachella	B-ORG
2011	I-ORG
:	O
The	O
Festival	O
Kicks	O
Off	O
,	O
Cee	B-PER
Lo	I-PER
Mouths	O
Off	O
,	O
Dance	O
Music	O
Blasts	O
Off	O
http://yhoo.it/f5yaxM	O

The	O
history	O
of	O
children	O
's	O
literature	O
http://bit.ly/ofHqZN	O
via	O
@bookforum	O

@sproutfarmindy	O
Sneak	O
out	O
between	O
the	O
rain	O
storms	O
this	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Our	O
market	O
stand	O
is	O
open	O
til	O
2	O
pm	O
today	O
!	O
http://ow.ly/5LEIb	O

Nifty	O
planet	O
and	O
moon	O
tracker	O
on	O
the	O
cute	O
(	O
if	O
snooty	O
)	O
Bristol	O
harborside	O
development	O
http://t.co/TDldYSo	O

@keithlaw	B-PER
better	O
question	O
:	O
WILL	O
Thomas	B-PER
go	O
in	O
on	O
first	O
ballot	O
.	O
Could	O
be	O
a	O
huge	O
backlog	O
,	O
plus	O
the	O
DH	O
thing	O
.	O

Great	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
with	O
@chaas	B-PER
and	O
#skype	B-ORG
at	O
#enterprisecon	B-MISC
(@	B-LOC
Old	I-LOC
Hickory	B-LOC
Steakhouse	I-LOC
w/	O
2	O
others	O
)	O
http://4sq.com/fWimgl	O

My	O
head	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
wrong	O
place	O
today	O
....	O

Happy	O
Fathers	B-MISC
Day	I-MISC
to	O
the	O
dads	O
who	O
raise	O
their	O
kids	O
with	O
morals	O
and	O
ethics	O
.	O
Enjoy	O
your	O
kids	O
today	O
.	O

For	O
the	O
most	O
potent	O
herbal	O
incense	O
and	O
hebal	O
potpourri	O
go	O
to	O
http://t.co/Bkpx8xh	O

South	O
Loop	O
Connection	O
:	O
Clean	O
,	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
Friendly	O
Too	O
:	O
Nassau	B-LOC
Concierge	O
a	O
New	O
Kind	O
of	O
Cleaning	O
Service	O
http://ht.ly/5JzCW	O

Sales	O
&	O
Marketing	O
Manager	O
(	O
Reno	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
NV	I-LOC
)	O
http://bit.ly/bYXVK4	O
#jobs	O
#in	O

"	O
SAS	O
has	O
about	O
600	O
internal	O
bloggers	O
and	O
more	O
than	O
40	O
external	O
bloggers	O
"	O
http://j.mp/dVvKNr	O
#brandbehavior	O
#culture	O
#leadership	O

The	O
latest	O
on	O
the	O
Flaming	B-ORG
Lips	I-ORG
:	O
http://tinyurl.com/cruatv	O

@TheCoOp420	O
ayo	O
fam	O
...	O
not	O
one	O
nigga	O
smiled	O
in	O
that	O
video	O
.	O
nann	O
.	O
nigga	O
.	O
we	O
gotta	O
bring	O
the	O
happy	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
game	O
fam	O
.	O

@indierocker7	B-PER
You	O
have	O
no	O
idea	O
how	O
jealous	O
I	O
am	O
!	O

Do	O
not	O
stand	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
of	O
danger	O
trusting	O
in	O
miracles	O
.	O
-Arab	O
Proverb	O

http://fb.me/NrNTIJnt	O

Samsung	B-ORG
Rolls	O
Out	O
22	O
Inch	O
Transparent	O
LCD	O
http://bit.ly/h2dKUF	O

316/365	O
:	O
iToEyes	O
posted	O
a	O
photo	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/42fuCL	O

my	O
time	O
line	O
has	O
stopped	O
WTF	O
thats	O
not	O
normal	O

@ccguinto	B-PER
WElcome	O
-	O
hope	O
it	O
went	O
well	O
!	O

Marty	B-PER
Sammon	I-PER
has	O
a	O
show	O
coming	O
up	O
on	O
05/20/2010	O
at	O
08:00	O
PM	O
@	B-LOC
Wellmont	I-LOC
Theatre	I-LOC
in	O
Montclair	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
NJ	I-LOC
http://soc.li/mlVAyJV	O

@FlyyingDutchman	B-PER
just	O
text	O
you	O

@carterbays	O
I	O
could	O
live	O
with	O
that	O
.	O
Would	O
prevent	O
#HIMYM	O
from	O
dragging	O
out	O
a	O
story	O
longer	O
than	O
24	O
...	O
(	O
don't	O
worry	O
,	O
I'm	O
still	O
watching	O
)	O

Watching	O
The	O
Craft	O
.	O
#imreallyawitch	O

Look	O
what	O
's	O
new	O
Sale	O
Serenity	O
Bay	O
-	O
artisan	O
lampwork	O
beads	O
,	O
Swarovski	O
crystals	O
,	O
sterling	O
silver	O
bracelet	O
and	O
ear	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/bZVaId	O

@davidtlewis	B-PER
we	O
didn't	O
know	O
but	O
i	O
think	O
Zarick	B-PER
has	O
a	O
handle	O
on	O
it	O
now	O

MT	O
@richcherry	B-PER
Apple	B-ORG
files	O
patent	O
with	O
potential	O
for	O
museum	O
beaming	O
info	O
like	O
an	O
audio	O
tour	O
to	O
iPhone	O
http://bp0.co/kGRHsl	O
#mtogo	O

@ssanquist	O
I	O
know	O
!	O
How	O
are	O
you	O
SS	O
?	O

Anyone	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
swimming	O
on	O
the	O
blue	O
line	O
?	O
http://yfrog.com/jyjuej	O

Farewell	O
,	O
Fargo	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
thank	O
you	O
.	O

The	O
Dark	O
Side	O
of	O
Oxycontin	B-MISC
|	O
Chicago	B-LOC
Personal	O
Injury	O
Law	O
Blog	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/iMHAQs	O

@StarCAM_com	O
Trailer	O
Mashup	O
Shows	O
'	O
Contagion	O
'	O
Looks	O
A	O
Lot	O
Like	O
'	O
Outbreak	O
'	O
http://t.co/XA3NpFz	O

@BrandSmart2011	O
CMO	O
branding	O
conference	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
Chicago	B-LOC
Wed	O
6/22	O
.	O
Use	O
discount	O
code	O
CRANKITUP	O
to	O
$ave	O
http://ow.ly/5lOo0	O

#GreatLakes	B-LOC
reporting	O
by	O
@WBEZ	O
's	O
new	O
project	O
:	O
Front	O
&	O
Center	O
.	O
Learn	O
about	O
the	O
emerging	O
"	O
freshwater	O
economy	O
"	O
|	O
http://t.co/w3pLY4x	O

Do	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
travel	O
tip	O
to	O
share	O
?	O
Tweet	O
us	O
!	O
And	O
check	O
out	O
our	O
must-have	O
product	O
to	O
throw	O
in	O
your	O
suitcase	O
http://ow.ly/5kysj	O

Visit	O
the	O
WEDGITS	B-ORG
Facebook	B-ORG
page	O
for	O
more	O
info	O
on	O
this	O
ASTRA	B-ORG
Award-Winning	O
toy	O
!	O
http://bit.ly/4lgXq9	O

@8C	O
@ToastCrust	O
HD	O
2D	O
porn	O
.	O

Colorado	B-LOC
company	O
produces	O
#MarijuanaSoda	O
.	O
http://tinyurl.com/37e2tao	O

@JadedTLC	O
Thank	O
YOU	O
!	O
It	O
's	O
really	O
great	O
to	O
see	O
SEO	O
folks	O
that	O
are	O
fighting	O
the	O
good	O
fight	O
.	O
Please	O
stay	O
in	O
touch	O
.	O
#SEOChat	O

@raniacombs	B-PER
we're	O
thrilled	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
succeed	O
!	O
http://bit.ly/mQVV63	O

@sgeiger27	B-PER
woooot	O
wooot	O
!!	O
Mimosas	O
,	O
shopping	O
carts	O
and	O
kanye	B-PER
OH	O
MY	O
!	O

Good	O
morning	O
friends	O
:)	O

@sdasgupt	B-PER
-	O
Thanks	O
for	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
MoMo	O
Chicago	B-LOC
meeting	O
last	O
week	O
!	O
But	O
who	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Your	O
Twitter	B-ORG
profile	O
is	O
blank	O
...	O
:-)	O

Fabulous	O
news	O
-	O
MCA	B-ORG
has	O
won	O
Best	O
Sales	O
Office	O
for	O
an	O
Adult	O
Community	O
at	O
Toll	B-ORG
Brothers	I-ORG
'	B-ORG
Regency	I-ORG
at	O
Monroe	B-LOC
community	O
!	O
http://fb.me/WTkrXCPJ	O

Sold	O
Stuff	O
:	O
5,000	O
-Square-Foot	O
Humboldt	B-LOC
Park	I-LOC
Church	O
Sells	O
for	O
$410K	O
http://ow.ly/1e08nN	O

@stanimal312	B-PER
Oh-	O
look	O
at	O
you	O
!	O
Tweeting	O
ALL	O
by	O
yourself	O
!	O
:)	O
Guess	O
you	O
learned	O
a	O
little	O
something	O
at	O
last	O
night	O
's	O
party	O
@TheJoyntChicago	B-PER

It	O
's	O
@SteppenwolfAux	O
Council	O
subscription	O
night	O
@steppenwolfThtr	O
,	O
Middletown	B-LOC
!	O
http://ow.ly/5tssP	O

Crain&apos	O
;	O
s	O
Daily	B-ORG
:	O
CNA	O
wraps	O
up	O
purchase	O
of	O
CNA	O
Surety	O
http://bit.ly/k2FcAI	O

Adult	O
obesity	O
is	O
stable	O
,	O
but	O
our	O
poor	O
kids	O
...!	O
http://ow.ly/1GPst	O

If	O
I	O
could	O
only	O
follow	O
one	O
person	O
it'd	O
be	O
@PaulyPeligroso	B-PER
@RonnieWK	B-PER
@ruthakers	B-PER
@JennyJohnsonHi5	B-PER
(	O
I	O
can't	O
count	O
but	O
,	O
still	O
,	O
follow	O
them	O
)	O
#FF	O

@holidayhaven	O
THANKYOU	O
!	O
Love	O
the	O
coverage	O
!	O

Google	B-ORG
Doodle	O
Honors	O
Mobile	O
Artist	O
Alexander	O
Calder	O
http://t.co/hUDIkw4	O
via	O
@mashable	O

Well	O
said	O
!	O
RT	O
@PRSportsGirl	B-PER
:	O
Thanks	O
so	O
much	O
for	O
the	O
#FF	O
and	O
new	O
followers	O
.	O
Big	O
wave	O
*runs	O
down	O
timeline	O
giving	O
(	O
cont	O
)	O
http://tl.gd/bokt8q	O

@BaoMouth	O
@Ramon_DeLeon	O
You	O
guys	O
interested	O
in	O
making	O
~30	O
entrepreneurs/techies	O
happy	O
on	O
6/8	O
?	O
:)	O
http://bit.ly/9QFdZr	O

Angels	O
and	O
Kings	O
tonight	O
for	O
the	O
Janus	B-PER
show	O
....	O
who	O
wants	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
?!?!?	O

@oneofak1nd_	O
That	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
line	O
(	O
smile)	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
means	O
so	O
I'm	O
completely	O
on	O
board	O
.	O

latest	O
warning	O
says	O
destructive	O
winds	O
in	O
excess	O
of	O
80mph	O
with	O
storm	O
heading	O
into	O
#chicago	B-LOC
.	O
Will	O
keep	O
stream	O
running	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O

Gregg	B-PER
Slapak	I-PER
,	O
The	B-ORG
Gregg	I-ORG
Slapak	B-ORG
Team	I-ORG
-	O
WheatonRealEstateGuy	O
.	O
com	O
http://fb.me/LGKhGZm9	O

At	O
punky's!!!!	O
<	O
3	O
u	O
Ana	B-PER
hahaha	O

@alexHGL	B-PER
thanks	O
!	O
:)	O

Come	O
to	O
"	O
5	B-ORG
Magazine	I-ORG
's	O
4/20	O
Party	O
feat	O
.	O
REES	O
URBAN	O
*	O
CZBOOGIE	O
*	O
5	O
MAG	O
STAFF	O
WRITERS	O
"	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
April	O
20	O
from	O
...	O
http://fb.me/10icE18sm	O

Does	O
anyone	O
know	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
gallery	O
space	O
to	O
book	O
an	O
event	O
in	O
Chicago	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
West	B-LOC
Loop	I-LOC
??	O
Preferably	O
,	O
a	O
gallery	O
owner	O
in	O
the	O
West	B-LOC
Loop	I-LOC
?	O

#SarahPalinUSA	B-PER
says	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
and	O
Dr	B-PER
.	I-PER
Laura	I-PER
have	O
been	O
'	O
shackled	O
.'	O
That	O
's	O
right	O
,	O
she	O
just	O
played	O
the	O
Kunta	O
Kinte	O
card	O
.	O
#Maverick	O
#BS	O

@CashDeVereaux	B-PER
nice	O
backshot	O

@shellscape	B-PER
what	O
?	O
Didn't	O
you	O
see	O
my	O
tweet	O
about	O
ninjas	O
?	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
good	O
!	O
Promise	O
to	O
do	O
better	O
tomorrow	O
my	O
friend	O
!	O

@kerryannsugrue	B-PER
@ChicagoISC	B-ORG
I'll	O
be	O
there	O
.	O

Sports	O
do	O
not	O
build	O
character	O
.	O
They	O
reveal	O
it	O
.	O

The	O
Legacy	O
Marketing	O
Partners	O
Daily	O
is	O
out	O
!	O
http://bit.ly/gvWoWA	O
?	O
Top	O
stories	O
today	O
via	O
@scanexplorer	O
@rachel__nichols	O
@matthewjones23	O

Photo	O
:	O
nice	O
body	O
painting	O
http://tumblr.com/xhz3lxtds2	O

The	O
only	O
thing	O
that	O
costs	O
more	O
than	O
your	O
dream	O
is	O
the	O
cost	O
of	O
not	O
having	O
one	O
.	O
Randy	B-PER
Gage	I-PER

$25	O
for	O
a	O
No-Chip	O
Manicure	O
from	O
Village	B-ORG
Cutting	I-ORG
Room	I-ORG
:	O
The	O
Price	O
is	O
25.00	O
http://bit.ly/mHqY4Q	O

@crocktees	B-PER
thank	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
!	O
We	O
are	O
super	O
pumped	O
at	O
this	O
opportunity	O
!!	O

Happy	O
Monday	O
#UsGuys	O
,	O
how	O
was	O
everyone	O
's	O
weekend	O
?!	O

Adams	B-PER
birthday	O
dinner	O
.	O
(@	B-LOC
David	I-LOC
Burke	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
Primehouse	I-LOC
)	O
http://4sq.com/nyev2e	O

@antlindsey	B-PER
got	O
a	O
super	O
sharp	O
jacket	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
loved	O
how	O
it	O
looked	O
on	O
him	O
def	O
dapper	O
;o	O
)	O

I'm	O
at	O
Flat	B-ORG
Top	I-ORG
Grill	I-ORG
w/	O
@mattpauli	B-PER
http://4sq.com/kbS7ur	O

@DelwynRockOn	B-PER
No	O
worries	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Christopher	B-PER
,	O
and	O
he	O
's	O
wonderful	O
.	O
We're	O
not	O
married	O
yet	O
,	O
but	O
already	O
have	O
plans	O
for	O
a	O
Jameson	O
fountain	O

Working	O
out	O
some	O
frustration	O
(@	B-ORG
XSport	I-ORG
Fitness	I-ORG
)	O
http://4sq.com/rf2IYt	O

http://m.cio.com/article/686302/10_Technologies_That_Will_Change_the_World_in_the_Next_10_Years?page=5&taxonomyId=3045	O
http://dlvr.it/bySRT	O

All-Star	O
Jose	B-PER
Bautista	I-PER
leaves	O
with	O
twisted	O
right	O
ankle	O
as	O
Blue	B-ORG
Jays	I-ORG
pound	O
...:	O
Bautista	B-PER
was	O
getting	O
treatment	O
af	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/p3sUDI	O

Alex	B-PER
Steinweiss	I-PER
,	O
Originator	O
of	O
Artistic	B-ORG
Album	I-ORG
Covers	I-ORG
,	O
Dies	O
at	O
94	O
http://nyti.ms/qAkyCO	O

Cooked	O
@mickklugfarms	O
rhubarb	O
&	O
pureed	O
it	O
to	O
make	O
our	O
Rhubarb	O
Red	O
Saison	O
for	O
the	O
#FarmersMarketSeries	B-MISC
this	O
wk	O
...	O
Premieres	O
at	O
12pm	O
tomorrow	O
!	O

@ErnestWilkins	B-PER
oh	O
the	O
phone	O
lines	O
will	O
be	O
jammed	O
by	O
then	O
.	O

Super	O
cute	O
printables	O
!	O
RT	O
@Ruffled_Blog	O
Printable	O
candy	O
buffet	O
signs	O
+	O
place	O
cards	O
courtesy	O
of	O
@twobrunettes	B-PER
http://su.pr/2DxWfj	O

@onfaith	O
@HuffPostRelig	B-ORG
Check	O
it	O
!	O
The	O
Calling	O
,	O
film	O
about	O
seminary	O
students	O
,	O
is	O
up	O
for	O
Independent	O
Lens	O
Audience	O
Award	O
:	O
http://t.co/NFkE5O1	O

Happy	O
Valentines	O
Day	O
from	O
CHPR	B-ORG
<	O
3	O
<	O
3	O

Sighs	O
of	O
relief	O
plump	O
#euro	O
-	O
#Forex	O
-	O
http://t.co/A2VYuex	O

Anxiety	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
policy	O
.	O
-Head	O
of	O
Israeli	B-ORG
Opposition	I-ORG
,	O
and	O
general	O
badass	O
,	O
Tzipi	B-PER
Livni	I-PER
#aifestival	O

Funniest	O
thing	O
ever	O
http://damnyouautocorrect.com/449/dinnertime/	O

Check	O
out	O
the	O
"	O
Birdies	O
for	O
Babies	O
"	O
Facebook	B-ORG
page	O
:	O
http://ht.ly/5nM7L	O

Study	O
:	O
Time	O
vs	O
.	O
Money	O
:	O
Analyzing	O
Which	O
One	O
Rules	O
Consumer	O
Choices	O
http://bit.ly/nRFZc	O

Buy	O
your	O
tickets	O
in	O
advance	O
!	O
Nyah	O
of	O
Mars	O
commands	O
you	O
!	O
http://fb.me/198v0QNeZ	O

@shashib	B-PER
Because	O
of	O
all	O
those	O
mountains	O
!!	O
LOL	O
.	O
Hi	O
Shashi	B-PER
-	O
haven't	O
said	O
hi	O
since	O
we	O
met	O
at	O
BWE	B-MISC
.	O

Hardware	O
with	O
no	O
assembly	O
required	O
.	O
http://tinyurl.com/3hwlwun	O
Perfect	O
for	O
Fathers	B-MISC
Day	I-MISC
.	O

Wow	O
!	O
1st	O
time	O
Apple	B-ORG
store	O
in	O
Northbrook	B-LOC
dropped	O
the	O
ball	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Excuses	O
,	O
excuses	O
and	O
no	O
resolution	O
to	O
problem	O
.	O

Bite	O
into	O
our	O
latest	O
top	O
10	O
:	O
Nude	O
Stars	O
with	O
Fruits	O
and	O
Vegetables	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/faAovE	O

@PLAYTHISWAY	B-PER
Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
#FF	O
!	O
xoxo	O

Defend	O
your	O
privacy	O
!	O
See	O
which	O
social	O
networking	O
sites	O
are	O
the	O
most	O
secure	O
with	O
these	O
ratings	O
from	O
@zonealarm	O
http://ow.ly/5nT6K	O

@B_tojza	O
transvestire	O
u	O
mofo	O
tan	O
ur	O
ass	O

Outdoor	B-ORG
Traveler	I-ORG
Destinations	I-ORG
Celebrates	O
Launch	O
of	O
OTDestinations	O
.	O
com	O
with	O
...	O
http://ht.ly/1dyIV2	O

Four	O
hours	O
until	O
I'm	O
officially	O
done	O
with	O
grad	O
school	O
!	O
Woohoo	O
!	O

Looking	O
for	O
affiliates	O
to	O
help	O
promote	O
raffle	O
for	O
charity	O
.	O
http://cli.gs/PBXZz	O
Earn	O
$5	O
per	O
ticket	O
!	O
Signup	O
http://cli.gs/6mPJ2	O

Taking	O
time	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
As	O
a	O
driven	O
professional	O
and	O
overachiever	O
....	O
http://tinyurl.com/clkp3e	O

His	O
Instrumentation	O
makes	O
my	O
Heart	O
skip	O
a	O
Beat	O
...	O

Getting	O
ready	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
first	O
public	O
screening	O
of	O
DECENT	B-MISC
MEN	I-MISC
.	O
I'll	O
be	O
introducing	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
!	O

Brewer	O
...	O
SPLASH	O
.	O
#LETSGOBULLS	B-MISC

VIDEO	O
:	O
Five	O
PR	O
Problems	O
http://t.co/eRzipzh	O

CHICAGO	B-LOC
-	O
Tonight	O
@Big_Once	O
@DJJemChicago	O
&	O
@DJTrentino	O
compete	O
amongst	O
others	O
@RedBull	O
Thre3style	O
@TheMidChicago	O
-	O
10pm	O
sharp	O
,	O
#trustthedj	O

@Oprah	B-PER
has	O
a	O
great	O
section	O
of	O
articles	O
,	O
tips	O
and	O
tricks	O
for	O
#collegebound	O
#students	O
.	O
Get	O
prepared	O
!	O
http://so-kt.tw/CEU	O
#college	O

@katatomiclabs	O
ugh	O
,	O
mine	O
above	O
neighbor	O
has	O
the	O
speakers	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
wall	O
...	O
and	O
like	O
magic	O
every	O
night	O
around	O
1am	O
the	O
bass	O
gets	O
turned	O
up	O

Have	O
pix	O
of	O
Chicago	B-LOC
peeps	O
from	O
REBlogWorld	B-ORG
that	O
you'd	O
like	O
included	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
REVerb	B-ORG
newsletter	O
?	O
Please	O
let	O
us	O
know	O
,	O
thanks	O
!	O
#rbw09	O
#bwe09	O

OR	O
social	O
media	O
is	O
like	O
telling	O
a	O
story	O
at	O
a	O
dive	O
bar-	O
need	O
to	O
speak	O
loudly	O
to	O
be	O
heard	O
over	O
the	O
noise	O
#MMC2011	O

@SecondCityStyle	O
@mrbradgoreski	O
@bravotv	O
I	O
dont	O
think	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
HAPPIER	O
!!	O

Hey	O
fellow	O
followers	O
If	O
you	O
want	O
MORE	O
followers	O
check	O
out	O
this	O
site	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/9Wni63	O

@OfficialAudrina	B-PER
they	O
way	O
people	O
usually	O
fix	O
their	O
blackberry	O
is	O
by	O
buying	O
an	O
iPhone	O
:)	O

Check	O
out	O
this	O
awesome	O
site	O
:	O
!	O
TOP	O
6	O
PTC	O
SITES	O
!	O
-	O
http://Sweeva.com/go/eqX	O
#Sweeva	O

#FF	O
:)	O
@KateWhitfield	B-PER
@ChicagoDiane	B-PER
@ZoeInspiresYou	B-PER
@LenaOgan	B-PER
@catgrl67	O
@ShesSoSocial	O
@amazgrace	O
@ConsensualSex	O
@ski7days	O
@MFalstreau	B-PER

Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
inspiration	O
@jfritsche	B-PER
!	O
It	O
hit	O
the	O
spot	O
!	O
http://t.co/mJdAmt2	O

@kjlagrave	B-PER
oh	O
don't	O
worry-	O
Celine	B-PER
Dion	I-PER
was	O
just	O
code	O
for	O
your	O
canoeing	O
busker	O
.	O

BMXer	O
@NigelSylvester	B-PER
will	O
be	O
taking	O
over	O
our	O
handle	O
at	O
2pmCST	O
today	O
for	O
a	O
live	O
fan	O
chat	O
!	O
Tune	O
in	O
or	O
start	O
sending	O
in	O
your	O
Q	O
.	O
#InsideTheEdge	O

Sunday	O
Funday	O
tomorrow	O
at	O
Cedar	B-LOC
Hotel	I-LOC
!	O
Bull	O
And	O
Bear	O
industry	O
Sundays	O
after	O
(@	O
Proof	O
w/	O
6	O
others	O
)	O
http://4sq.com/m8PVzc	O

Chicago	O
Cubs	B-ORG
Online	O
:	O
Rambling	O
After	O
the	O
Cubs	B-ORG
Didn't	O
Lose	O
http://bit.ly/okQajH	O

Word	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
for	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
July	O
26	O
,	O
2011	O
mantic	O
\MAN-tik\	O
,	O
adjective	O
:	O
1	O
.	O
Of	O
or	O
pertaining	O
to	O
divination	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Having	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
divination	O

Urban	B-MISC
Folk	I-MISC
Circuit	I-MISC
date	O
change	O
!	O
Our	O
July	O
market	O
will	O
be	O
Saturday	O
,	O
July	O
23	O
NOT	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
The	O
market	O
will	O
be	O
held	O
at	O
...	O
http://fb.me/NnACQPVi	O

Big	O
Ol	O
Booty	O
an	O
a	O
cold	O
drink=	O
a	O
good	O
night	O

Cufon	B-PER
-	O
what	O
are	O
your	O
thoughts	O
on	O
this	O
text	O
replacement	O
technology	O
?	O
http://cufon.shoqolate.com	O
#cufon	B-PER
#wordpress	O
#fonts	O

@lpmassage	O
GM	O
food	O
=	O
genetically	O
modified	O
food	O
.	O

There	O
are	O
plenty	O
of	O
attractive	O
soccer	O
players	O
that	O
LA	B-LOC
could	O
find	O
to	O
replace	O
Beckham	B-PER
.	O
My	O
favorite	O
is	O
Fabio	B-PER
Cannavaro	I-PER
.	I-PER

Star	O
Wars	O
Meets	O
Metal	O
http://sns.mx/Ipdiy7	O

New	O
Review	O
:	O
Goulet	O
:	O
The	O
Spins	O
(	O
Roy	B-PER
Davis	I-PER
Jr	I-PER
&	O
JT	B-PER
Donaldson	I-PER
Remixes	O
,	O
Revolutionary	O
Music	O
)	O
//	O
http://t.co/dmkcNLH	O

@mspeeptoepumps	B-PER
MY	O
Heart	O
sincerly	O
goes	O
out	O
to	O
you	O
guys	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
Iam	O
so	O
sorry	O
please	O
accept	O
my	O
condolenses	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Much	O
Love	O
!!!	O
S	O
.	O
M	O
.	O
C	O

@amritabhatia	B-PER
@mrsgregginson	B-PER
editors	O
for	O
@the3six5chicago	B-ORG
,	O
yes	O
.	O
the	O
post	O
is	O
somewhere	O
on	O
http://the3six5chicago.com	O

Kindred	O
The	O
Family	O
Soul	O
-	O
Love	O
Has	O
No	O
Recession	O
-	O
2011	O
.	O
rar	O
http://hulkshare.com/jj80slnwve3e	O

The	O
Social	O
Network	O
:	O
Why	O
Justin	B-PER
Timberlake	B-PER
Has	O
Not	O
Confirmed	O
Your	O
Friend	O
Request	O
http://ht.ly/19aF7p	O

Are	O
you	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
affected	O
by	O
the	O
500	O
canceled	O
flights	O
in	O
Chicago	B-LOC
?	O
How	O
are	O
you	O
killing	O
time	O
?	O

@pample_moose	O
Girl	B-LOC
and	I-LOC
the	B-LOC
Goat	I-LOC
,	O
Purple	B-LOC
Pig	I-LOC
.	O
All	O
great	O
places	O
.	O

@Ramon_DeLeon	B-PER
can	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
Dominos	B-ORG
tonight	O
??	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
place	O
an	O
order	O
soon	O
:)	O

@raelt	B-PER
I	O
really	O
miss	O
you	O
,	O
the	O
floor	O
of	O
the	O
#smartshow	O
isn't	O
the	O
same	O
w/o	O
your	O
#Diva	O
commentary	O
.	O

Looking	O
for	O
a	O
Real	O
Estate	O
Guy	O
in	O
Beverly	B-LOC
Hills	I-LOC
?	O
...	O
simply	O
visit	O
BeverlyHillsRealEstateGuy	O
.	O
com	O
...	O
http://fb.me/BeGYQ0hr	O

Bring	O
your	O
bags	O
to	O
the	O
grocery	O
and	O
your	O
mug	O
to	O
your	O
local	O
coffee	O
shop	O
!	O
#greenliving	O

Clout	O
Club	O
x	O
SickLife	O
x	O
Doobie	O
Clothing	O
//	O
Next	O
Sunday	O
(	O
24th	O
)	O
//	O
New	O
Venue	O
!	O
//	O
18+	O
http://t.co/Evq7uPy	O
RETWEET	O
!!!!!!	O

CLE	O
10/8	O
Houston	B-LOC
:	O
Chemical	O
Products	O
and	O
Toxic	O
Torts	O
From	O
Crisis	O
to	O
Mass	O
Litigation	O
:	O
Starting	O
Smart	O
and	O
Finishing	O
Strong	O
http://bit.ly/d7iViC	O

Congrats	O
on	O
the	O
launch	O
party	O
for	O
Built	O
in	O
Chicago	B-LOC
http://bit.ly/kB7IWM	O
(	O
love	O
the	O
new	O
logo	O
)	O

Lol	O
..	O
RT	O
@ChanellD	B-PER
:	O
"	O
Nappy	O
ass	O
shit	O
.	O
Like	O
how	O
old	O
is	O
she	O
??	O
She	O
needs	O
some	O
of	O
that	O
PINK	O
lotion	O
shit	O
lol	O
"	O
-	O
@DanaPLambert	B-PER
#dead	O
lmfao	O

Jeanette	B-PER
L	O
.	O
Brooks	B-PER
and	O
the	O
Xocai	O
Story	O
From	O
Buffalo	B-LOC
Grove	I-LOC
http://bit.ly/bVjYed	O
via	O
@AddToAny	O

Wendell	B-PER
Cox	I-PER
:	O
Good	O
weather	O
cannot	O
nullify	O
the	O
effects	O
of	O
policies	O
that	O
drive	O
away	O
people	O
and	O
jobs	O
.	O
#Prop23	O
could	O
help	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/9EIDJC	O

Mini	O
Precint	O
Trainings	O
and	O
Holiday	O
Cookies	O
!	O
http://conta.cc/i9Whad	O
via	O
#constantcontact	O

Chi	B-ORG
Air	O
Hair	O
Appliances	O
are	O
15%	O
OFF	O
on	O
Walgreens	O
.	O
com	O
-	O
Get	O
the	O
Deal	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/kEMVd4	O

Lady	O
at	O
7-11	B-ORG
opened	O
a	O
thing	O
of	O
Doritos	O
then	O
topped	O
them	O
with	O
3	O
big	O
spoons	O
of	O
jalapenos	O
from	O
the	O
nacho	O
station	O
before	O
buying	O
them	O
.	O
#party	O

I	O
think	O
my	O
family	O
is	O
secretly	O
trying	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
feel	O
bad	O
for	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
prom	O
.	O
They	O
spend	O
too	O
much	O
time	O
talking	O
about	O
other	O
people	O
's	O
prom	O

#WhosGoing	O
?	O
to	O
#Fenway	B-LOC
Park	I-LOC
for	O
#BlueJays	B-ORG
vs	O
#RedSox	B-ORG
-	O
http://t.co/dXIEKEC	O

ay	O
i	O
just	O
got	O
a	O
bbm	O
hit	O
me	O
at	O
215B6C69	O

Union	O
Pizzeria	O
RT	O
@makeitbetterns	B-PER
:	O
Favorite	O
restaurant	O
on	O
the	O
North	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
?	O
Keep	O
'	O
em	O
comin'!	O

Leftover	O
prime	O
rib	O
and	O
au	O
gratin	O
potatoes	O
for	O
breakfast	O
...	O
still	O
so	O
good	O
!	O

@ekswitaj	B-PER
Except	O
all	O
I	O
do	O
is	O
tweet	O
for	O
help	O
.	O
:)	O

@DaGypsyBitchLa	O
@lexislkgversace	O
lol	O
.	O
its	O
coo	O

http://fb.me/u5YYnnn0	O

@habitforming	O
#sharktank	O
crashed	O
us	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
love	O
@zazzle	O
as	O
a	O
savior	O

Bon	B-PER
Iver	I-PER
loves	O
MKE	O
.	O
RT	O
@onmilwaukee	B-PER
:	O
Bon	B-PER
Iver	I-PER
gives	O
props	O
to	O
Pabst	B-ORG
team	O
in	O
Rolling	B-ORG
Stone	I-ORG
's	O
Best	O
of	O
Rock	O
http://bit.ly/kyFLId	O

Remote	O
iPad/iPhone	O
control	O
:	O
Apple	O
Support	O
Communities	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
cannot	O
control	O
the	O
units	O
Remote	O
by	O
Apple	O
Remot	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/pYWuzN	O

Today	O
at	O
Ebert	B-ORG
Fest	I-ORG
!	O
A	O
Small	O
Act	O
,	O
Life	O
Above	O
All	O
,	O
Leaves	O
of	O
Grass	O
and	O
I	O
Am	O
Love	O
.	O
Also	O
check	O
out	O
an	O
all	O
new	O
At	O
The	O
Movies	O
online	O
.	O

Thanks	O
for	O
everyone	O
's	O
support	O
.	O

Embark	O
on	O
a	O
journey	O
of	O
exploring	O
your	O
inner	O
self	O
.	O
Join	O
us	O
for	O
"	O
Waking	O
Up	O
The	O
Real	O
You	O
,"	O
&	O
soak	O
up	O
the	O
wisdom	O
!	O
http://t.co/MZdfiaG	O

Aiming	O
your	O
sprinkler	O
directly	O
across	O
the	O
sidewalk	O
:	O
very	O
funny	O
,	O
UIC	O
!	O
Why	O
exactly	O
do	O
you	O
have	O
sprinklers	O
on	O
today	O
anyway	O
??	O

@FueledByMarilyn	B-PER
I	O
have	O
no	O
idea	O
what	O
you're	O
trying	O
to	O
say	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
approve	O
.	O

@skabaru	O
hahah	O
,	O
that	O
article	O
rules	O
.	O

Great	O
tip	O
!	O
RT	O
@LoyolaCareerCtr	O
:	O
Please	O
use	O
your	O
alumni	O
network	O
!	O
Alumni	O
complain	O
they	O
don't	O
hear	O
enough	O
from	O
students	O
!	O
#JobHuntChat	O

@ashlieey	B-PER
explain	O
this	O
drive	O
by	O
bubbling	O
...	O

Interesting	O
article	O
on	O
Soros	B-PER
,	O
Financial	O
crisis	O
,	O
Obama	B-PER
,	O
etc	O
.	O
in	O
FT	O
:	O
http://tinyurl.com/cyq7rr	O

The	O
[	O
IMO	O
,	O
eventual	O
]	O
Social	O
Network	O
Bubble	O
is	O
the	O
new	O
Dot	O
Com	O
Bubble	O
.	O
#LinkedIn	B-ORG

A	O
big	O
#job	O
search	O
no-no	O
is	O
to	O
not	O
follow	O
thru	O
when	O
given	O
a	O
networking	O
lead	O
.	O
Makes	O
the	O
referer	O
look	O
bad	O
.	O

Social	O
media	O
and	O
the	O
new	O
wave	O
of	O
journalism	O
-	O
TNW	O
Social	O
Media	O
:	O
http://tnw.co/oolGZ9	O

I'm	O
in	O
Terre	B-LOC
Haute	I-LOC
....	O
#nocomment	O

Can't	O
afford	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
today	O
?	O
Why	O
not	O
Rent	O
it	O
?	O
Speakers	O
,	O
Amps	O
,	O
Wireless	O
,	O
Wedding	O
Systems	O
or	O
Concert	O
Sound	O
800-533-3923	O
http://ow.ly/5rtbN	O

Today	O
's	O
posts	O
:	O
Sox	B-ORG
to	O
debut	O
new	O
restaurant	O
for	O
opener	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
after	O
opener	O
,	O
plenty	O
of	O
bargains	O
for	O
Sox	B-ORG
tix	O
in	O
April	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/ie7Sgj	O

Breaking	O
News	O
:	O
Ricketts	O
,	O
Tribune	B-ORG
Co	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
reach	O
final	O
deal	O
on	O
sale	O
of	O
#Cubs	B-ORG
http://bit.ly/2v2kGz	O
#Chicago	B-LOC

@cubanalaf	B-PER
When	O
I	O
drove	O
from	O
Chicago	B-LOC
to	O
Austin	B-LOC
we	O
made	O
it	O
to	O
Dallas	B-LOC
in	O
about	O
15-16	O
hours	O
.	O

Lord	B-PER
I	O
worship	O
you	O
,	O
because	O
who	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
because	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
..	O
[	O
Like	O
it	O
?	O
http://bit.ly/pPY7oR	O
]	O

Don't	O
lean	O
on	O
technology	O
to	O
grow	O
ur	O
biz	O
.	O
Slow	O
&	O
consistent	O
improvement	O
2	O
ur	O
business	O
model	O
,	O
then	O
incorporate	O
technology	O
.	O
That	O
brings	O
success	O
.	O

@julesinchicago	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
?	O
Too	O
many	O
strollers	O
for	O
your	O
liking	O
?	O

@SirTristanSV	O
just	O
got	O
this	O
from	O
someone	O
else	O
too	O
.	O
great	O
to	O
see	O
twitter	B-ORG
also	O
increases	O
access	O
to	O
art	O
instead	O
of	O
just	O
marketing	O
schemes	O
:)	O

@bbdodd	O
Exactly	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
there	O
are	O
Polish	B-MISC
people	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
building	O
and	O
are	O
we	O
Polish	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
well	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
?	O

"	O
@stayhumble	O
:	O
S/O	O
to	O
@sirandmadame	O
@usernameautumn	O
and	O
@thesirofsmc	O
....."	O
Yessuh	O
!!	O

As	O
long	O
as	O
you	O
feel	O
the	O
need	O
to	O
put	O
some	O
kind	O
of	O
qualifying	O
adjective	O
before	O
the	O
word	O
"	O
sinner	O
"	O
you	O
won't	O
see	O
your	O
need	O
for	O
the	O
grace	O
of	O
God	O
.	O

Get	O
up	O
to	O
$1500	O
back	O
with	O
home	O
energy	O
upgrades	O
like	O
windows	O
,	O
insulation	O
,	O
etc	O
.	O
Http	O
:/	O
/is	O
.	O
gd/13FWW	O

YES	O
!	O
Sign	O
me	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
free	O
"	O
WINS	O
-	O
Write	O
It	O
NOW	O
with	O
SARK	O
"	O
call	O
on	O
July	O
7	O
@	O
9pm	O
Eastern	O
!	O
http://ht.ly/5qra3	O

It	O
's	O
football	O
time	O
on	O
Culby	O
10	O
.	O

@ColouredLines	B-PER
thanks	O
!!	O
I	O
LOVE	O
philip	B-PER
glass	I-PER
.	O

I	O
subscribed	O
to	O
RealtorActionCenter	O
's	O
channel	O
on	O
YouTube	O
.	O
http://www.youtube.com/user/RealtorActionCenter?feature=autoshare	O

Two	O
seats	O
left	O
in	O
our	O
iPhone	O
Developers	O
Workshop	O
this	O
Thursday	O
.	O
Got	O
an	O
app	O
idea	O
?	O
Get	O
the	O
core	O
tools	O
to	O
build	O
it	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/hEdCGE	O

Bathroom	O
Sinks	O
For	O
Your	O
Bathroom	O
Remodeling	O
Jobhttp	O
:/	O
/bit	O
.	O
ly/a9Wo9f	O
#chicago	B-LOC
#bathroom	O
#remodeling	O
#sinks	O

@nomgasm	B-PER
yep	O
I'm	O
heading	O
over	O
now	O
!	O
Need	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
all	O
these	O
food	O
trucks	O
are	O
about	O
,	O
haha	O
.	O

The	O
#Bulls	B-ORG
may	O
look	O
at	O
Vince	B-PER
Carter	I-PER
to	O
fill	O
that	O
starting	O
2-spot	O
.	O
I	O
honestly	O
don't	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
feel	O
about	O
that	O
.	O

@JoshBackers	B-PER
We're	O
starting	O
up	O
in	O
9	O
days	O
!	O
The	O
first	O
skate	O
street	O
event	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
weekend	O
of	O
Aug	O
11-14	O
though	O

http://fivesecondtest.com	O
and	O
usabilityhub	O
guys	O
have	O
done	O
a	O
great	O
job	O
taking	O
5st	O
,	O
adding	O
more	O
tools	O
and	O
turning	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
viable	O
product	O

@b_loock	B-PER
Make	O
sure	O
you're	O
logged	O
out	O
&	O
reset	O
your	O
password	O
by	O
clicking	O
the	O
"	O
Login	O
"	O
button	O
on	O
the	O
new	O
form	O
then	O
click	O
"	O
Forgot	O
UN	O
&	O
PW	O
"	O
link	O
.	O

Super	O
#travel	O
#writing	O
book	O
on	O
#japan	B-LOC
:	O
http://ow.ly/5Af9Z	O

Nick	B-PER
Cannon	I-PER
's	O
New	O
Weekly	O
Countdown	O
Show	O
Coming	O
To	O
WBBM-FM	B-ORG
--	O
http://bit.ly/hbTb2U	O

@hootsuite_help	O
Why	O
can	O
I	O
only	O
see	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Twitter	O
feeds	O
now	O
?	O
No	O
e-mail	O
notice	O
?	O
How	O
can	O
I	O
add	O
another	O
account	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
dashboard	O
?	O

@Chris_Culos	B-PER
@jerrydepizzo	B-PER
Sounds	O
like	O
a	O
crazy	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
614	O

@TLoveSpeaksss	O
yu	O
aint	O
hood	O
til	O
yu	O
got	O
a	O
license	O
...	O

Thank	O
you	O
all	O
for	O
the	O
wonderful	O
support	O
for	O
this	O
year	O
's	O
Autism	B-ORG
Speaks	I-ORG
Heroes	B-ORG
Ball	I-ORG
.	O
We	O
will	O
be	O
posting	O
pics	O
on	O
our	O
Facebook	B-ORG
Page	O
!	O

Happy	O
Friday	O
everyone	O
!	O
Treat	O
yourself	O
to	O
an	O
ice	O
cold	O
@HonestTea	O
for	O
just	O
$1	O
at	O
all	O
Jewel	B-ORG
Osco	I-ORG
's	O
with	O
your	O
preferred	O
card	O
today	O
!	O

Grace	B-PER
PR	O
thinks	O
@DinkelsBakery	B-ORG
hot	O
chocolate	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
in	O
town	O
--	O
yummy	O
!	O
:)	O
http://twitpic.com/3r89zj	O

Good	O
morning	O
!	O
How	O
are	O
all	O
those	O
New	O
Year	O
's	O
resolutions	O
holding	O
up	O
?	O
Still	O
hitting	O
the	O
gym	O
?	O
Staying	O
organized	O
?	O
:)	O

LCD	B-ORG
Soundsystem	I-ORG
's	O
"	O
All	O
My	O
Friends	O
"	O
-	O
In	O
LEGO	O
!!	O
http://sns.mx/IEdpy3	O

Flip	B-PER
will	O
be	O
59	O
on	O
September	O
18th	O
and	O
his	O
eyesight	O
is	O
great	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
read	O
the	O
type	O
he	O
can	O
read	O
without	O
glasses	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
has	O
a	O
Kindle	O
.	O

Spiderman	O
:	O
Shattered	O
Dimensions	O
-	O
Beenox	O
Interview	O
:	O
Spiderman	O
:	O
Shattered	O
Dimensions	O
-	O
Beenox	O
Interview	O
This	O
int	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/akHTrB	O

@CSNChi_Beatnik	O
clearly	O
cora	B-PER
knows	O
what	O
he	O
's	O
doing	O
!	O

"	O
Life	O
is	O
really	O
simple	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
insist	O
on	O
making	O
it	O
complicated	O
."	O
Confucius	B-PER

#SongsYouDontWannaHearInJail	O
"	O
Take	O
it	O
Back	O
"	O
Dorinda	B-PER
Clark	I-PER
Cole	I-PER

This	O
is	O
getting	O
extra	O
ridiculous	O
.	O
Another	O
attack	O
on	O
the	O
CTA	B-ORG
today	O
(	O
on	O
Billy	B-PER
Corgan	I-PER
's	O
brother	O
,	O
strangely	O
enough	O
)	O
http://tinyurl.com/3gajjde	O

Today..I'm	O
celebrating	O
over	O
125	O
subscribers	O
and	O
over	O
9,000	O
views	O
on	O
youtube	B-ORG
...	O
Get	O
plugged	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
http://bit.ly/260DXn	O

A	O
goal	O
properly	O
set	O
is	O
halfway	O
reached	O
.	O

@jeffcoffee	B-PER
@jenokimoto	B-PER
sat	O
in	O
on	O
innovation	O
session	O
.	O
Great	O
conversation	O
.	O

@mommacuisine	B-PER
Your	O
blog	O
is	O
making	O
me	O
hungry-lol	O
I	O
must	O
try	O
the	O
Spanish	B-MISC
Chicken	I-MISC
Bake	B-MISC
Recipe	I-MISC
!	O

#fail	O
word	O
choice	O
.	O
RT	O
@SeanDFrancis	B-PER
On	O
fire	O
?	O
Really	O
?	O
RT	O
@CBSNews	B-ORG
:	O
Amy	B-PER
Winehouse	I-PER
death	O
sets	O
Twitter	B-ORG
on	O
fire	O
http://bit.ly/pLr6Bu	O

@RobertKunda	B-PER
Except	O
that	O
the	O
chicken	O
does	O
not	O
cross	O
the	O
yardstick	O
first	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
Egg	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
.	O

Remodeling	O
Existing	O
Homes	O
Seen	O
as	O
the	O
Next	O
Big	O
Thing	O
in	O
Green	O
Building	O
:	O
http://ht.ly/4oKQz	O

We	O
have	O
lost	O
Louie	B-PER
Bellson	I-PER
,	O
1924-2009	O
.	O
Legendary	O
jazz	O
drummer	O
.	O
http://ow.ly/Rn7	O

Product	O
Marketing	O
Manager	O
(	O
Itasca	O
,	O
IL	O
)	O
http://bit.ly/bZZQTG	O
#jobs	O
#in	O

@BUSHBIGBIZNES	O
dm	O
me	O
the	O
address	O

Umbrella	O
Policy	O
:	O
Should	O
Be	O
Taken	O
Or	O
Not	O
|	O
Cheap	O
Insurance	O
and	O
Quotes	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/9GyyNn	O
via	O
@addthis	O

So	O
excited	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
2	O
more	O
Grandbabies	O
on	O
the	O
way	O
due	O
January	O
2010	O
.	O
That	O
will	O
bring	O
us	O
to	O
five	O
Grandkids	O
.	O
More	O
uses	O
for	O
our	O
Simply	O
Soft	O
!	O

@alyssadealmeida	B-PER
I	O
will	O
have	O
to	O
come	O
visit	O
you	O
and	O
@juliarosinus	B-PER
...	O
You	O
guys	O
should	O
meet	O
because	O
you're	O
both	O
amazing	O
and	O
in	O
NY	B-LOC
!	O

If	O
one	O
more	O
person	O
asks	O
me	O
if	O
this	O
bus	O
goes	O
to	O
Navy	B-LOC
Pier	I-LOC
,	O
I'm	O
going	O
to	O
drive	O
this	O
bus	O
off	O
Navy	B-LOC
Pier	I-LOC
.	O
#CTA	O

@KapriStylesxxx	B-PER
i	O
think	O
you	O
need	O
some	O
dark	O
chocolate	O
!	O

Whips	O
And	O
Chains	O
Excite	O
Me	O
...	O

Be	O
sure	O
to	O
check	O
out	O
our	O
Sweet	B-MISC
&	I-MISC
Spooky	B-MISC
Halloween	I-MISC
Event	I-MISC
!	O
Sign	O
up	O
today	O
!!!	O

Now	O
Honig	O
06	O
Cab	O
,	O
very	O
creamy	O
,	O
a	O
top	O
10	O
.	O
(	O
Don't	O
worry	O
,	O
I'm	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
family	O
:)	O
)	O

Good	O
article	O
on	O
the	O
future	O
of	O
paper	O
maps	O
:	O
http://tinyurl.com/28np3vp	O

Have	O
some	O
time	O
to	O
decide	O
but	O
wonder	O
if	O
2011	O
is	O
the	O
year	O
I'm	O
willing	O
to	O
spend	O
$3	O
on	O
one	O
doughnut	O

My	O
take	O
on	O
RIM	B-MISC
Playbook	I-MISC
vs	O
.	O
email	O
...	O
http://buz.tw/qpsYG	O

need	O
.	O
google	B-ORG
chat	O
.	O
now	O
.	O

@matt0willi	B-PER
If	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
count	O
on	O
Chocolates	O
on	O
MY	O
Pillow	O
.	O
http://chocolatesomp.com/housesitting.html	O

@tokissthecook	O
Oh	O
Lord	O
!	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
need	O
to	O
put	O
Ms	O
.	O
Honeycat	O
on	O
lock	O
down	O
.	O

@TimeOutChicago	B-PER
It	O
's	O
this	O
newfound	O
sunny	O
weather	O
that	O
's	O
got	O
every1	O
all	O
lovey-dovey	O
.	O
Good	O
day=good	O
night	O
.	O
Who	O
's	O
comin	O
to	O
@rinochicago	O
2nite	O
?	O

I'm	O
at	O
Viagra	O
Triangle	O
(	O
Rush	B-LOC
St	I-LOC
.,	O
State	O
St	O
.,	O
Chicago	B-LOC
)	O
http://4sq.com/pWKdcX	O

@Jenniferwah	B-PER
@rockinronnie	O
Rockin	O
got	O
just	O
a	O
smidge	O
wet	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Just	O
a	O
smidge	O
.	O
One	O
leg	O
off	O
the	O
wagon	O
,	O
trailing	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Barely	O
.	O

Men&#39	O
;	O
s	O
basketball	O
kicks	O
off	O
season	O
with	B-ORG
win	I-ORG
over	O
Purple	O
Eagles	O
http://tinyurl.com/y8h2og8	O

Juror	O
:	O
Rod	B-PER
Blagojevich	I-PER
proved	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
http://bit.ly/m7DTSN	O

QCertified	O
Daily	O
is	O
out	O
!	O
http://bit.ly/inVtEz	O
?	O
Top	O
stories	O
today	O
via	O
@seejanesell	B-PER
@fer_rosas2	O
@usedcarsauction	O
@kristenemery	B-PER

I'm	O
at	O
Glenn	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
Diner	I-LOC
(	O
1820	O
W	O
.	O
Montrose	O
Ave	O
.,	O
Wolcott	O
,	O
Chicago	O
)	O
http://4sq.com/ismdSp	O

My	O
brother	O
&	O
his	O
NEW	O
fiance	O
LOVE	O
gaming	O
.	O
The	O
proposal	O
is	O
uniquely	O
theirs	O
!	O
True	O
Love	O
's	O
Found	O
In	O
Nintendo	B-ORG
Classics	O
http://t.co/GaWAaba	O
@kotaku	O

Two	O
day	O
left	O
in	O
this	O
year	O

Google	B-ORG
Economist	O
Sees	O
Good	O
Signs	O
in	O
Searches	O
:	O
Jobless	O
Queries	O
Down	O
,	O
Real	O
Estate	O
Up	O
.	O
http://tr.im/yFy2	O

@larryluk	B-PER
Don't	O
hate	O
bro	O
...	O
your	O
boys	O
crumble	O
too	O
easy	O
.	O
Start	O
firing	O
3	O
's	O
down	O
by	O
9	O
with	O
4	O
to	O
go	O
...	O

Happy	O
Monday	O
-	O
Song	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
:	O
@rej3ctz	B-PER
-	O
Cat	O
Daddy	O
.	O
Learn	O
the	O
dance	O
,	O
learn	O
the	O
song	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
repeat	O

@klewing	B-PER
Considering	O
the	O
family	O
recipe	O
of	O
homemade	O
cheesecake	O
.	O
Quite	O
complicated	O
...	O
not	O
up	O
for	O
making	O
3	O
!	O
ha	O
ha	O

Check	O
Out	O
The	O
Top	O
100	O
#Songs	O
On	O
The	O
Official	O
Chicago	B-LOC
Myspace	O
Page	O
@Double_o_Promo	O
@Caine2	B-PER
@JayRush1	B-PER
@TTaylor1220	B-PER
myspace.com/Chicitytime	O

Calling	O
all	O
fans	O
of	O
@CableMtnLodge	O
!	O
Drawing	O
one	O
winner	O
on	O
Sept	O
23	O
of	O
the	O
Fall	O
Colors	O
Sweepstakes	O
-	O
http://bit.ly/b1bgKI	O
(	O
via	O
@wude72	O
)	O

@TheTimHayden	B-PER
With	O
music	O
,	O
baby	O
.	O
How	O
are	O
you	O
faring	O
,	O
daddy	O
?	O

@blb22	O
Twit	O
Pic	O
Dick	O
Pic	O

Talbott	B-ORG
Teas	I-ORG
hits	O
the	O
newsstand	O
in	O
Marie	B-ORG
Claire	I-ORG
Magazine	O
in	O
November	O
!	O

@localcelebrity	B-PER
@treobennyI	B-PER
feel	O
like	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
products	O
out	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
competition	O
if	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
mean	O
.	O

Short	O
update	O
:	O
Finch	B-ORG
's	O
steam	O
beer	O
,	O
not	O
bad	O
.	O
Short	O
's	O
Beach	O
Wheat	O
&	O
Nicie	O
Spicie	O
,	O
not	O
bad	O
.	O
Still	O
looking	O
for	O
a	O
holy-shit	O
beer	O
this	O
week	O
.	O

@BX_Bomber02	B-PER
and	O
congratulations	O
on	O
the	O
wedding	O
...	O
make	O
it	O
last	O

Figured	O
I	O
was	O
safe	O
getting	O
to	O
Smoque	B-ORG
BBQ	I-ORG
at	O
4:45	O
.	O
No	O
joy	O
!	O
Still	O
waiting	O
in	O
line	O
30	O
minutes	O
later	O
...	O

Thanks	O
to	O
our	O
early	O
partners	O
!	O
Be	O
Well	O
BlueberryMoon	B-ORG
Couvert	I-ORG
,	O
Exsalonce	O
Hush	O
LPMassageSpa	O
LPWaxing	O
Nail	O
.	O
com	O
Nirvana	O
Nail	O
Pure	O
Nirvana	O
...	O

@ScholAmerica	B-ORG
has	O
been	O
helping	O
students	O
succeed	O
for	O
50	O
years	O
!	O
http://scholarshipamerica.org/	O

Golden	B-ORG
Diner	I-ORG
Centers	I-ORG
serve	O
meals	O
and	O
gives	O
older	O
adults	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
meet	O
new	O
people	O
,	O
play	O
games	O
&	O
just	O
have	O
fun	O
.	O
http://ow.ly/5DMNO	O

@2EnvyEnt	B-PER
Did	O
you	O
decide	O
to	O
spend	O
Mother	O
's	O
Day	O
with	O
us	O
?	O

This	O
is	O
exciting	O
!	O
Let	O
us	O
do	O
the	O
clicking	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
http://followe.rs/qfB	O

I	O
swear	O
if	O
she	O
come	O
back	O
downstairs	O
she	O
getting	O
stole	O
off	O
of	O
#OnStoneAndGD	O

What	O
can	O
parents	O
do	O
to	O
prevent	O
#gang	O
activity	O
in	O
their	O
child	O
?	O
Learn	O
more	O
at	O
http://t.co/9uKG4zt	O

There	O
is	O
only	O
one	O
character	O
in	O
movies	O
that	O
can	O
get	O
a	O
new	O
actor	O
and	O
NOT	O
need	O
a	O
repeat	O
of	O
the	O
origin	O
:	O
James	O
Bond	O
.	O

By	O
@-tyleraturner	O
Green	B-ORG
Day	I-ORG
's	O
American	B-MISC
Idiot	I-MISC
.	O
A	O
truly	O
timeless	O
album	O
.	O
#-tgif	O
#nowplaying	O
http://ff.im/-geaUv	O
