Free-	O
Intellectual	O
Property	O
for	O
Non-Profits	O
,	O
Art	O
Organziations	O
&	O
Small	O
Business	O
Owners	O
02/17/11	O
Columbia-Harlem	B-LOC
SBDC	O
http://t.co/37l3SQl	O

Running	O
a	O
Robust	O
#HR	O
Shared	O
Services	O
Center	O
of	O
Excellence	O
http://bit.ly/l2PcAe	O
#HRIQ	O
#Podcast	O

Magic	O
Hat	O
:	O
Dance	O
Video	O
by	O
Mihran	B-PER
Kirakosian	I-PER
http://bit.ly/jGYH6Y	O

@eye4style	B-PER
Brave	O
girl	O
!	O
Karaoke	O
on	O
a	O
date	O
?	O

Things	O
left	O
in	O
7b	O
:	O
some	O
soap	O
,	O
travel	O
size	O
shampoo	O
,	O
cute	O
blue	O
tank	O
from	O
Express	O
.	O

@MeghanMillz	B-PER
WHAT	O
HAPPENED	O
?!	O

pantheon	O
booth	O
1515	O
is	O
in	O
full	O
force	O
at	O
comiccon	O
.	O
http://tinyurl.com/3zux8xu	O
#sdcc	O

A	O
#residenceinn	O
#FF	O
to	O
a	O
group	O
of	O
bloggers	O
I	O
can't	O
wait	O
to	O
meet	O
!	O
@TheBadAssMama	B-PER
@glamamom	B-PER
@MommasGoneCity	O
@StrollerBallet	O

The	O
March	O
towards	O
liberty	O
starts	O
now	O
!	O
FreedomWatch	O
!	O
It	O
's	O
a	O
libertarian	O
r3VOLution	O
!	O
Only	O
on	O
@FoxBusiness	O
,	O
the	O
power	O
to	O
prosper	O
.	O
8	O
&	O
11PM	O
ET	O

The	O
Cochrane	O
Collaboration	O
:	O
Comprehensive	O
geriatric	O
assessment	O
for	O
older	O
adults	O
admitted	O
to	O
hospital	O
-	O
http://t.co/ktoG6em	O

Spinback	O
featured	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
York	O
Observer	O
's	O
Betabeat	O
!	O
http://t.co/sWniZUm	O

@longorshort	O
sheesh	O
you	O
sure	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
girl	O
get	O
all	O
gooey	O
inside	O
.	O

Could	O
?	O
>	O
"	O
RT	O
@Hotdocstacy	O
:	O
All	O
new	O
@WhyYouSuckInBed	O
is	O
now	O
available	O
at	O
GloryHoleRadio	O
.	O
com	O
Learn	O
how	O
vaginas	O
could	O
run	O
the	O
world	O
"	O

Sitting	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
at	O
the	O
Metropolitan	O
opera	O
house	O
in	O
Lincoln	B-LOC
center	I-LOC
for	O
the	O
ballet	O
!	O
http://t.co/Vebe7Zx	O

@sitepointdotcom	O
We	O
are	O
following	O
you	O
!	O

@SharelOmer	B-PER
thanks	O
!	O
We	O
have	O
huge	O
plans	O
for	O
it	O
!	O
How	O
do	O
u	O
want	O
to	O
use	O
it	O
?	O
We'd	O
love	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
feedback	O

We	O
are	O
far	O
more	O
liable	O
to	O
catch	O
the	O
vices	O
than	O
the	O
virtues	O
of	O
our	O
associates	O

Author	O
cocktail	O
party	O
starting	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I'm	O
sneaking	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
hostess	O
duties	O
to	O
change	O
dresses	O
!	O
#4EvrSelina	O
#RWA11	O

Glimmer	O
...	O
indeed	O
...	O
#realestate	O
buyers	O
market	O
http://lnkd.in/FbSYhH	O

@Nayline	B-PER
Do	O
you	O
have	O
current	O
digital	O
portfolio	O
@SNDOOR	O
would	O
like	O
a	O
look	O
see	O
?	O
Please	O
forward	O
@JaiUnique	B-PER
for	O
NYC	B-LOC
casting	O
call	O
.	O
We	O
want	O
class	O
.	O

Fake	O
Apple	O
Stores	O
Shut	O
Down	O
http://t.co/0lrYTaX	O

Cure	O
your	O
recipients	O
wintertime	O
blues	O
with	O
Happy	O
Hour	O
Glasses	O
.	O
http://www.giftgenius.com/gifts/2149-happy-hour-glasses	O
http://bit.ly/bWu7rA	O

Calories	O
Count	O
First	O
!	O
http://bit.ly/itTBV7	O

Office	O
Manners	O
:	O
5	O
Rules	O
You	O
Need	O
To	O
Know	O
http://moneywatch.bnet.com/career-advice/blog/on-job/5-office-etiquette-rules-you-need-to-know/521/	O

Today	O
's	O
Eco-Buy	O
:	O
Thermos	O
Insulated	O
Bottles	O
&	O
Sippy	O
Cups	O
.	O
Perfect	O
for	O
Back	O
to	O
School	O
!	O
50%	O
off	O
.	O
www.ecobabybuys.com	O
#backtoschool	O
#sippycup	O

Brumberg	B-PER
Defends	O
Gay	O
Community	O
from	O
Paladino	B-PER
's	O
Remarks	O
|	O
http://brumberg2010.com/?p=912	O

Thank	O
u	O
manito	O
RT	O
@AMAURY_ALLPRO	B-PER
@J_Promo	O
happy	O
BDAY	O
bro	O
...	O

What	O
did	O
every	O
one	O
post	O
about	O
today	O
?	O
Send	O
us	O
some	O
links	O
=)	O
#fashion	O
#style	O
#blogs	O

@Mike_Peters	B-PER
http://bit.ly/11memd	O
Here	O
is	O
your	O
example	O
RINO	O
.	O
#njtcot	O
#njgop	O
#takebacknj	O

Spring	O
is	O
time	O
for	O
home	O
renovations	O
,	O
need	O
cash-out	O
refinancing	O
?	O
http://tinyurl.com/bxmtg1	O
#refinance	O
#mortgages	O

To	O
let	O
life	O
happen	O
to	O
you	O
is	O
irresponsible	O
.	O
To	O
create	O
your	O
day	O
is	O
your	O
divine	O
right	O
.	O

@arfrank	B-PER
Thank	O
you	O
!!	O

@romanymalco	B-PER
time	O
to	O
update	O
your	O
IMDB	B-ORG
profile	O
!	O
@justsayin	O

@dcoopsd	O
Thrive	O
In	O
Your	O
Small	O
Space	O
http://t.co/vBbQZr3	O

@BloodyPaws	O
she	O
's	O
following	O
again	O
!!!	O

@SharonDGriffin	B-PER
It	O
can	O
certainly	O
be	O
a	O
quick	O
way	O
to	O
ruin	O
your	O
reputation	O

Thank	O
you	O
!!	O
@GoldJenna	B-PER
&	O
@HeatherZeller	O
!!	O

Top	O
100	O
Social	O
Networked	O
Cities	O
in	O
the	O
US	B-LOC
c/o	O
@Mashable	O
-	O
where	O
does	O
your	O
city	O
rank	O
?	O
NYC	B-LOC
is	O
#53	O
!	O
http://yhoo.it/elSZGW	O

Check	O
out	O
Robin	B-PER
Thicke	I-PER
&	O
Jay-Z	B-PER
Recording	O
in	O
the	O
studio	O
http://bit.ly/3GbE4S	O

Thanks	O
lady	O
!	O
RT	O
@melissahallny	B-PER
:	O
@AmandaPearly	B-PER
love	O
the	O
new	O
cutch	O
and	O
what	O
a	O
great	O
cause	O
.	O
Check	O
it	O
out	O
:	O
http://t.co/YsxQ64h	O

Hot	O
topic	O
on	O
#bizbash	O
linkedin	O
community	O
:	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
when	O
a	O
supplier	O
won't	O
provide	O
cert	O
of	O
insurance	O
,	O
join	O
the	O
convo	O
http://linkd.in/eigvx3	O

I	O
WAS	O
JUST	O
GOING	O
TO	O
TWEET	O
THAT	O
!	O
RT	O
@ValentinaMonte	B-PER
:	O
In	O
retrospect	O
,	O
that	O
little	O
girl	O
did	O
a	O
great	O
ross	O
perot	O
.	O
#90sareallthat	O

Good	O
Morning	O
!	O

I'm	O
sure	O
that	O
most	O
of	O
you	O
don't	O
go	O
on	O
Neopets	O
.	O
com	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
might	O
find	O
their	O
latest	O
site	O
feature	O
vaguely	O
familiar	O
...	O
http://sns.mx/p9ely9	O

Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
follow	O
@singforhope	O
!	O

@skydiver	B-PER
Ricky	B-PER
Gervias	I-PER
,	O
Martin	B-PER
Freeman	I-PER
,	O
Lucy	B-PER
Davis	I-PER
,	O
Mackenzie	B-PER
Crook	I-PER
and	O
Stephen	B-PER
Merchant	I-PER

I	O
realize	O
that	O
some	O
days	O
I'm	O
just	O
a	O
punk	O
rock	O
prince	O
wearing	O
the	O
designer	O
labels	O
of	O
pop	O
.	O

It	O
's	O
fight	O
or	O
flight	O
for	O
Twitter	B-ORG
by	O
@charlesarthur	B-PER
http://t.co/COLaPMG	O
via	O
@guardian	B-ORG

All	O
you	O
people	O
.	O
Wanna	O
go	O
hang	O
out	O
with	O
your	O
Romans	O
.	O
Your	O
fuckin	O
Romans	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
sad	O
.	O
#NYCBumRants	O

@serkilicious	B-PER
thanks	O
Serkan	B-PER
!	O
Send	O
info	O
about	O
it	O
to	O
info	O
AT	O
XELLEmusic	O
DOT	O
com	O
and	O
we'll	O
try	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
happen	O
!	O

@peggyvicioso	B-PER
We	O
have	O
lots	O
of	O
goodies	O
from	O
Auntie	B-PER
Peggy	I-PER
.	O
:-)	O

Up	O
early	O
,	O
heading	O
out	O
to	O
Bk	O
for	O
a	O
shoot	O
.	O
Should	O
be	O
fun	O
.	O

Using	O
Viral	O
Marketing	O
Strategies	O
to	O
Bring	O
More	O
Viewers	O
to	O
your	O
Site	O
http://bit.ly/elzIK7	O

DEA	O
wants	O
to	O
pay	O
black	O
ppl	O
to	O
translate	O
"	O
black	O
ppl	O
language	O
"	O
so	O
cops	O
can	O
arrest	O
more	O
black	O
ppl	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/dkV5Ry	O

Titus	B-PER
Welliver	I-PER
Joins	O
FX	O
's	O
Powers	O
-	O
Comic	O
Book	O
Resources	O
http://t.co/xVtI8sQ	O

Makeup	O
Ads	O
Banned	O
in	O
UK	B-LOC
for	O
Too	O
Much	O
Photoshop	O
#photography	O
http://t.co/6J7xX0Z	O

How	O
Bloggers	O
Can	O
Use	O
Book	O
Reviews	O
to	O
Conne	O
...	O
http://www.socialmediaexaminer.com/how-bloggers-can-use-book-reviews-to-connect-with-experts/	O

That	O
's	O
the	O
OG	O
combo	O
RT	O
@Luis_Ruano	B-PER
:	O
I'm	O
a	O
Hypebeast	O
for	O
this	O
one	O
...	O
#HEINEKEN100	B-MISC
http://instagr.am/p/HhU-a/	O

Discuss	O
Obama	B-PER
and	O
Keith	B-PER
Olbermann	I-PER
's	O
stances	O
on	O
gay	O
marriage	O
on	O
the	O
Friendfactor	B-MISC
blog	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/kg4f2T	O
#NY4M	O

Photo	O
:	O
http://tumblr.com/xeu1du19v2	O

The	O
Simpsons	O
Futurama	O
Crossover	O
Crisis	O
Giveaway	O
!	O
Enter	O
to	O
win	O
a	O
#free	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
new	O
book	O
!	O
http://ow.ly/1tdsQ	O

Review	O
on	O
New	O
Vegas	B-LOC
DLC	O
Dead	O
Money	O
is	O
up	O
.	O
A	O
mixed	O
bag	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
http://ow.ly/3vnwm	O

Thanks	O
!	O
@FrommersTravel	O
@notfortourists	O
@zanya	B-PER
@johngerzema	B-PER
@barrysmyth	B-PER
@chispitabrown	O
@amywiddowson	O
@TLWinSF	O
@EvanChen	B-PER

@brides	O
@oscarprgirl	O
WOW	O
I	O
agree	O
!	O

A	O
ShowMe	O
user	O
@mcarls	B-PER
(	O
and	O
his	O
son	O
)	O
using	O
ShowMe	O
to	O
review	O
ShowMe	O
(	O
so	O
meta)	O
:	O
http://www.showmeapp.com/sh/?i=102	O

Just	O
finished	O
a	O
fun	O
grilling	O
segment	O
on	O
Fox	O
5	O
Good	O
Day	O
NY	B-LOC
.	O
Thx	O
@jessgdny	B-PER
@gregkellyfox5	B-PER
@juliechangfox5	B-PER
@rosannascotto	B-PER

One	O
Of	O
A	O
Kind	O
Tie	O
Dye	O
Clothing	O
At	O
World	O
Fest	O
2011	O
http://tinyurl.com/5tsxc5v	O

I	O
burned	O
my	O
tongue	O
on	O
soup	O
today	O
&	O
it	O
's	O
still	O
all	O
raw	O
&	O
nasty	O
.	O
What	O
the	O
fuck	O
was	O
I	O
doing	O
eating	O
soup	O
today	O
?!	O
Serves	O
me	O
right	O
,	O
I	O
guess	O
.	O

Start	O
your	O
day	O
off	O
right	O
with	O
the	O
perfect	O
business	O
attire	O
!	O
Get	O
tips	O
from	O
real	O
stylists	O
on	O
corporate	O
do	O
's	O
and	O
don'ts.	O
http://bit.ly/NYsms	O

We	O
dare	O
call	O
them	O
comics	O
!	O
#kidscomics	B-MISC
@fuseeight	O
@goodcomics4kids	O
Tell	O
us	O
What	O
you	O
call	O
them	O
?	O
where	O
you	O
shelve	O
them	O
?	O
http://bit.ly/apMW3M	O

Astor	B-PER
's	O
son	O
--	O
Prison	O
for	O
the	O
over	O
80	O
crowd	O
?	O
http://bit.ly/LNf66	O

Blasting	O
Forty	O
Licks	O
to	O
mask	O
the	O
jackhammers	O
&	O
dishwasher	O
.	O
#GoodMorningNY	O

Esp	O
the	O
classy	O
ones	O
..	O

YA	O
:	O
Horror	O
,	O
dark	O
mystery	O
,	O
contemp	O
.	O
fiction	O
w/	O
strong	O
characters	O
,	O
magical	O
realism	O
,	O
light	O
fantasy	O
,	O
psych	O
thrillers	O
,	O
witches/ghosts/monsters	O

@dvisiblemag	O
Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
follow	O
fam	O
!	O
Join	O
our	O
EXCLUSIVE	O
network	O
http://qwiliterecords.ning.com	O
for	O
latest	O
on	O
QwiLite	O
Records	O
!	O
much	O
luv	O
!	O

The	O
4th	O
Bin	O
mobile	O
unit	O
is	O
rocking	O
the	O
LES	B-LOC
and	O
Lower	B-LOC
Manhattan	I-LOC
!	I-LOC

Does	O
The	O
Scent	O
Of	O
Pumpkin	O
Pie	O
Make	O
You	O
Fall	O
In	O
Love	O
?	O
http://ow.ly/1dOsXR	O

@StephenKinsella	B-PER
Recites	O
Dr	O
.	O
Goose	O
:	O
[	O
Audio	O
]	O
Stephen	B-PER
Kinsella	I-PER
,	O
Lecturer	O
in	O
Economics	O
at	O
the	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Limeric	I-ORG
...	O
http://bit.ly/lZ2WbZ	O

@ShellyWymer	B-PER
What	O
arrogance	O
-	O
those	O
guys	O
thought	O
they	O
could	O
stage	O
a	O
coup	O
,	O
discredit	O
Obama	B-PER
....	O
and	O
screw	O
the	O
nation	O
on	O
8/2	O

@MarkSkinner_	O
tools	O
us	O
stronger	O
,	O
faster	O
,	O
more	O
efficient	O
.	O
they	O
don't	O
point	O
the	O
way	O

Charlotte-Mecklenburg	O
Media	O
Specialists	O
to	O
Keep	O
Jobs	O
http://bit.ly/kjHVli	O

Using	O
the	O
Power	O
of	O
Subtext	O
for	O
Your	O
Website	O
http://bit.ly/mQjlRr	O

Of	O
all	O
the	O
Jazz	O
musicians	O
you've	O
seen	O
live	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
your	O
favorite	O
and	O
why	O
?	O
http://fb.me/E89wNmlp	O

Connect	O
with	O
us	O
on	O
Facebook	B-ORG
too	O
!	O
http://www.facebook.com/avelient	O

@ironbunny	B-PER
HAHAHAHA	O
.	O
your	O
ass	O
packed	O
up	O
and	O
left	O
?	O

http://bit.ly/mQSrAF	O
Freestyle	O
-	O
Join	O
Forces	O
!!	O

Insights	O
from	O
top	O
experts	O
and	O
more	O
.	O
For	O
FREE	O
!	O
Subscribe	O
to	O
RSS	O
blog	O
http://www.prlog.org/11042870-american-conference-institutes-blog.html	O

Lol	O
,	O
nope	O
!	O
Much	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
well	O
#harBodyStatus	O
RT	O
@MicBlaque	O
:	O
@HipHopHardBody	O
yoo	O
i	O
thought	O
i	O
was	O
like	O
the	O
(	O
cont	O
)	O
http://tl.gd/9s97jb	O

@JenKirkman	B-PER
I	O
was	O
once	O
at	O
a	O
party	O
w/	O
@dianasaurus	B-PER
where	O
we	O
met	O
Wes	B-PER
Craven	I-PER
and	O
she	O
yelled	O
at	O
him	O
for	O
giving	O
her	O
nightmares	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
glorious	O
.	O

I	O
can	O
haz	O
a	O
7	O
train	O
this	O
morning	O
?	O

@RamiroProd	O
as	O
you	O
always	O
do	O
.	O

?	O
#Dr0p	O
...	O
Streaming	O
Tracks	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
~	O
#AmericanRoyalty	O
http://t.co/7phhXRW	O
Enjoy	O
the	O
new	O
EP	O
!	O
Tracks	O
are	O
Levolution	O
&	O
Sun	O
Day	O
.	O
Love	O
them	O
!	O

@CashDeVereaux	B-PER
Nita	B-PER
,	O
whats	O
good	O
my	O
fellow	O
vampire	O

Nicki	B-PER
Minaj	I-PER
&	O
Ricky	B-PER
Martin	I-PER
announced	O
as	O
MAC	O
's	O
newest	O
#VivaGlam	O
faces	O
.	O
On	O
set	O
in	O
Miami	B-LOC
today	O
shooting	O
'	O
12	O
w/	O
David	B-PER
La	I-PER
Chappelle	I-PER
.	O
#beauty	O

Back	O
home	O
after	O
my	O
"	O
Ballers	O
Trip	O
"	O
to	O
Dallas	B-LOC
for	O
Game	O
3	O
!	O
The	O
Heat	O
was	O
on	O
.	O
So	O
much	O
to	O
tell	O
.	O
Work	O
first	O
,	O
catch	O
y'all	O
la8r	O
.	O

Ben	B-PER
Mandelson	I-PER
&	O
Justin	B-PER
Adams	I-PER
of	O
the	O
Black	O
Earth	O
Boys	O
/	O
@BillyBragg	B-PER
's	I-PER
Blokes	O
running	O
thru	O
songs	O
for	O
#LCBigBusk	O
http://lockerz.com/s/124178799	O

My	O
bracket	O
is	O
pretty	O
wrecked	O
(	O
fucking	O
L'ville	O
)	O
but	O
George	B-PER
Mason	I-PER
just	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
style	O

Our	O
National	O
Arena	O
Tour	O
opened	O
last	O
night	O
in	O
Madison	B-LOC
-	O
did	O
anyone	O
catch	O
the	O
show	O
?	O

An	O
interview	O
with	O
Philip	B-PER
Scott	I-PER
Andrews	I-PER
,	O
former	O
@AP	O
intern	O
and	O
current	O
@NYTimes	B-ORG
photographer	O
,	O
on	O
@NYTimesPhoto	O
:	O
http://nyti.ms/eH2fvC	O

I'm	O
at	O
Tranny	O
Disco	O
w/	O
@adponce	B-PER
@johnlendman	B-PER
http://4sq.com/j1Gra8	O

@RudyRoOdles	B-PER
LOL	O
sorry	O
it	O
took	O
so	O
long	O
sweets	O
....	O

Check	O
out	O
Laurie	B-PER
's	O
favorite	O
app	O
on	O
Cool	B-ORG
Mom	I-ORG
Tech	I-ORG
-	O
and	O
don't	O
forget	O
our	O
own	O
Laurie	O
Berkner	O
Band	O
app	O
too	O
!	O
http://fb.me/UDRrBvil	O

What	O
could	O
be	O
more	O
difficult	O
than	O
venturing	O
out	O
on	O
your	O
own	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
feature	O
?	O
How	O
about	O
...	O
http://fb.me/BMoIw73Y	O

Hey	O
thanks	O
that	O
sounds	O
awesome	O
!	O
Wait	O
...	O
RT	O
@shibainus_tms	O
Welcome	O
to	O
the	O
series	O
of	O
intermittent	O
panic	O
attendant	O
upon	O
becoming	O
a	O
Shiba	O
parent	O

Going	O
from	O
"	O
Someday	O
"	O
to	O
"	O
Why	O
Not	O
Now	O
"	O
http://networkedblogs.com/fhsVf	O
#makeithappen	O

Get	O
Thin	O
For	O
Life	O
Weight	O
Loss	O
System	O
http://bit.ly/hoIDDK	O

NY	B-ORG
Times	I-ORG
looks	O
at	O
mandatory	O
furloughs	O
from	O
the	O
employee	O
perspective	O
http://is.gd/12oWQ	O

@austinnbostonn	B-PER
check	O
out	O
our	O
collection	O
of	O
glasses	O
online	O
-	O
we	O
can	O
send	O
you	O
a	O
replacement	O
pair	O
within	O
24	O
hours	O
with	O
a	O
prescription	O
!	O

Misunderstanding	O
SNAFU	O
:	O
I'm	O
LMAO	O
at	O
weight	O
loss	O
,	O
viagra	B-MISC
,	O
mafia	O
family	O
,	O
&	O
somebody	O
said	O
something	O
bad	O
about	O
me	O
tweets-NOT	O
seeking	O
ANSWERS	O

SEC	O
charged	O
advisor	O
who	O
allegedly	O
lied	O
to	O
his	O
friends	O
&	O
family	O
telling	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
investing	O
their	O
$$$	O
in	O
a	O
company	O
developing	O
a	O
cancer	O
drug	O

Ladenburg	O
Augments	O
Its	O
Eastern	O
Exposure	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/bDrXZN	O
via	O
@addthis	O

@vp24lxhm	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
pics	O
!	O

Break	O
time	O
between	O
sessions	O
and	O
we're	O
teaching	O
pat	O
about	O
twitter	O

88%	O
Plan	O
To	O
Use	O
Mobile	O
This	O
Year	O
according	O
to	O
ANA	O
,	O
MMA	O
:	O
http://dld.bz/JQtu	O
#in	O

Tech	O
giants	O
Nokia	B-ORG
and	O
Apple	B-ORG
return	O
to	O
the	O
patent	O
battle	O
,	O
adds	O
to	O
the	O
string	O
of	O
lawsuits	O
http://ow.ly/4p2y3	O
#patent	O

Sounds	O
great	O
if	O
sub	O
vodka	O
for	O
gin	O
.	O
RT@Liqurious	O
no	O
better	O
way	O
to	O
enjoy	O
a	O
ball	O
game	O
than	O
with	O
a	O
Cooperstown	B-LOC
Cocktail	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/iy4YZ2	O

Really	O
looking	O
forward	O
to	O
my	O
vacation	O
next	O
week	O
.	O
Really	O
sad	O
about	O
all	O
the	O
work	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
do	O
before	O
I	O
leave	O
.	O

Your	O
choice	O
in	O
social	O
media	O
,	O
shape	O
or	O
be	O
shaped	O
by	O
the	O
conversation	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/glCSEq	O
#socpharm	O
#hcsm	O

Do	O
same-sex	O
spouses	O
ever	O
follow	O
the	O
tradition	O
of	O
taking	O
one	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
last	O
name	O
?	O
(	O
and	O
if	O
so	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
they	O
choose	O
?!	O
)	O
#gaymanners	O

#gop	O
A	O
Word	O
from	O
Dr	B-PER
.	I-PER
Thomas	B-PER
Sowell	I-PER
http://bit.ly/cxS2dQ	O

Behind	O
the	O
Veil	O
:	O
Questions	O
About	O
Art	O
Authentication	O
-	O
Supreme	O
Fiction	O
http://fb.me/QqrphZP5	O

@ATOMsanRafael	O
My	O
pleasure	O
.	O
Have	O
a	O
great	O
week	O
!	O

Watching	O
Dalia	B-PER
Davi	I-PER
perform	O
(@	O
Repertorio	O
Espanol	O
)	O
http://4sq.com/dHaP9B	O

How	O
to	O
Enhance	O
your	O
Eyelashes	O
and	O
Eyebrows	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/9MXjGS	O
via	O
@suite101	O

When	O
the	O
missus	O
says	O
'	O
I	O
wanna	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
foursquare	O
'	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
's	O
going	O
mainstream	O

it	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
great	O
!	O
RT	O
@leibofest	O
@JewishCamp	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
at	O
@CapitalCamps	O
R	O
so	O
excited	O
for	O
#cornerstone11	O
!	O
#jewishcamp	O
#cornerstone2011	O

United	O
Nations	O
'	O
Luescher	B-PER
shows	O
communicators	O
how	O
to	O
simplify	O
|	O
PRWeek	O
US	O
http://ow.ly/2VToJ	O
#prsa_ic	O

The	O
Facebook	B-MISC
Setting	O
You	O
Should	O
Change	O
as	O
Quickly	O
as	O
Possible	O
http://gaw.kr/eEptRt	O
http://fb.me/HQDSW99E	O

AT&T	O
previously	O
offered	O
an	O
iPhone	O
insurance	O
plan	O
for	O
$12	O
a	O
month	O
with	O
a	O
deductible	O
up	O
to	O
$199	O
,	O
de	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/pxrmHP	O
#VerizoniPhone	O

YOU'RE	O
GOING	O
TO	O
LOVE	O
@DaSexiiBad1	O
>>>	O
http://bit.ly/mqK46n	O
NEW	O
@GORGEOUSACADEMY	O
FEATURE	O

Summer	O
Weekend	O
Special	O
-	O
Romance	O
Books	O
for	O
$1	O
!	O
http://t.co/QQFHmb2	O

A	O
*must*	O
read	O
:	O
Virtues	O
of	O
"	O
rigorous	O
theology	O
,"	O
seen	O
via	O
review	O
of	O
"	O
Book	O
of	O
#Mormon	O
"	O
musical	O
http://ow.ly/4F3ZF	O
@NYTimes	B-ORG
'	O
David	B-PER
Brooks	I-PER
#LDS	O

I	O
would	O
say	O
#ihatemondays	O
but	O
tonight	O
is	O
#NightStrike	O
with	O
UNLIMITED	O
Bowling	O
at	O
all	O
our	O
locations-	O
so	O
now	O
#ilovemondays	O
!	O

A3	O
:	O
Co-Create	O
a	O
new	O
language	O
(	O
out	O
of	O
shared	O
experience	O
)	O
new	O
signifiers	O
and	O
a	O
short-hand	O
for	O
l8r	O
to	O
break	O
habit	O
.	O
#npcons	O

getting	O
some	O
fresh	O
air	O
..	O
will	O
give	O
a	O
walk	O

@MattHaze	B-PER
I	O
was	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
darn	O
funny	O
!	O

Elice	O
:	O
"	O
Alex	B-PER
and	O
Roger	B-PER
both	O
love	O
storytelling	O
through	O
language	O
and	O
imagination	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
where	O
their	O
styles	O
overlap	O
"	O

Love	O
your	O
life	O
.	O

@roxiebeane	B-PER
Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
Follow	O
Friday	O
shout-out	O
!	O
http://bit.ly/FollowFridayCap	O

Charlie	B-PER
should	O
take	O
out	O
KK	O
so	O
he	O
gets	O
all	O
huffy	O
and	O
talks	O
about	O
his	O
hurt	O
feelings	O
.	O

How	O
Fast	O
Food	O
Chains	O
Could	O
Prevent	O
Water	O
Pollution	O
-	O
http://bit.ly/lhk3zR	O
(	O
via	O
@fastcompany	O
)	O

Quell	O
his	O
barkin	O
'	O
and	O
you	O
dispel	O
his	O
sparkin'!	O
RT	O
@russbengtson	B-PER
The	O
refs	O
ain't	O
fussin	O
'	O
over	O
KG	B-PER
's	O
cussin'!	O

@NewYorkMets	B-PER
33-45	O

Black	O
Friday	O
gets	O
a	O
new	O
meaning	O
..	O
The	O
price	O
of	O
stereotyping	O
,	O
pre-judgment	O
and	O
presumption	O
come	O
due	O
this	O
season	O
...	O
www.giveusourproper.org	O

I've	O
already	O
set	O
my	O
TiVo	O
for	O
The	O
Conan	O
Show	O
on	O
Fox	B-ORG
,	O
this	O
September	O
.	O
NBC	B-ORG
,	O
O'Brien	B-PER
agree	O
$45	O
mil	O
exit	O
deal	O
http://tinyurl.com/yjl9r2f	O

@Urban_Zen	O
My	O
pleasure	O
,	O
and	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
support	O
of	O
@LynchFoundation	O
and	O
@TMmeditation	B-MISC
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
world	O
of	O
both	O
.	O

@phxguy88	O
glad	O
i	O
could	O
help	O
out	O

Dang	O
.	O
RT	O
@cnnbrk	O
Singer	O
#AmyWinehouse	B-PER
found	O
dead	O
at	O
her	O
apartment	O
in	O
London	B-LOC
,	O
UK	B-LOC
Press	O
Association	O
reports	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
27	O
.	O

TWO	O
FREE	O
TICKETS	O
!!	O
BOBBY-	B-PER
musical	O
comedy	O
of	O
a	O
Jewish	O
,	O
gay	O
man	O
w/	O
Tourettes	O
becoming	O
a	O
hot	O
young	O
talent	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/theaterscene-bobby	O

Meek	B-PER
Mill	I-PER
Ft	O
.	O
Triple	O
C	O
&	O
Magazeen	O
-	O
Put	O
Yourself	O
in	O
My	O
Position	O
http://t.co/beDeBB2	O

@GameraSpinning	O
.	O
Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
tweet	O
.	O

UNICEF	B-ORG
's	O
Trick	O
or	O
Treat	O
Boxes	O
Have	O
Barcodes	O
to	O
Enable	O
Smartphone	O
Donations	O
|	O
Inhabitots	O
http://su.pr/1WXuX6	O

Beyonce	B-PER
's	O
'	O
4	O
'	O
Headed	O
For	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
with	O
Perhaps	O
300,000	O
|	O
Billboard	B-ORG
.	O
com	O
:	O
fourth	O
studio	O
album	O
,	O
"	O
4	O
,"	O
i	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/lQvgkw	O

Oh	O
dear	O
lord	O
,	O
a	O
sequel	O
to	O
Lolita	B-PER
--	O
JLolita	O
--	O
that	O
imagines	O
Humbert	O
as	O
JLo	B-PER
and	O
Lolita	O
as	O
Puff	B-PER
Daddy	I-PER
?	O
Wow	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
speechless	O
.	O

$12	O
for	O
15	O
Issues	O
of	O
"	O
Food	O
&	O
Wine	O
"	O
Magazine	O
($	O
24.99	O
Value	O
)	O
http://ow.ly/1bCKcn	O

I	O
hope	O
my	O
client	O
&	O
I	O
don't	O
get	O
blown	O
2	O
Kansas	O
in	O
all	O
this	O
wind	O
as	O
we	O
make	O
our	O
way	O
to	O
Garden	O
State	O
Plaza	O
mall	O
!	O
Lol	O
!	O

@KriziaLauren	B-PER
Thanks	O
for	O
entering	O
!	O
Who	O
is	O
your	O
favorite	O
band	O
on	O
@VansWarpedTour	B-MISC
?	O
#warpedtour	B-MISC

@SpookDaMonster	O
Diddy	B-PER
will	O
dance	O
all	O
over	O
Birdman	O

Expo	O
seeks	O
innovative	O
ideas	O
to	O
help	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
Gulf	O

Mets	O
Ship	O
Francisco	B-PER
Rodriguez	I-PER
to	O
Milwaukee	B-LOC
http://bit.ly/qfmLv5	O
@JoshAlper	O

Got	O
to	O
check	O
out	O
this	O
kid	O
!	O
Super	O
funny-about	O
to	O
breakthrough	O
at	O
Disney	B-ORG
-	O
#armaanthegreat	B-MISC
-	O
@armaanthegreat	O
-	O
Follow	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
jokes	O
PLSRT	O

"	O
NYC	B-LOC
Cocktail	O
Week	O
2011	O
"	O
via	O
Liquor	O
.	O
com	O
(	O
h/t	O
@natalie4287	B-PER
)	O
-	O
http://bit.ly/l7Rf63	O

Prevent	O
Stowaway	O
Bedbugs	O
When	O
You	O
Travel	O
-	O
Prevent	O
Stowaway	O
Bedbugs	O
When	O
You	O
Travel	O
by	O
Carolyn	O
W	O
.	O
Paddock	O
...	O
http://tumblr.com/xwx2zbg9ud	O

@marilynpeake	B-PER
Thank	O
you	O
!	O
I'm	O
freaking	O
out	O
over	O
here	O
haha	O

200	O
year-old	O
guitars	O
in	O
Venice	B-LOC
(	O
almost)	O
,	O
and	O
I'm	O
On	O
My	O
Way	O
.	O
Check	O
out	O
my	O
blog	O
:	O
http://t.co/RFXShCz	O

Damon	B-PER
Lindelof	I-PER
:	I-PER
Confession	O
Time	O
http://sns.mx/pYd0y3	O

nightcrawler	O
-	O
lionel	B-PER
richie	I-PER
"	O
dancing	O
on	O
the	O
ceiling	O
"	O
#xmenkaraoke	O

Migrating	O
to	O
a	O
cloud-based	O
application	O
carries	O
risks	O
that	O
can	O
expose	O
companies	O
to	O
costly	O
damage	O
suits	O
and	O
litigation	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
covered	O
?	O

Clothing	O
Fashion	O
|	O
Deadly	O
Sins	O
Lisa	O
Lashes	O
Photoshoot	O
.	O
m4v	O
http://dlvr.it/ZzWPN	O

What	O
would	O
the	O
Mets	O
do	O
if	O
the	O
Dodgers	O
gave	O
up	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
Brooklyn	B-LOC
?	O
Would	O
they	O
all	O
get	O
sensible	O
jobs	O
at	O
H&R	O
Block	O
?	O

In	O
LA	B-LOC
for	O
#operaconf	O
;	O
just	O
got	O
some	O
mango	O
,	O
pineapple	O
,	O
and	O
cucumber	O
with	O
salt/chile/lime	O
juice	O
on	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Off	O
to	O
a	O
good	O
start	O
!	O

Seriously	O
!	O
What	O
's	O
the	O
strangest	O
Jewish	O
custom	O
you	O
can	O
think	O
of	O
?	O
RT	O
@skjask	O
Gosh	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
write	O
the	O
TOC	O
appendix&	O
the	O
footnotes	O
!	O

@rejism	O
So	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
,	O
hope	O
it	O
continues	O
to	O
inspire	O
you	O
!	O
It	O
is	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
fabulous	O
Organizers	O
!	O

@Aleitzes	O
We	O
can	O
only	O
hope	O
.	O

The	O
Duomo	O
and	O
Florence	B-PER
below	O
from	O
San	B-LOC
Miniato	I-LOC
al	B-LOC
Monte	I-LOC
.	O
http://twitpic.com/4zs0ur	O

@ravpnuty	O
such	O
a	O
sweet	O
#FF	O
!	O
thanks	O
and	O
#shabbatshalom	O

My	O
old	O
co-worker	O
@seerodrigzread	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
the	O
best	O
lunches	O
.	O
#brownbag	O

CLASSIC	O
!!	O
RT	O
@CoryBooker	B-PER
:	O
Do	O
I	O
have	O
2	O
answer	O
that	O
during	O
the	O
#superbowl	O
?	O
RT	O
@Crcolard	B-PER
:	O
How	O
does	O
Newark	B-LOC
and	O
other	O
(	O
cont	O
)	O
http://tl.gd/8lgv23	O

Did	O
y'all	O
read	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Feminist	O
Porn	O
Awards	O
2011	O
on	O
WHACK	O
today	O
?	O
http://www.whackmagazine.com	O

Excited	O
to	O
be	O
"	O
Live	O
Tweeting	O
"	O
from	O
the	O
Intrepid	O
this	O
Thursday	O
during	O
the	O
CT	O
Wolters	O
Kluwer	O
Corporate	O
Legal	O
Services	O
annual	O
customer	O
event	O
!	O

States	O
Crack	O
Down	O
on	O
Drunken	O
Boating	O
Alcohol	O
use	O
is	O
the	O
leading	O
contributor	O
in	O
fatal	O
boating	O
accidents	O
involving	O
the	O
USA	B-LOC
http://t.co/xaBuNgm	O

Foto	O
Find	O
:	O
Geohot	O
returns	O
to	O
his	O
roots	O
:	O
Hacker	O
and	O
programmer	O
George	B-PER
"	I-PER
Geohot	B-PER
"	I-PER
Hotz	I-PER
recently	O
took	O
a	O
job	O
at	O
F	O
...	O
http://aol.it/pKRaxR	O

2nd	O
day	O
in	O
a	O
row	O
without	O
coffee	O
#notanewyearsresolutionjustdoingit	O

$RIMM	O
about	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
move	O
here	O
over	O
70	O

In	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
the	O
editor	O
,	O
MSF	O
Dr	B-PER
.	I-PER
Susan	B-PER
Shepherd	I-PER
responds	O
to	O
@NickKristof	B-PER
's	I-PER
"	O
The	O
Breast	O
Milk	O
Cure	O
"	O
http://nyti.ms/oPIOIS	O
#STRVD	O

La	O
Vie	O
is	O
headed	O
to	O
Edinburgh	O
!	O
Earnhardt	B-PER
and	O
Pierce	B-PER
's	O
adaptation	O
of	O
"	O
The	O
Wind-Up	O
Bird	O
Chronicle	O
"	O
goes	O
to	O
Edinburgh	O
...	O
http://fb.me/ta6t7YpY	O

Woot	O
!	O
MT	O
@ZekeFT	O
edith	B-PER
zimmerman	I-PER
is	O
going	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
column	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
York	O
Times	O
Magazine	O
http://bit.ly/fd3sf5	O

Things	O
are	O
not	O
funny	O
here	O
but	O
profound	O
and	O
oh	O
so	O
revealing	O
into	O
the	O
content	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
still	O
no	O
ice	O
cream	O
here	O
.	O

@TheGrottoTweets	O
Thanks	O
as	O
always	O
!	O

@robinjessica	B-PER
have	O
fun	O
bowling	O
!	O
next	O
time	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
NYC	B-LOC
make	O
sure	O
you	O
check	O
out	O
our	O
lanes	O
and	O
lounge	O
~	O
www.leisuretimebowl.com	O
!!!	O

Yuck	O
!	O
Whats	O
next	O
tattoos	O
"	O
Tats	O
for	O
Tots	O
"?	O
RT	O
@BetterHalfMommy	O
Pole	O
dancing	O
class	O
for	O
infants	O
and	O
toddlers	O
??	O

Stargate	B-MISC
Universe	I-MISC
wins	O
best	O
Series	O
constellation	O
award	O
http://sns.mx/p7fpy9	O

Foresight	O
could	O
make	O
wise	O
men	O
of	O
Durraman	O
's	O
donkeys	O
.	O
-	O
Darkovan	O
Proverb	O

That	O
@CherylStrayed	B-PER
's	O
book	O
"	O
Wild	O
,"	O
coming	O
out	O
in	O
2012	O
,	O
is	O
practically	O
trending	O
on	O
Twitter	B-ORG
among	O
insiders	O
right	O
now	O
is	O
killing	O
me	O
!	O
#suspense	O

@twomomsandababy	O
welcome	O
to	O
the	O
famileebee	O
!	O
hope	O
you'll	O
become	O
a	O
facebook	B-MISC
fan	O
!	O
post	O
a	O
pic	O
and	O
comment	O
.	O
thx	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/3EFDfD	O

Apartment	O
for	O
rent	O
in	O
East	B-LOC
Village	I-LOC
.	O
1BD/1BT/$3800	O
.	O
24	O
Hr	O
doorman	O
,	O
No	O
fee	O
.	O
www.realty.mx/115a50	O

http://t.co/HHf6OwP	O
glad	O
you	O
enjoy	O
our	O
saucy	O
moments	O
@eaterny	O

How	O
@DL1961jeans	B-MISC
Gets	O
Ready	O
for	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
-	O
How	O
will	O
YOU	O
wear	O
Red	O
White	O
&	O
Blue	O
this	O
weeked	O
?	O
http://t.co/pHe16f8	O

Once	O
you	O
pass	O
the	O
bottom	O
you	O
gon	O
get	O
to	O
the	O
top/	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
lotta	O
hate	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
make	O
sure	O
that	O
you	O
watch	O
#lilb	O

How	O
the	O
disaster	O
may	O
help	O
Japan	B-LOC
's	O
brand	O
http://is.gd/oGMfPE	O
by	O
@devintstewart	B-PER

#Grossout	O
-	O
Larry	B-PER
Flint	I-PER
offering	O
Casey	B-PER
Anthony	I-PER
$	O
500,000	O
to	O
pose	O
nude	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
low	O
even	O
for	O
you	O
@HustlerMag	O

@Nerve	O
Hey	O
-	O
I'm	O
Richard	B-PER
Easton	I-PER
,	O
NYC	B-LOC
's	O
most	O
exclusive	O
matchmaker...I'm	O
also	O
a	O
guy	O
's	O
guy	O
,	O
and	O
relate	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
perspective	O
.	O
Let	O
's	O
talk	O
.	O

@WorldtoTable	O
For	O
the	O
price	O
we	O
paid	O
,	O
absolutely	O
.	O
I	O
kind	O
of	O
wish	O
they	O
had	O
bigger	O
crabs	O
,	O
but	O
our	O
platter	O
was	O
no	O
joke	O
.	O
Writeup	O
is	O
forthcoming	O
!	O

@iiadorejb07	O
@jelenasforever	O
@nourroumany	O
@pdjmoo	O
@grayhorse10	O
@look_at_meow	O
@puppynumber7	O
@lopelyr	O
@eddiechiwowwow	O
@tedd	B-PER

Sustainable	O
Innovations	O
in	O
Movement-Based	O
Education	O
.	O
http://ping.fm/dcaaL	O

@aprilmaylady	O
you	O
could	O
always	O
get	O
a	O
maid	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
:	O
)	O
...	O
once	O
I	O
get	O
back	O
to	O
work	O
I'm	O
doing	O
just	O
that	O
.	O

@culinarylibrari	O
they're	O
the	O
best	O
!!	O

#REUTERS	O
:	O
#Gaddafi	O
son	O
sees	O
negotiation	O
,	O
"	O
a	O
negotiated	O
ceasefire	O
could	O
be	O
in	O
place	O
by	O
Saturday	O
"	O
(	O
??!!!	O
)	O
#Libya	O
http://t.co/KQKQxYS	O
#Feb17	O

Great	O
new	O
timeline	O
charts	O
are	O
in	O
!	O
Export	O
them	O
,	O
interact	O
with	O
them	O
!	O
Enjoy	O
!	O
http://qoo.ly/38e	O
#socialreport	O
#socialmedia	O

@AshelynnS	B-PER
Dang	O
!	O
And	O
I	O
was	O
really	O
excited	O
about	O
using	O
"	O
moped	O
"	O
as	O
an	O
active	O
verb	O
meaning	O
"	O
to	O
give	O
one	O
grief	O
in	O
a	O
sulky	O
manner	O
."	O

Your	O
walls	O
-	O
a	O
Designer	O
's	O
Canvas	O
.	O

Have	O
you	O
visited	O
us	O
recently	O
?	O
Tell	O
us	O
what	O
you	O
loved	O
most	O
(	O
maybe	O
even	O
show	O
us	O
some	O
photos)	O
!	O
#Travel	O

This	O
Valentine	O
's	O
Day	O
,	O
show	O
your	O
love	O
by	O
supporting	O
Woodhull	O
!	O
Every	O
donation	O
goes	O
towards	O
our	O
programming	O
and	O
helps	O
...	O
http://fb.me/sWpBgeWU	O

[	O
balloons	O
]	O
http://t.co/WvimnHF	O
#photo	O
#eyeem	O
#iphoneography	O

@indymill	O
@kdrm	O
@parabasis	O
1	O
.	O
only	O
some	O
of	O
arts	O
funding	O
goes	O
to	O
"	O
unpopular	O
"	O
art	O
;	O
much	O
goes	O
to	O
make	O
art	O
accessible	O
to	O
underserved	O
populations	O

Did	O
you	O
hear	O
about	O
the	O
vampire	O
who	O
had	O
an	O
eye	O
for	O
the	O
ladies	O
?	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
back	O
pocket	O
.	O

Hey	O
@eao_explore	O
,	O
just	O
downloaded	O
@CityMint	O
and	O
look	O
forward	O
to	O
the	O
experience	O
when	O
in	O
SF	O
next	O
week	O
for	O
@adtech	O

It	O
's	O
bracket	O
time	O
!	O
Already	O
enjoying	O
talking	O
smack	O
as	O
the	O
only	O
Jayhawk	O
in	O
a	O
'	O
Cuse	O
dominated	O
office	O
.	O

NHL	B-ORG
Trade	O
Deadline	O
2011	O
Team	O
Preview	O
,	O
Part	O
Two	O
:	O
New	B-ORG
York	I-ORG
Islanders	I-ORG
-	O
Bleacherreport	O
.	O
com	O
:	O
As	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
series	O
,	O
wr	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/eNumuX	O

Newsday	O
>>	O
Practice	O
Report	O
:	O
July	O
30	O
http://buzztap.com/-4Um47l	O

Food	O
Truck	O
Event	O
NYC	B-LOC
http://t.co/alZ6dAW	O
#healthyfood	O
#healthy	O
#creative	O

@deannainlasvega	O
No	O
I	O
don't	O
use	O
protein	O
shakes	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
ever	O
advocate	O
them-	O
check	O
this	O
out	O
:	O
http://ow.ly/5eSKO	O

Spread	O
the	O
word	O
.	O
http://on.fb.me/eJjqy8	O

@Vandalyzm	O
yeah	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
dumb	O
.	O

9/11	O
Terror	O
Suspects	O
to	O
Face	O
Military	O
Tribunals	O
at	O
Gitmo	B-LOC
,	O
Report	O
Says	O
http://bit.ly/hjUfTA	O

Comments	O
From	O
Gartnerites	O
1979-1992	O
:	O
http://goo.gl/fb/T0wdE	O

Manhattan	B-LOC
Mini	O
Storage	O
has	O
my	O
ire	O
:	O
http://tumblr.com/xrx1sjq7o0	O

Have	O
to	O
laugh	O
at	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
!	O
Wackiest	O
Beauty	O
Products	O
Ever	O
http://ow.ly/2fqev	O

12	O
Hour	O
Shirt	O
Shower	O
Extravaganza	O
is	O
live	O
at	O
www.bustedtees.com	O
.	O
All	O
Shirts	O
:	O
$	O
12.99	O
,	O
All	O
Hoodies	O
:	O
$	O
24.99	O
.	O
Thru	O
12:00	O
am	O
EST	O
on	O
10/1	O
.	O
Act	O
now	O
!	O

@jusywho	B-PER
:	O
Congrats	O
on	O
winning	O
BORN	B-MISC
OF	I-MISC
SHADOWS	I-MISC
.	O
Please	O
DM	O
us	O
your	O
address	O
.	O

MLS	O
-	O
Multiple	O
Listing	O
Service	O
of	O
NYC	B-LOC
.	O
Every	O
Manhattan	B-LOC
apt	O
.	O
listing	O
.	O
No	O
Cost	O
.	O
Full	O
info	O
and	O
photos	O
.	O
http://www.listingtorch.com/	O

@pinkberry	O
has	O
a	O
buy	O
1	O
get	O
1	O
free	O
coupon	O
on	O
their	O
website	O
today	O
...	O
and	O
the	O
heavens	O
have	O
opened	O

What	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
when	O
your	O
ex	O
gets	O
out	O
of	O
jail	O
and	O
wants	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
kids	O
?	O
http://bit.ly/murLX9	O

I	O
love	O
this	O
new	O
website	O
-	O
dedicated	O
to	O
bringing	O
the	O
sexy	O
fun	O
back	O
to	O
moms	O
!	O
-	O
ad	O
http://tumblr.com/x1b2x4prg9	O

5	O
Steps	O
to	O
Improved	O
#DataSecurity	O
-	O
http://ow.ly/4L8io	O
http://ow.ly/4LZAz	O
#law	O
#lawfirm	O
#datasecurity	O
RT	O
@virtual_com	O

I'm	O
outta	O
for	O
now	O
tweeps	O
.	O
<	O
3	O

@NYsocialbee	O
//	O
awesome	O
choices	O

Bookcase	O
at	O
office	O
http://instagr.am/p/M7SN/	O

@sdevon	B-PER
you're	O
on	O
your	O
own	O
for	O
the	O
morning	O
(	O
icff+kips	O
bay	O
optional)	O
,	O
first	O
official	O
item	O
is	O
12:30	O
lunch	O
at	O
@leejofa	B-PER
at	O
the	O
D&D	O
building	O

@salsb	B-PER
That	O
's	O
amazing	O
and	O
cool	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
strong	O
feelings	O
every	O
time	O
I	O
hear	O
of	O
something	O
like	O
that	O
.	O
My	O
inner	O
7	O
year	O
old	O
gets	O
pissed	O
.	O

Yikes	O
,	O
say	O
it	O
ain't	O
so	O
RT	O
@LaJollaPatch	O
'	O
Real	O
World	O
La	O
Jolla	O
:'	O
Are	O
#MTV	O
Cameras	O
Coming	O
Back	O
to	O
San	B-LOC
Diego	I-LOC
?	O
http://aol.it/kfzC06	O

"	O
Hi	O
,	O
please	O
attempt	O
to	O
rob	O
us	O
"	O
http://sns.mx/fAduy0	O

Nuts	O
!	O
Wonder	O
how	O
many	O
takes	O
?	O
@AndrewBloch	B-PER
:	O
Great	O
film	O
to	O
promote	O
new	O
BMW	O
M1	O
:	O
"	O
BMW	O
Vs	O
.	O
Concrete	O
Walls	O
"	O
http://t.co/H6gOSOo	O
(	O
via	O
@gumball3000	O
)	O

@MomieLady	B-PER
AWESOME	O
!	O

Check	O
out	O
the	O
Howdini	O
GadgetGuru	O
Sweepstakes	O
!	O
Just	O
"	O
like	O
"	O
our	O
page	O
&	O
then	O
enter	O
for	O
a	O
chance	O
to	O
win	O
a	O
$100	O
gift	O
card	O
!	O
http://bit.ly/dQfjlX	O

Only	O
one	O
shopping	O
day	O
left	O
until	O
tomorrow	O
!	O

Watch	O
@PreventionMag	B-MISC
on	O
@todayshow	B-MISC
'	O
Makeup	O
Mistakes	O
That	O
Age	O
You	O
'	O
http://ow.ly/5DFBi	O
http://ow.ly/i/ehud	O
&	O
see	O
our	O
editors	O
before	O
filming	O
!	O

Dream	O
:	O
on	O
trip	O
w/	O
family	O
&mom	O
keeps	O
handing	O
me	O
outboard	O
motor	O
to	O
hold	O
.	O
tell	O
her	O
it	O
's	O
cutting	O
me	O
but	O
she	O
says	O
we	O
need	O
it	O
2get	O
out	O
of	O
Nebraska	B-LOC

S/o	O
to	O
@THEREALESMITTY	B-PER
on	O
the	O
follow	O
!	O
Get	O
with	O
the	O
move-mint	O
Yesssir	O
!!!	O
WE	O
here	O
!	O

Yes	O
,	O
please	O
!	O
RT	O
@poh	O
:	O
Hey	O
#NWP	O
tchrs	O
:	O
How	O
do	O
you/will	O
you	O
teach	O
about	O
9/11	O
?	O
Share	O
http://nyti.ms/pw7LrW	O
&	O
identify	O
yourself	O
as	O
#NWP	O
!	O

Internet	O
Marketing	O
Business	O
Losing	O
the	O
Battle	O
?	O
Then	O
Read	O
This	O
Article	O
Now	O
http://ping.fm/iupDZ	O

Best	O
Gchat	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
:	O
"	O
ps	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
squirrel	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
about	O
,	O
http://twitter.com/#!/common_squirrel	O
,	O
25K	O
followers	O
"	O

@tanatan245	O
yeah	O
.	O
They	O
be	O
doing	O
us	O
dirty	O
.	O

Winning	O
resume	O
tip	O
|	O
Prioritize	O
the	O
content	O
of	O
your	O
Winning	O
resume	O

Isn't	O
it	O
STUNNING	O
??	O
RT	O
@anniefitz	B-PER
:	O
The	O
beautiful	O
jewel	O
box	O
inspired	O
dining	O
room-Tiffany	O
Suite	O
,	O
St	O
.	O
Regis	O
NY	O
http://twitpic.com/5pnsdl	O

Yahoo	B-ORG
!	O
Sports	O
>>	O
Plaxico	O
and	O
the	O
Giants	O
will	O
meet	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
http://buzztap.com/-bLinxK	O

@gdowning14	O
-	O
I	O
can't	O
reveal	O
the	O
specific	O
category	O
yet	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
later	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
it	O
's	O
not	O
sports	O
related	O
.	O

@BottinoZampaNYC	O
the	O
roasted	O
turk	O
with	O
olive	O
bread	O
,	O
though	O
I've	O
heard	O
the	O
roasted	O
pork	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
next	O
one	O
I	O
try	O
.	O

@theworkroomNYC	O
you'll	O
have	O
to	O
settle	O
for	O
Van	O
Winkle	O
's	O
in	O
Hunter	O
NY	B-LOC
.	O
Great	O
burgers	O
there	O
.	O
I'll	O
settle	O
for	O
Shake	O
Shack	O

BLAP	O
NEWS	O
!!!	O
http://ih.advfn.com/p.php?pid=nmona&article=46472198	O

@EvansJudy	O
@schnuckmarkets	O
Thanks	O
Judy	B-PER
!	O
Hope	O
we	O
see	O
you	O
there	O
!	O
If	O
you	O
can	O
make	O
it	O
please	O
let	O
us	O
know	O
!	O

New	O
from	O
@NASTAD	O
:	O
Viral	O
Hepatitis	O
Advocacy	O
Toolkit	O
-	O
great	O
resource	O
[	O
PDF	O
]	O
-	O
http://ow.ly/5BJEh	O

@LTO_cambodia	O
Great	O
find	O
,	O
thanks	O
!	O
Yeah	O
,	O
I	O
recall	O
that	O
IRI	O
opinion	O
poll	O
from	O
last	O
year	O
.	O

Friday	O
Pairing	O
:	O
Moylans	O
Chelsea	O
Porter	O
with	O
Meatloaf	B-PER
-	O
http://bit.ly/aLmXUC	O
via	O
@BarleyDine	O
#craftbeer	O

Insurance	O
Leads	O
Generation	O
.	O
http://is.gd/ca11C	O

Join	O
us	O
tomorrow	O
night	O
,	O
Saturday	O
May	O
7	O
for	O
the	O
"	O
Knock	O
Ya	O
Self	O
Out	O
"	O
fight	O
and	O
after-party	O
.	O
We	O
will	O
be	O
showing	O
the	O
...	O
http://fb.me/N0Q3u9eq	O

Last	O
chance	O
to	O
get	O
free	O
US	B-LOC
shipping	O
,	O
sale	O
ends	O
tomorrow	O
morning	O
!	O
http://www.etsy.com/shop/lapoubellevintage	O

Depressing	O
,	O
yet	O
oddly	O
(	O
depressingly	O
?	O
)	O
compelling	O
:	O
"	O
Escape	O
the	O
Tedium	O
of	O
Life	O
in	O
'	O
Everyday	O
The	O
Same	O
Dream	O
'"	O
http://t.co/MmXgPJX	O
via	O
@Switched	O

@RedTornadoArt	O
thnx	O

"	O
wow	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
tired	O
from	O
all	O
that	O
blowing	O
(	O
airmattress)	O
."	O
#TWSS	O

@brianroberts44	B-PER
@blackknight76	B-PER
shhhhh	O
!	O
don't	O
let	O
jimmy	B-PER
find	O
out	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
making	O
more	O
elsewhere	O
!	O

Another	O
disease	O
eradicated	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
huge	O
.	O
http://www.nytimes.com/2010/10/16/science/16pest.html	O

Why	O
Google+	O
will	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
Sourcing	O
&	O
Recruiting	O
than	O
Facebook	O
.	O
via	O
http://t.co/mhQIYkE	O
http://t.co/4GxHqyc	O

Open	O
2011	O
:	O
Success	O
would	O
be	O
special	O
for	O
'	O
patient	O
'	O
Lee	B-PER
Westwood	I-PER
http://bit.ly/rpzxpe	O

@elandes	B-PER
funding	O
matters	O
less	O
to	O
me	O
than	O
transparent	O
methodology	O
#followreader	O

Yes	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
TRUE	O
.	O
the	O
AGING	O
of	O
HUMAN	O
CELLS	O
can	O
be	O
REVERSED	O
http://cot.ag/9mEnf2	O
#MaxLife	O

Homeless	O
at	O
14	O
to	O
Fashion	O
Week	O
in	O
NYC	O
.	O
Special	O
screening	O
of	O
@DressedtheMovie	O
by	O
@FGINYC	O
and	O
@LIMCollege	O
on	O
June	O
2nd	O
http://ow.ly/4Ri2s	O

Parents	O
,	O
Kids	O
and	O
Social	O
Media	O
http://bit.ly/poq2Pb	O

GIRL	O
TALK	O
RELEASES	O
NYE	O
CHICAGO	B-LOC
DOCUMENTARY	O
http://bit.ly/bVbbNP	O

More	O
than	O
100	O
Advocates	O
Thinking	O
Big	O
About	O
Second	O
Annual	O
Small	O
Business	O
...	O
-	O
MarketWatch	O
(	O
press	O
release	O
)	O
http://sns.mx/Vzeky5	O

why	O
does	O
yale	O
always	O
lose	O
at	O
football	O
?	O

Best	O
Student	O
Checking	O
Accounts	O
http://aol.it/ex8fQn	O

Some	O
advice	O
for	O
those	O
looking	O
to	O
start	O
their	O
own	O
photography	O
business	O
http://thephotoletariat.com/creating-your-own-photography-business	O

"	O
STYLE	O
SYLLABUS	O
"	O
SUBJECTS	O
OF	O
THE	O
DAY	O
:	O
Fab	O
Read	O
"	O
RED	O
"	O
(	O
assoulinepub	O
)	O
"	O
by	O
Stephanie	B-PER
Busuttil	I-PER
:	O
http://bit.ly/j0rM6M	O

Will	O
never	O
forget	O
GMpalooza	O
!	O
Great	O
conference	O
,	O
thank	O
you	O
Marriott	O
!	O
http://yfrog.com/gyas3hrj	O

@GlamandGraceWed	B-PER
Love	O
mentions	O
from	O
our	O
fans	O
.	O
Thanks	O
so	O
much	O
!	O
Bridesview	O
.	O
com	O
@TheBridesView	O

Researchers	O
sequence	O
the	O
genome	O
of	O
prostate	O
cancer	O
,	O
a	O
step	O
toward	O
identifying	O
aggressive	O
tumors	O
-	O
..	O
http://lat.ms/hD11t6	O

A	O
chance	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
pick	O
the	O
Hunger	O
Games	O
fandom	O
name	O
.	O
Will	O
it	O
be	O
MOCKINGJAYS	O
or	O
TRIBUTES	O
?	O
via	O
@crushable	O
http://t.co/wbIZIXG	O

"	O
I	O
feel	O
so	O
sorry	O
for	O
all	O
those	O
people	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
other	O
movies	O
."	O
-	O
my	O
sister	O
#deathlyhallows	O

Running	O
a	O
Robust	O
#HR	O
Shared	O
Services	O
Center	O
of	O
Excellence	O
http://bit.ly/l2PcAe	O
#HRIQ	O
#Podcast	O

What	O
brands	O
can	O
learn	O
from	O
Transformers	B-MISC
.	O
#notdecepticons	O
#orautobots	O
http://ow.ly/4VvNO	O

Cadwalader	O
Restructuring	O
Review	O
,	O
June	O
2010	O
http://bit.ly/oYyJD0	O

Just	O
posted	O
a	O
photo	O
http://instagr.am/p/GWmJ7/	O

Harry	B-PER
potter	I-PER
was	O
Realllly	O
good	O
!	O
Sad	O
tho	O
that	O
an	O
era	O
has	O
endeed	O
:(	O

Buzz	O
Killer	O
:	O
Special	O
Smells	O
Keep	O
Mosquitoes	O
at	O
Bay	O
|	O
Mosquitoes	O
,	O
Bites	O
&	O
Infection	O
|	O
LiveScience	O
http://fb.me/11b9olGth	O

@hmbscully	O
@DiscJockeyEtc	O
I	O
got	O
some	O
salmon	O
from	O
Seattle	B-LOC
last	O
September	O
!	O
Haha	O
I	O
could	O
play	O
this	O
game	O
all	O
day	O
.	O

HIVE	O
5	O
:	O
Patrick	O
Carney	O
's	O
(@patrickcarney	O
of	O
the	O
@theblackkeyss	O
)	O
Multiple	O
Twitter	B-ORG
Personalities	O
http://bit.ly/kow3dH	O

I	O
am	O
excited	O
for	O
today	O
's	O
journalism	O
reunion	O
to	O
kick	O
off	O
three	O
full	O
weeks	O
of	O
papers	O
.	O

Body	O
as	O
canvas	O
and	O
every	O
frame	O
a	O
beauty	O
.	O
Love	O
Daphne	B-PER
Guinness	I-PER
Gets	O
"	O
Undressed	O
"	O
for	O
@nowness	O
http://bit.ly/kF5QnN	O
@TheRealDaphne	O

Good	O
morning	O
!	O
Our	O
managing	O
editor	O
@jon_fitzgerald	O
has	O
a	O
post	O
up	O
at	O
@HuffPostRelig	O
about	O
the	O
future	O
of	O
evangelicalism	O
:	O
http://huff.to/dwChYj	O

Announcing	O
Private	O
Alpha	O
Release	O
of	O
dorthy.com	B-PER
http://bit.ly/P8Icg	O

I	O
just	O
became	O
the	O
mayor	O
of	O
Mediterranean	O
Grill	O
on	O
@foursquare	O
!	O
http://4sq.com/7nQKaB	O

BEYONCE	B-PER
KICKS	O
SOME	O
ASS	O
IN	O
THE	O
VID	O
FOR	O
RUN	O
THE	O
WORLD	O
(	O
GIRLS)	O
.	O
WATCH	O
.	O
#beyonce	O
#gay	O
#runtheworldgirls	O
#jay-z	O
http://bit.ly/l2V3oX	O

Brief	O
rundown	O
of	O
new	O
social	O
engagement	O
reporting	O
within	O
Google	B-ORG
Analytics	I-ORG
http://selnd.com/mVWC8v	O

Howdy	O
to	O
all	O
of	O
our	O
new	O
followers	O
!!	O

Art	O
of	O
the	O
Strip	O
Tease	O
is	O
happening	O
tonight	O
at	O
9pm	O
(	O
est)	O
.	O
Get	O
inspired	O
to	O
bump	O
&	O
grind	O
for	O
stage	O
and/or	O
bedroom	O
!	O
http://t.co/npU5IcY	O

@CJKoegelMTV	B-PER
Hey	O
CJ	B-PER
!	O
It	O
was	O
nice	O
to	O
meet	O
you	O
last	O
night	O
at	O
Gia	B-PER
's	O
Record	O
Release	O
Party	O
:)	O

@TomMcFeeley	B-PER
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
.	O

Great	O
minds	O
think	O
a	O
like	O
lol'sRT	O
@Jrick23	B-PER
:	O
@HStyless	B-PER
Do	O
half	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
Haha	O
!	O

Reading	O
a	O
yahoo	O
news	O
article	O
where	O
a	O
bentley	B-MISC
,	O
ferrari	B-MISC
,	O
Porsche	O
,	O
Mercedes	B-MISC
and	O
Aston	B-MISC
Martin	I-MISC
all	O
smashed	O
into	O
each	O
other	O
in	O
Spain	B-LOC
in	O
one	O
lot	O

Tip	O
for	O
the	O
Hundred	O
:	O
Imagine	O
you're	O
pumping	O
your	O
arms	O
against	O
the	O
resistance	O
of	O
water	O
.	O
Engage	O
those	O
lats	O
!	O

Gym	O
at	O
8	O
pm	O
...	O

Guy	B-PER
Chiarello	I-PER
Chief	O
Information	O
Officer	O
at	O
JPMorgan	O
Chase	O
http://t.co/Kamlzhf	O

@fusionrocks	O
Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
#FF	O
!	O

Breaking	O
#fashionpolice	B-MISC
news	O
:	O
finally	O
caught	O
a	O
teen	O
boy	O
forced	O
to	O
actually	O
pull	O
up	O
pants	O
that	O
had	O
dropped	O
so	O
low	O
he	O
could	O
no	O
longer	O
walk	O
.	O

Download	O
pdf	O
Handbook	O
of	O
Herbs	O
and	O
Spices	O
ebook	O
-	O
NBA	O
JAM	O
Off	O
...:	O
Download	O
Handbook	O
of	O
Herbs	O
and	O
Spices	O
ebook	O
p	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/kYBWaz	O

@CCThePR	O
Thank	O
you	O
!	O

say	O
ah	O
!	O
Whale	O
shark	O
almost	O
sucks	O
diver	O
http://yhoo.it/p4vmNv	O
#photography	O
#diving	O
#snorkeling	O

Escape	O
To	O
The	O
Caribbean	O
With	O
Your	O
Own	O
Jerk	O
Seasoning	O
http://bit.ly/h4ad58	O

glad	O
you're	O
enjoying	O
it	O
!	O
RT	O
@writemeg	O
Halfway	O
through	O
Lindsey	B-PER
Kelk	I-PER
's	O
I	O
HEART	O
NEW	B-LOC
YORK	I-LOC
and	O
digging	O
it	O
.	O

My	O
Princess	O
Boy	O
Giveaway	O
going	O
on	O
on	O
awesome	O
mommyblog	O
,	O
The	O
Lindsay	O
List	O
:	O
Win	O
a	O
free	O
signed	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
book	O
!	O
http://tinyurl.com/4ogmbha	O

http://t.co/jgY7VqL	O

@momfinds	O
thanks	O
!!	O
xo	O

#HR	O
#Shared	O
#Services	O
:	O
Making	O
Strategic	O
Players	O
Out	O
Of	O
Generalists	O
http://bit.ly/jJ70MO	O
#HRIQ	O
#Article	O

finally	O
testing	O
Gwibber	B-MISC
in	O
Ubutu	B-ORG
10.04	O

@lace_5	O
yes	O
I've	O
seen	O
it	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
happens	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
?	O

Skopemag	O
.	O
com	O
put	O
Billion	O
's	O
"	O
whippin	O
'	O
that	O
"	O
video	O
in	O
rotation	O
.	O
Thanks	O
Mike	B-PER
!	O

Massive	O
Quake	O
,	O
Tsunami	O
Strike	O
Japan	B-LOC
-	O
Updated	O
from	O
4:18	O
a.m.	O
EST	O
TOKYO	O
(	O
TheStreet	O
)	O
--	O
A	O
massive	O
earthquake	O
,	O
the	O
...	O
http://ow.ly/1bIply	O

#ContinuousGrindin	O

Food	O
Photography	O
Tips	O
http://bit.ly/5gbSy1	O

Law	O
enforcement	O
setting	O
up	O
extra	O
patrols	O
for	O
holiday	O
weekend	O
-	O
Springfield	B-LOC
News	O
Sun	O
http://ow.ly/15GHZD	O

New	O
minipost	O
:	O
Why	O
do	O
we	O
have	O
sleep	O
?	O
Why	O
can't	O
we	O
just	O
always	O
kee	O
http://ow.ly/19WHuQ	O

Local	O
Mobile	O
Ads	O
Drive	O
Mobile	O
Shopping	O
:	O
Study	O
http://dld.bz/MRqb	O
#in	O

@FeKaulitz_483	O
Follow	O
me	O
please	O
!	O
:)	O
http://ericktheblogger.tumblr.com/	O

Your	O
Mysterious	O
Bookshop	O
staff	O
for	O
Sunday	O
12/19/10	O
is	O
Dan	B-PER
and	O
Chris	B-PER
!	O

Check	O
out	O
our	O
latest	O
blog	O
post	O
:	O
Little	O
Things	O
Make	O
a	O
Big	O
Difference	O
:	O
http://ow.ly/41ROu	O

Today	O
's	O
the	O
day	O
!	O
We	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
winner	O
of	O
the	O
Big	O
Apple	O
ticket	O
!	O
Thanks	O
to	O
everyone	O
for	O
tweeting	O
.	O
Stay	O
tuned	O
.	O

#moms	B-MISC
#kids	B-MISC
#music	B-MISC
#homeschoolers	O
#preschoolers	O
#education	O
Speaking	O
the	O
Language	O
of	O
Music	O
http://bit.ly/h8hAYK	O

Last	O
week	O
we	O
announced	O
that	O
the	O
2010	O
Hey	O
,	O
Hot	O
Shot	O
!	O
Ne	O
Plus	O
Ultra	O
(&	O
winner	O
of	O
our	O
$10K	O
honorarium	O
)	O
is	O
Chikara	B-PER
Umihara	I-PER
.	O
Congrats	O
Chikara	B-PER
!	O

@keith_stewart	B-PER
Likewise	O
.	O
Smh	O
.	O

@fifthand56th	O
heat	O
wraps	O
are	O
the	O
only	O
thing	O
that	O
help	O
me	O
...	O
ice	O
has	O
only	O
helped	O
warm	O
soda	O
cool	O
off	O
;-)	O

Wow	O
.	O
Just	O
started	O
using	O
@teuxdeux	O
&	O
feel	O
like	O
I've	O
found	O
the	O
holy	O
grail	O
of	O
lifehacking	O
lists	O
.	O
Simple	O
+	O
elegant	O
=	O
win	O
#productivitynerd	O

$20	O
for	O
$40	O
Worth	O
of	O
Bar	O
Eats	O
and	O
Drinks	O
at	O
Traffic	O
Restaurant	O
&	O
Bar	O
-	O
http://t.co/zILUz44	O

Healthy	O
Diet	O
|	O
Tevez	B-PER
:	O
Prince	O
Of	O
The	O
Blue	O
Moan	O
http://dlvr.it/cfm3m	O

Theres	O
a	O
neighborhood	O
for	O
every	O
race	O
in	O
New	B-LOC
York	I-LOC
.	O
#	O
Gotta	O
love	O
it	O
.	O

#TeamStarrSimplicity	O
shooting	O
with	O
@iam_MORELLE	B-PER
I'm	O
LOVING	O
how	O
this	O
looks	O
>>>	O
#PyeYow	O
!	O

If	O
you	O
need	O
drops	O
or	O
interview	O
send	O
to	O
guru	O
.	O
promo	O
(	O
at	O
)	O
gmail	O
(	O
dot	O
)	O
com	O

Can	O
we	O
make	O
a	O
range	O
hood	O
only	O
1.5	O
"	O
thick	O
?	O
YES	O
WE	O
CAN	O
!	O
http://www.futurofuturo.com/island-rangehood-Streamline_White-36inch.php	O

CLUE	O
:	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
Spike	B-ORG
TV	I-ORG
(	O
3	O
letters	O
)	O
ANSWER	O
:	O
TNN	O

"	O
Why	O
Twitter	O
Inc	O
.	O
Loves	O
Charlie	B-PER
Sheen	I-PER
"	O
http://t.co/IXGSWrC	O
via	O
@simplymeasured	O

Hey	O
BEA-ers	O
!	O
First	O
5	O
people	O
to	O
mention	O
Twitter	B-ORG
at	O
the	O
booth	O
(	O
4148	O
)	O
win	O
a	O
free	O
copy	O
of	O
@pwhny	B-PER
'	O
s	O
Companion	O
to	O
the	O
Lit	O
of	O
NY	O
#bea10	O
#bea2010	O

in	O
New	B-ORG
York	I-ORG
Sports	B-ORG
Clubs	I-ORG
http://loopt.us/PWt0Wg.t	O

Decorative	O
Box	O
!!	O

Black	O
Bird	O
Fly	O
...	O
you	O
were	O
only	O
waiting	O
for	O
this	O
moment	O
to	O
arrive	O
...	O

Facebook	B-ORG
Pages	O
Can	O
Now	O
Be	O
Personalized	O
Based	O
on	O
Klout	O
Score	O
http://t.co/q9PgYho	O
via	O
@mashsocialmedia	B-MISC
@mashable	O

@wonkeydonkey42	B-PER
for	O
sure	O
,	O
emailing	O
you	O
now	O

Don't	O
miss	O
the	O
Wearable	O
Collections	O
profile	O
on	O
Anderson	B-PER
Cooper	I-PER
360°	O
on	O
Sept	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
They're	O
our	O
UWS	O
recycling	O
heroes	O
.	O
http://ow.ly/2xrNr	O

Be	O
sure	O
and	O
check	O
out	O
our	O
blog	O
for	O
some	O
great	O
photography	O
tips	O
http://bit.ly/cTgEvs	O

@dzalcman	O
I'm	O
laughing	O
because	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
researchers	O
--	O
Fulbrighters	O
or	O
not	O
--	O
here	O
in	O
DF	B-LOC
have	O
the	O
same	O
local	O
cell	O
as	O
well	O
.	O
Abrazos	O
!	O

@jniehof	O
thanks	O
!	O

@JaredCohen	B-PER
Congratulations	O
!	O

New	B-ORG
York	I-ORG
Times	I-ORG
Still	O
on	O
Anti-Graffiti	O
Kick	O
With	O
Dumbass	O
Article	O
http://zah.cc/nUJ	O

@phi162	B-PER
Yes	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
almost	O
there	O
,	O
congrats	O
!	O
:)	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
plan	O
,	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
PCPC	O
when	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
Philly	B-LOC
(	O
Street	O
admin)	O
.	O
Happy	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
!:	O
)	O

Patty	B-PER
Griffin	I-PER
...	O
Let	O
him	O
Fly	O
...	O
beautiful	O
http://fb.me/ShBw7hFM	O

You're	O
a	O
mom	O
and	O
you've	O
got	O
a	O
family	O
to	O
feed	O
.	O
May	O
we	O
be	O
of	O
assistance	O
?	O
http://dld.bz/Bq5q	O

8th	O
Inning	O
,	O
Phi	O
8	O
,	O
NYM	O
2	O

Station	O
Casinos	O
scales	O
back	O
free	O
live	O
entertainment	O
http://bit.ly/4zJmjY	O

@deconstructive	O
.	O
do	O
you	O
buy	O
it	O
or	O
no	O
?	O
what	O
does	O
dramatic	O
texts	O
mean	O
to	O
you	O
?	O

Ewww	O
.	O
Have	O
some	O
self-respect	O
,	O
ladies	O
.	O
"'	O
Slut	O
walk	O
'	O
women	O
are	O
simply	O
fighting	O
for	O
their	O
right	O
to	O
be	O
dirty	O
"	O
http://t.co/pSHYHyX	O
via	O
@Telegraph	O

@garygold23	B-PER
i've	O
tried	O
BR	O
,	O
but	O
can't	O
figure	O
out	O
how	O
to	O
parse	O
out	O
splits	O
from	O
the	O
Game	O
Logs	O
...	O
any	O
suggestions	O
?	O

Dealing	O
with	O
Failure	O
:	O
Felix	B-PER
Rohatyn	I-PER
and	O
the	O
lessons	O
of	O
Gotham	B-LOC
's	O
seventies	O
bankruptcy	O
crisis	O
for	O
today	O
:	O
By	O
Nicole	B-PER
...	O
http://bit.ly/gieiV9	O

"	O
I	O
would	O
like	O
to	O
sincerely	O
thank	O
all	O
those	O
who	O
have	O
spoken	O
out	O
and	O
taken	O
action	O
against	O
the	O
most	O
recent	O
attempt	O
to	O
defame	O
me	O
."	O
~MJ	B-PER
(	O
2004	O
)	O

I	O
have	O
to	O
get	O
creative	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
think	O
.	O
#sxse	O
@gopalo	O
@vicequeenmaria	O
@LoreLama	O
@beagarcia	O
@MiamiJorge	O
@mklopez	O

@kevinbe1	B-PER
Hah	O
!	O
We	O
think	O
you'll	O
all	O
love	O
it	O
:)	O
#timetoplaylive	O

OMG	O
!	O
Really	O
?	O
But	O
Gokey	B-PER
sucked	O
ass	O
!	O
(	O
And	O
not	O
in	O
that	O
good	O
way	O
!	O
)	O

Some	O
history	O
of	O
the	O
High	O
Line	O
with	O
it	O
's	O
curator	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/hDMzxS	O
http://fb.me/HIj2eETK	O

Sexual	O
Relationships	O
Always	O
Consist	O
of	O
'	O
Leftovers':	O
http://bit.ly/iyvFRA	O
(#Psychology	B-MISC
Today	I-MISC
)	O

Beet	O
Juice	O
-	O
Why	O
You	O
Should	O
Be	O
Drinking	O
It	O
http://bit.ly/lgP6lS	O

Ready	O
to	O
save	O
up	O
to	O
80%	O
off	O
your	O
favorite	O
yoga	O
brands	O
?	O
Sign	O
up	O
at	O
http	O
:/	O
www.yogafinds.com	O
to	O
get	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
sale	O
on	O
May	O
3rd	O

Save	O
Up	O
To	O
40%	O
on	O
Barbecue	O
Grills	O
http://sho.me/Lj/fy	O

Troves	O
of	O
lithium	O
,	O
valuable	O
for	O
batteries	O
,	O
boost	O
mood	O
in	O
Bolivia	B-LOC
and	O
Afghanistan	B-LOC
-	O
http://is.gd/eQb5G	O

Remembering	O
photographer	O
Robert	B-PER
Mapplethorpe	I-PER
.	O
Left	O
us	O
March	O
9	O
,	O
1989	O
.	O
Biography	O
-	O
http://bit.ly/eIsKtU	O
RT	O
@AntiquePhoto	O
@Guggenheim	O

Rainy	O
days	O
make	O
me	O
want	O
to	O
hide	O
behind	O
a	O
book	O
,	O
preferably	O
one	O
set	O
somewhere	O
tropical	O
.	O

got	O
an	O
extra	O
$180k	O
lying	O
around	O
?	O
ICANN	O
's	O
new	O
ruling	O
can	O
get	O
you	O
a	O
dot-your	O
namehere	O
domain	O
name	O
for	O
a	O
low	O
low	O
price	O
http://n.pr/l5q9df	O

NYPD	B-ORG
Once	O
Again	O
Dumps	O
Police	O
Documents	O
in	O
Public	O
Trashcan	O
http://bit.ly/nogBGE	O

Once	O
you	O
choose	O
hope	O
,	O
anything	O
's	O
possible	O
.	O
-	O
Christopher	B-PER
Reeve	I-PER
-	O
Vote	O
4	O
EverGift	O
at	O
http://pep.si/b3EZJd	O

AdoramaTV	B-ORG
:	O
@jmarkwallace	O
reviews	O
JuicedLink	B-MISC
DT454	I-MISC
,	O
a	O
4-channel	O
DSLR	O
preamp/AGC	O
disabler	O
.	O
http://cot.ag/grinJ3	O

am	O
i	O
tripping	O
?	O
#phish	O

@saraivry	O
Terry	B-PER
Castle	I-PER
seems	O
crazy	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
But	O
yet	O
,	O
I	O
love	O
reading	O
every	O
word	O
.	O

Guess	O
what	O
?	O
when	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
networking	O
event	O
you	O
are	O
there	O
to	O
meet	O
new	O
ppl	O
not	O
huddle	O
in	O
a	O
group	O
of	O
folks	O
you	O
know	O
.	O
Just	O
sayin'.	O

Self	O
tanner	O
that	O
gets	O
you	O
wedding	O
ready	O
with	O
a	O
sun	O
kissed	O
glow	O
:	O
Bliss	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
air	O
as	O
wedding	O
season	O
commences	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/eXeNUC	O

@MarriageFire	O
@CatholicMomVA	O
Thanks	O
for	O
RT	O
!	O

Need	O
video	O
production/editing	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
professional	O
online	O
commercial	O
?	O
We	O
can	O
help	O
...	O
http://is.gd/4xHcE	O

I'm	O
at	O
MCO	O
Orlando	O
International	O
in	O
Orlando	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
FL	I-LOC
http://gowal.la/c/4Eifz	O

"	O
Knewton	O
is	O
as	O
Good	O
As	O
Advertised	O
!"	O
http://bit.ly/fjlkS4	O
Always	O
great	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
our	O
customers	O
.	O
Thanks	O
Roland	B-PER
!	O

$$	O
8	O
Large-Cap	O
Dividend	O
Stocks	O
With	O
Excellent	O
Dividend	O
Trends	O
-	O
Seeking	O
Alpha	O
http://bit.ly/qUKnA6	O

Happy	O
place	O
http://twitpic.com/4p8gf4	O

Change	O
Is	O
A	O
Constant	O
:	O
Embrace	O
It	O
And	O
Love	O
It	O
,	O
Or	O
Leave	O
http://sofre.sh/Qd	O

@worrierblog	O
We	O
hope	O
you	O
enjoy	O
it	O
!	O

Hmm	O
..	O
Could	O
today	O
be	O
a	O
more	O
perfect	O
day	O
for	O
Ice	O
Cream	O
??	O
http://bit.ly/dqLPxo	O
#saveonicecream	O

Yes	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
girl	O
.	O
Yes	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
(@	O
Splash	O
Bar	O
w/	O
@djjrocnyc	O
@newyorker85	O
@erickinnyc	O
@themarsh10	O
@lsmael	O
)	O
http://4sq.com/oX9eIU	O

Good	O
hanging	O
out	O
last	O
night-hope	O
to	O
see	O
ya	O
both	O
soon	O
.	O
Wise-sorry	O
for	O
the	O
"	O
Irish	O
"	O
goodbye	O
man-I'm	O
not	O
even	O
Irish	O
.	O
@clutch_22	O
@onegreatseason	O

@meoskop	O
the	O
basic	O
thought	O
is	O
that	O
2,500	O
books	O
represents	O
many	O
years	O
'	O
consumption	O
;	O
acquisition	O
(	O
piracy	O
)	O
probably	O
signals	O
something	O

Charming	O
Shoppes	O
Inc	O
.,	O
owner	O
of	O
Lane	B-ORG
Bryant	I-ORG
,	O
exploring	O
sale	O
of	O
Fashion	O
Bug	O
that	O
operates	O
740	O
stores	O
http://tinyurl.com/3d98q5m	O
(	O
Bloomberg	O
)	O

Lol	O
so	O
true	O
.	O
RT	O
@corinneam	O
:	O
@AmandaPearly	B-PER
Absolutely	O
-	O
and	O
on	O
hairy	O
male	O
feet	O
?!	O
Blech	O
.	O

@zephoria	B-PER
pump	O
up	O
the	O
volume	O
.	O
hands	O
down	O
.	O
i	O
win	O
.	O
i'll	O
take	O
what	O
's	O
behind	O
door	O
number	O
three	O
...	O

what	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
your	O
dad	O
for	O
Father	O
's	O
Day	O
?	O

Today	O
is	O
trying	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Terrible	O
,	O
Horrible	O
,	O
No	O
Good	O
,	O
Very	O
Bad	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
stay	O
happy	O
and	O
sunshiney	O
,	O
damn	O
it	O
!	O

NYC	B-LOC
will	O
welcome	O
a	O
Museum	O
of	O
Mathematics	O
next	O
fall	O
!	O
(@NicoleBranigan	B-PER
we	O
are	O
so	O
bringing	O
our	O
pops	O
)	O
http://bit.ly/hrGVTr	O

@Ultada	B-PER
I	O
would	O
trade	O
all	O
of	O
that	O
for	O
respectability	O
.	O

@NiamhHughes	B-PER
I	O
haven't	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
RSA	O
event	O
yet	O
!	O
Did	O
I	O
miss	O
the	O
email	O
?	O

My	O
new	O
cut	O
and	O
style	O
by	O
@mfsalon	O
#NYC	O
http://lockerz.com/s/124254594	O

@ABC	O
News	O
National	O
:	O
Salaries	O
of	O
Top	O
American	O
Executives	O
Increased	O
in	O
2010	O
http://abcn.ws/l5Jb9Y	O

Punching	O
Back	O
Twice	O
As	O
Hard	O
-	O
http://is.gd/kx7q2	O
#TCOT	O
#TLOT	O
#GOP	O
#teaparty	O
#Tucson	B-LOC
#Giffords	O
#Loughner	O
#Palin	O

How	O
to	O
Make	O
Salsa	O
http://bit.ly/nj0Y2c	O
.	O

10	O
Quickest	O
Ways	O
to	O
Turn	O
a	O
Guy	O
Off	O
-	O
Lifestyle	O
News	O
-	O
StyleCaster	O
http://ow.ly/1qCamV	O

Jan	O
6th	O
,	O
Love	O
and	O
Love	O
and	O
Licenses	O
:	O
From	O
gay	O
marriage	O
to	O
border	O
passes	O
,	O
two	O
plays	O
about	O
finding	O
love	O
and	O
controlling	O
it	O
.	O
http://ow.ly/OHsl	O

@habarb	O
Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
write	O
up	O
and	O
congrats	O
on	O
your	O
recognition	O
!	O
Ever	O
thought	O
of	O
hosting	O
a	O
@BenchleySociety	O
event	O
at	O
The	O
Algonquin	O
?	O

Drugs	O
That	O
Increase	O
Risk	O
of	O
High-Grade	O
Prostate	O
Cancer	O
in	O
Men-	O
http://t.co/l5BX6fd	O

BLAP	O
bid	O
37	O
ask	O
39	O
!!	O

I	O
just	O
voted	O
for	O
Zachary	B-PER
&	O
you	O
should	O
too	O
because	O
he	O
's	O
hot	O
and	O
Scottish	O
&	O
I	O
refuse	O
to	O
believe	O
he	O
's	O
fictional	O
:	O
http://t.co/dTB6vMh	O

Oceans	O
first	O
...	O
we	O
are	O
next	O
!	O
http://fb.me/sOOkVi7M	O

Freedom	O
is	O
just	O
not	O
our	O
choice	O
of	O
religion	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
prison	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
our	O
government	O
allows	O
us	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Freedom	O
is	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
mind	O
.	O

Seems	O
like	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
time	O
as	O
any	O
to	O
open	O
this	O
bad	O
boy	O
http://lockerz.com/s/121240614	O
#Whiskey	O

Magnitude-	O
6.4	O
earthquake	O
hits	O
off	O
Japan	B-LOC
http://sns.mx/9Rely4	O

@ADCookArt	O
Nice	O
work	O
!	O
Do	O
it	O
again	O
tomorrow	O
!	O

An	O
all-new	O
www.sarahsloboda.com	O
will	O
be	O
launching	O
this	O
month	O
!	O
Keep	O
your	O
eyes	O
peeled	O
.	O

@kelleylmoore	O
Well	O
make	O
sure	O
to	O
send	O
pics	O
for	O
our	O
facebook	B-ORG
page	O
when	O
you	O
are	O
all	O
done	O
!	O

S/O	O
TO	O
the	O
Sexy	O
@NikkiBruno	B-PER
Follow	O
Her	O
<<<	O
She	O
doing	O
the	O
damn	O
thing	O
and	O
loving	O
her	O
Life	O
too	O
!!!	O

From	O
the	O
YOUnique	O
archives	O
:	O
What	O
's	O
ON	O
:	O
Issue	O
49	O
http://bit.ly/faBwFo	O

Oy	O
.	O
RT	O
-	O
@popeater	O
The	O
fight	O
begins	O
over	O
Elizabeth	B-PER
Taylor	I-PER
's	O
fortune	O
http://aol.it/i9Y7ze	O

chevron	O
everywhere	O
!	O
@camillestyles	O
I	O
say	O
zig	O
...	O
you	O
say	O
zag	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/ljGjut	O

McCain	B-PER
,	O
Kerry	B-PER
to	O
introduce	O
privacy	O
'	O
bill	O
of	O
rights	O
'	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
latest	O
salvo	O
of	O
the	O
hot-button	O
information	O
privacy	O
issu	O
...	O
http://ow.ly/1c8ITW	O

We'll	O
cut	O
away	O
from	O
NASA	B-ORG
at	O
approximately	O
11:00	O
amET	O
due	O
to	O
a	O
special	O
report	O
with	O
President	O
Obama	O
holding	O
a	O
news	O
conference	O
regarding	O
debt	O
.	O

It	O
really	O
is	O
mysterious	O
when	O
a	O
certain	O
blog	O
post	O
gets	O
WAY	O
more	O
visits	O
and	O
hits	O
than	O
others	O
.	O
Braised	O
chicken	O
thighs	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
thought	O

Check	O
out	O
@GalleyCat	O
's	O
guide	O
to	O
how	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
job	O
in	O
publishing	O
at	O
#BEA11	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/lC2GAw	O
Anything	O
you	O
would	O
add	O
?	O
#YPG	O

And	O
also	O
our	O
thanks	O
to	O
@HBO	O
.	O
Their	O
amazing	O
@gameofthrones	B-MISC
has	O
brought	O
new	O
readers	O
to	O
series	O
and	O
boosted	O
sales	O
.	O
#GRRM	O

ABI	O
:	O
Lanzan	O
primera	O
feria	O
educativa	O
e	O
informativa	O
de	O
la	O
#quinua	O
orgánica	O
http://is.gd/HVHKy6	O
#alimentos	O
#agricultura	B-MISC
#ONU	O
#Bolivia	O

Good	O
news	O
!	O
A	O
little	O
bird	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
#HBS	B-MISC
is	O
no	O
longer	O
youth-obsessed	O
!	O
#MBA	B-MISC

oh	O
:(	O
Got	O
my	O
hopes	O
up	O
!	O
RT	O
@centralparktc	O
:	O
Lady	B-PER
Gaga	I-PER
to	O
appear	O
at	O
the	O
CPTC	O
benefit	O
auction	O
tonight	O
!	O
JK	O
,	O
but	O
Khalid	B-PER
Khannouchi	I-PER
will	O
be	O
there	O
!	O

Wheels	O
up	O
to	O
Chennai	B-LOC
via	O
Frankfurt	B-LOC
...	O
With	O
hopes	O
of	O
sleep	O
.	O
Goodnight	O
,	O
my	O
friends	O
.	O
Hug	O
those	O
you	O
love	O
tight	O
.	O

#FF	O
#wine	O
@WineSpectator	O
@WineSpectator	O
@WineEnthusiast	O
@winetrends	O
@Wine_n_Waves	O
@WolfferWine	O
@raelinn_wine	O
@LIWineCountry	O
@SlateWine	O

Boobs	O
!	O

Still	O
can't	O
believe	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
husband	O
at	O
beatrice	O
,	O
especially	O
since	O
we're	O
not	O
hipsters	O
,	O
socialites	O
or	O
celebs	O
http://bit.ly/9cKfp0	O

LOVE	O
them	O
too	O
!	O
Have	O
been	O
a	O
loyal	O
customer	O
for	O
3+	O
yrs	O
.	O
RT	O
@looklingerlove	B-PER
:	O
@giggle	B-PER
just	O
found	O
you	O
through	O
@ChicCheapNrsery	O
,	O
Love	O
your	O
site	O
!	O

@JohnFitzBoston	B-PER
Nice	O
!	O
Enjoy	O
what	O
's	O
left	O
of	O
your	O
trip	O
.	O
When	O
are	O
you	O
heading	O
back	O
?	O

@katiestars	O
they	O
have	O
little	O
taste	O
-	O
I	O
like	O
them	O

Documentary	O
fans	O
:	O
what	O
(	O
not	O
)	O
to	O
doc	O
:	O
On	O
DVD	O
:	O
THE	O
SOUND	O
OF	O
INSECTS	O
:	O
http://wp.me/pYCKd-CH	O

#tech	O
iPad	O
Isn't	O
Mobile	O
:	O
Google	O
Docs	O
Desktop	O
Site	O
Works	O
Fine	O
http://ow.ly/1aongW	O

Movie	O
Review	O
:	O
'	O
Another	O
Earth	O
'	O
|	O
http://su.pr/2NMud8	O

@Quence	B-PER
I	O
recommend	O
it	O
!	O
been	O
playing	O
for	O
about	O
1/2	O
hr	O
.	O
it	O
's	O
totally	O
worth	O
ten	O
bucks	O
.	O

#ff	O
@GorgeousPR	O
@neverassumeprod	O
@EastVillageNY	O
@jlanz79	B-PER
@publicAssembly	O
@clairelondon	B-PER
@emilyzuzik	B-PER
@bust_magazine	O
@mistyboyce	B-PER
@lisajaeggi	B-PER

Real	O
Capital	O
Rewind	O
for	O
Q1'11	O
is	O
now	O
available	O
on	O
http://bit.ly/mxMPdu	O

High	O
Road	O
NYC	B-LOC
Restaurants	O
Con't:	O
All	O
Danny	B-PER
Meyer	I-PER
,	O
Cowgirl	B-PER
,	O
Annisa	B-PER
...	O
http://ow.ly/2SsMA	O

New	O
article	O
:	O
Forest	O
Green	O
vs	O
Bristol	O
City	O
live	O
HD	O
quality	O
sports	O
video	O
here	O
:	O
Welcome	O
to	O
watch	O
and	O
enjoy	O
Friendly	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/rn23sJ	O

"	O
@productpasha	O
&	O
I	O
posing	O
like	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
high	O
school	O
kids	O
in	O
front	O
of	O
a	O
Zarkana	O
poster	O
http://t.co/XfZATf5	O

Listening	O
to	O
@mattpowersmusic	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
as	O
Matt	B-PER
Bass	I-PER
.	O
I	O
played	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
7	O
yrs	O
in	O
The	O
Cringe	O
.	O

@Bridgeline	B-PER
Brian	I-PER
,	O
check	O
here	O
for	O
the	O
full	O
archive	O
of	O
#cxmchat	O
http://is.gd/z3u588	O

Keeping	O
busy	O
keeping	O
busy	O
.	O
Work	O
work	O
work	O
.	O
Soon	O
soon	O
soon	O
.	O

@BrianTroyFilms	O
haha	O
nice	O
!	O
looking	O
forward	O
to	O
seeing	O
it	O
!	O

@SilentHustla	B-PER
been	O
there	O
done	O
that	O
hahaha	O

WHat	O
's	O
the	O
word	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
building	O
.....	O
@HHReynolds	O
:	O
College	O
Hoops	O
bloggers	O
-	O
drop	O
me	O
a	O
line	O

Infographic	O
of	O
Google	O
's	O
Acquisitions	O
http://www.scores.org/graphics/google/	O
(	O
via	O
@SusanEsparza	B-PER
)	O

@cynephile	B-PER
Clever	O
!	O

Glad	O
you're	O
enjoying	O
it	O
.	O
RT	O
@its_adrii	O
:	O
Never	O
noticed	O
how	O
relaxing	O
bryant	B-LOC
Park	I-LOC
can	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
a	O
.	O
m	O

@gretchenrubin	B-PER
explains	O
how	O
to	O
be	O
happy	O
,	O
even	O
if	O
you	O
didn't	O
keep	O
your	O
resolutions	O
on	O
@todayshow	B-MISC
http://on.today.com/gptNyw	O

@DNA2K10	O
whats	O
good	O
my	O
g	O
....	O

TV	O
nets	O
hype	O
Al	B-ORG
Qaeda	I-ORG
's	O
surgically	O
implanted	O
bombs	O
.	O
@dangerroom	O
assess	O
the	O
hype	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/nsSyOI	O
and	O
http://bit.ly/oHle6w	O

@rebkatz	B-PER
Route	O
80	O
and	O
it	O
's	O
all	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
bus	O

Checking	O
out	O
this	O
pic	O
:	O
http://firetown.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/04/bowing-to-saudi-king.jpg	O

Really	O
craving	O
breakfast	O
from	O
@darkhorsecafe	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
An	O
oatmeal	O
berry	O
scone-like-thing	O
would	O
be	O
pretty	O
awesome	O
right	O
now	O
.	O

@nperold	O
good	O
to	O
know	O
will	O
avoid	O
using	O
that	O
word	O
in	O
the	O
title	O
.	O

I	O
got	O
some	O
great	O
treasures	O
at	O
the	O
scrap	O
yard	O
to	O
turn	O
into	O
great	O
art	O
!	O
Can't	O
wait	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
my	O
studio	O
and	O
play	O
!!!!	O
:)	O

...?...	O
GlamReal	O
.	O
com	O
:	O
Considering	O
A	O
Career	O
In	O
Real	O
Estate	O
http://tinyurl.com/2aobhjo	O
#glam	O
#realestate	O
#jobs	O
#media	O

@stuffyngpplrd	B-PER
email	O
littlebrownschool@hbgusa	O
.	O
com	O

@BearCreekFest	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
RT	O
!	O
Have	O
a	O
great	O
weekend	O
!	O

The	O
Euro	O
RSCG	O
New	O
York	O
Social	O
is	O
out	O
!	O
http://bit.ly/ijrj9k	O
?	O
Top	O
stories	O
today	O
via	O
@katierosman	O
@llllitl	O

How	O
to	O
Monetize	O
#SocialMedia	B-MISC
-	O
http://t.co/W8EHFSe	O

Love	O
that	O
@casefoundation	B-PER
allows	O
ppl	O
to	O
vote	O
for	O
grant	O
winners	O
.	O
Hooray	O
for	O
transparent	O
funding	O
decisions	O
!	O
Less	O
slimy	O
than	O
Pepsi	B-ORG
.	O
#ncvs	O

sloboda	B-PER
's	O
photo	O
http://fb.me/122E00UtD	O

Green	O
Tip	O
:	O
Borrow	O
books	O
from	O
your	O
local	O
library	O
instead	O
of	O
buying	O
!	O
http://alturl.com/48fui	O

@dsellis	B-PER
Meatball	O
Shop	O
on	O
Bedford	B-LOC
.	O
Not	O
sure	O
if	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
or	O
not	O
though	O
.	O
Any	O
insight	O
?	O

dgetman93	O
:	O
#Accenture	O
-Earned	O
Value	O
-	O
Program	O
Analyst-Hartford	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
CT	I-LOC
http://bit.ly/o5342s	O
#ACN	O
#jobs	O
#hiring	O
#JobAngels	O

Should	O
publishers	O
use	O
more	O
orange	O
in	O
their	O
covers	O
?	O
This	O
infographic	O
says	O
,	O
"	O
Yes	O
."	O
http://bit.ly/gn9zKc	O
(	O
via	O
@olivehues	O
@gretchenrubin	B-PER
)	O

@mtn_dew	O
builds	O
a	O
"	O
throwback	O
shack	O
"	O
(	O
dewthrowbackshack.com	O
)	O
for	O
the	O
permanent	O
return	O
of	O
Mountain	O
Dew	O
Throwback	O
(	O
made	O
with	O
real	O
sugar	O
)	O

In	O
a	O
move	O
to	O
be	O
more	O
like	O
Apple	B-ORG
,	O
Microsoft	B-ORG
will	O
open	O
75	O
retail	O
stores	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
3	O
years	O
:	O
http://t.co/l0Yyu1e	O

Rocky	B-MISC
Horror	I-MISC
Picture	B-MISC
Show	I-MISC
:	O
The	O
Unconventional	O
Convention	O
:	O
Same-Sex	O
Marriage	O
is	O
Legal	O
in	O
NY	B-LOC
!	O
Have	O
Your	O
Ceremony	O
..	O
http://t.co/8hE4GEo	O

@tblanchfield	B-PER
you	O
and	O
many	O
others	O
who	O
commented	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
tan	O
is	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
run	O
.	O

@SarahRayani	B-PER
look	O
forward	O
to	O
working	O
together	O
more	O
!!	O

Be	O
on	O
the	O
LOOKOUT	O
for	O
our	O
HOT	O
STOCK	O
PICK	O
released	O
tonight	O
.	O
Get	O
it	O
@	O
www.stockprofessors.com	O

Enjoying	O
this	O
clever	O
photo	O
aggregator	O
or	O
food/recipe/drink	O
image	O
"	O
potluck	O
"	O
blog	O
:	O
www.tastespotting.com	O
(	O
via	O
@sallymak26	B-PER
)	O

Bow	B-MISC
Tie	I-MISC
Tuesday	I-MISC
(	O
late	O
night	O
hustle	O
)	O
http://twitpic.com/4es950	O

Do	O
you	O
want	O
Spotify	B-ORG
?	O
Admit	O
it	O
,	O
sure	O
you	O
do	O
.	O
Get	O
an	O
invite	O
here	O
:	O
http://ow.ly/5HHLp	O

ABI	O
:	O
Bolivia	B-LOC
mantiene	O
oposición	O
al	O
acuerdo	O
de	O
Cancún	B-LOC
sobre	O
cambio	O
climático	O
http://is.gd/tvSUaC	O
#Bolivia	B-LOC
#cambioclimatico	O
#Cancun	B-LOC
#UNFCCC	B-ORG

@IsThatSnow	O
lol	O
yes	O
Jamal	B-PER
...	O

@ARoadRetraveled	B-PER
I	O
plan	O
on	O
checking	O
out	O
the	O
CPK	O
Wizard	O
of	O
Oz	O
concert	O
if	O
this	O
rain	O
will	O
stop	O
.	O
Looks	O
really	O
cool	O
:)	O

I'm	O
at	O
Whirlpool	B-ORG
Headquarters	O
(	O
2000	O
M-63	O
,	O
Benton	B-LOC
Harbor	I-LOC
)	O
http://4sq.com/jujixb	O

@NMCGlynn	B-PER
@Adwal	O
@AdamHirsch	B-PER
@howardgr	B-PER
panel	O
at	O
@SMCNYC	B-ORG
about	O
#SXSW	O

#anonymousfame	O

Wikipedia	B-ORG
.	O
Print	O
edition	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/awygw	O
via	O
digitaldj	O
.	O
jp	O

Happiness	O
is	O
an	O
inside	O
job	O
.	O

Rhetorical	O
question	O
:	O
If	O
you	O
are	O
looking	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
why	O
cut	O
medicare	O
,	O
medicaid	O
&	O
SS	O
?	O
Don't	O
ppl	O
like	O
that	O
?	O
And	O
revenues	O
&	O

@CamilleLivette	B-PER
heres	O
where	O
all	O
the	O
food	O
trucks	O
went	O
!	O
@midtownlunch	O
RT	O
@nytimesdining	O
:	O
Food	O
Trucks	O
Shooed	O
From	O
Midtown	B-LOC
http://t.co/jJwmWvg	O

Thx	O
RT	O
@twittersuggests	O
:	O
@amalhathlool	O
New	O
suggestions	O
for	O
you	O
:	O
@mommypalooza	O
,	O
@TodaysMoms	O
&	O
@cafemom	O
http://twitter.com/#!/who_to_follow	O

Get	O
started	O
with	O
Facebook	B-ORG
video	O
chat	O
-	O
http://www.facebook.com/videocalling	O

AP	B-ORG
sources	O
:	O
Panetta	B-PER
to	O
OK	O
end	O
of	O
military	O
gay	O
ban	O
http://dlvr.it/cCjZZ	O

Thanks	O
Sherrell	B-PER
!	O
Hope	O
your	O
summer	O
is	O
great	O
!	O
@organicvixen	B-PER
@bebenoir	B-PER
@lovingyourhair	B-PER
@afrobella	B-PER
@stylesj	B-PER
@blingingbeauty	B-PER
@juneambrose	B-PER

FREE	O
online	O
resources	O
for	O
Social	O
Media	O
.	O
Check	O
out	O
the	O
list	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/1bIV9a	O
Please	O
RT	O

"	O
She	O
could	O
be	O
a	O
FARMER	O
in	O
those	O
clothes	O
..."	O
RT	O
@susanheecho	B-PER
:	O
Why	O
is	O
@KELLYROWLAND	B-PER
reciting	O
the	O
entire	O
Clueless	B-MISC
dialogue	O
in	O
the	O
car	O

GlamReal	B-ORG
.	I-ORG
com	I-ORG
:	O
Commercial	O
Real	O
Estate	O
Loan	O
Closer	O
(	O
NorthMarq	O
Capital	O
,	O
Inc	O
.	O
)	O
San	B-LOC
Francisco	I-LOC
,	B-LOC
CA	I-LOC
9	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/h6C7Ex	O
#realestate	O
#jobs	O

@jimblogger	B-PER
Cult	O
of	O
Apple	B-ORG
.	O
Can	O
we	O
still	O
be	O
friends	O
?	O

@TylerHWilliams	B-PER
Worse	O
case	O
scenario	O
is	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
you	O
6PM	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
done	O
with	O
work	O
.	O

word	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
:	O
WORD	O

New	O
post	O
:	O
Earn	O
$43	O
Per	O
Sale	O
-	O
CB	O
's	O
Highest	O
Quality	O
Panic	O
&	O
Anxiety	O
Product	O
http://bit.ly/qE0ib2	O

Jeff	B-PER
Schleider	I-PER
in	O
Crain	B-LOC
's	O
this	O
week	O
discussing	O
social	O
media	O
http://fb.me/yU0CrcWJ	O

OH	O
at	O
work	O
:	O
"	O
I'm	O
not	O
angry	O
I'm	O
just	O
Russian	B-MISC
"	O

@NYCLoverMan	O
yeah	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
have	O
another	O
now	O
.	O
Just	O
feels	O
like	O
its	O
dragging	O
...:	O
(	O
.	O
How're	O
you	O
?	O

@GYVISNYC	B-PER
yo	O

More	O
like	O
,	O
b/c	O
YOU	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
suggestions	O
tweeps	O
RT	O
@angelaecarder	B-PER
:	O
Great	O
NYC	B-LOC
blogs	O
,	O
b/c	O
Scoutmob	B-PER
says	O
so	O
!	O
http://bit.ly/lXL5iw	O

Actress	O
@OliviaMunn	B-PER
shows	O
us	O
her	O
beatboxing	O
skills	O
.	O
http://t.co/qx8wuRz	O

@PrecociousLil	B-PER
More	O
long	O
kisses	O
,	O
making	O
her	O
toes	O
curl	O
.	O
Move	O
along	O
people	O
,	O
nothing	O
to	O
see	O
here	O
.	O

#NowPlaying	O
on	O
the	O
@WeaponXPromo	O
newsletter	O
|	O
@KardinalO	B-PER
feat	O
.	O
@TheRealAkon	O
"	O
Body	O
Bounce	O
"	O
|	O
http://mim.io/95e13	O

AP	B-ORG
citing	O
US	B-LOC
official	O
:	O
New	O
bin	B-PER
Laden	I-PER
tape	O
,	O
recorded	O
shortly	O
before	O
death	O
,	O
expected	O
to	O
surface	O
soon	O

NEW	O
POST	O
from	O
@kevineikenberry	B-PER
:	O
6	O
Ways	O
to	O
Build	O
on	O
Recent	O
Success	O
http://bit.ly/ik9bzk	O
#sales	O

How	O
is	O
it	O
one	O
careless	O
match	O
can	O
start	O
a	O
forest	O
fire	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
takes	O
a	O
whole	O
box	O
to	O
start	O
a	O
campfire	O
?	O

On	O
8/3	O
a	O
first-of-its-kind	O
discussion	O
on	O
immortality	O
,	O
TRANSCENDENT	B-MISC
MAN	I-MISC
w/Ray	B-PER
Kurzweil	I-PER
,	O
will	O
broadcast	O
LIVE	O
from	O
NY	B-LOC
:	O
http://bit.ly/oBOIHu	O

Hermaphrodites	O
On	O
the	O
Rise	O
:	O
Find	O
out	O
which	O
celeb	O
might	O
be	O
keeping	O
a	O
well-hidden	O
secret	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/MgH7h	O

New	O
Event	O
:	O
Ride	O
to	O
Milford	B-LOC
,	O
NJ	B-LOC
via	O
Sweet	B-LOC
Hollow	I-LOC
Road	I-LOC
http://bit.ly/l6KaEt	O

@meetjenn	B-PER
Only	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
in	O
...	O
so	O
far	O
so	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
Norton	B-PER
was	O
the	O
original	O
impetus	O
.	O

OMG	O
!	O
I	O
just	O
found	O
ShoeGlamm	O
.	O
com	O
!	O
STUNNING	O
shoes	O
&	O
ultra	O
low	O
prices	O
.	O
FF	O
@shoeglamm	B-ORG
for	O
exclusive	O
#giveaways	O
!	O
http://lx.im/1dxI9	O
-	O
spon	O

Calcium	O
without	O
cows	O
?	O
Three	O
experts	O
weigh	O
in	O
on	O
how	O
to	O
get	O
your	O
daily	O
dose	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/nOS0Li	O
@ozgarcia	B-PER
@BlumCenter	B-ORG
@rdlinda	O

.	O
@thecurvystylist	B-PER
Cool	O
!	O
Can't	O
wait	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
new	O
site	O
!	O

@AntonioReyX360	B-PER
@WPIX	O
@PIXat10	O
I	O
don't	O
know	O
...	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
police	O
will	O
uncover	O
more	O
information	O
soon	O
.	O

@AngelStrange54	B-PER
thank	O
you	O
for	O
spreading	O
the	O
word	O
!	O

@GildaKoralFlora	B-PER
Hello	O
!	O
You	O
can	O
get	O
a	O
hold	O
of	O
us	O
at	O
info@boutiqued	O
.	O
com	O

10	O
Foods	O
men	O
should	O
include	O
in	O
their	O
diets	O
to	O
improve	O
health	O
and	O
prevent	O
disease	O
http://bit.ly/9KKK35	O

Great	O
mood	O
today	O
,	O
awesome	O
morning	O
to	O
start	O
off	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Happy	O
hump	O
day	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
embrace	O
the	O
"	O
TGIF	O
"	O
concept	O
:)	O

@mrdearybury1	B-PER
nice	O
,	O
training	O
starting	O
for	O
which	O
one	O
?	O
#runchat	O

Buying	O
the	O
Best	O
Flight	O
Simulator	O
-	O
Flight	B-MISC
Pro	I-MISC
Sim	I-MISC
-	O
A	O
Review	O
http://bit.ly/ebsq9F	O

When	O
we	O
examine	O
the	O
human	O
brain	O
and	O
brain	O
functioning	O
,	O
we	O
become	O
clear	O
that	O
the	O
brain	O
is	O
a	O
tool	O
of	O
something	O
larger	O
than	O
itself	O
.	O

special	O
surprise	O
:	O
Locksley	B-PER
to	O
play	O
at	O
our	O
AW11	B-MISC
debut	O
!!!	O

The	O
@MemphisBroadway	B-ORG
performance	O
is	O
so	O
cute	O
with	O
all	O
of	O
those	O
kids	O
!	O
But	O
@ChrisRock	B-PER
doesn't	O
look	O
amused	O
.	O
WARM	O
IT	O
UP	O
,	O
CHRIS	O
!!!	O
#TonyAwards	O

MAY	O
Pilobolus	O
Workshop	O
at	O
Peridance	B-LOC
:	O
http://blog.danceruniverse.com/blog/story/2010/4/24/123022/063	O

Looking	O
forward	O
to	O
Motel	O
Luca	O
tonight	O
.	O
Given	O
that	O
dick	O
jokes	O
abound	O
most	O
days	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
banner	O
night	O
.	O
#weinergate	O
#iloveanopenmic	O
#fb	O

Only	O
constant	O
theft	O
and	O
murder	O
will	O
guarantee	O
the	O
survival	O
of	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
Israel	B-LOC
.	O

GREAT	O
FALL	O
DEALS	O
TO	O
ASIA	B-LOC
AVAILABLE	O
FOR	O
A	O
LIMITED	O
TIME	O
-	O
http://eepurl.com/bAfeH	O

Getting	O
ready	O
for	O
4th	O
quarter	O
action	O
.	O

@MLLTPhotos	B-PER
@iamisis	B-PER
@McElijahblack	B-PER
Those	O
of	O
u	O
who	O
didn't	O
read	O
"	O
A	B-MISC
Visit	I-MISC
frm	B-MISC
the	I-MISC
Goon	B-MISC
Squad	I-MISC
"	O
yet	O
,	O
pls	O
get	O
in	O
touch	O
w/	O
me	O
for	O
ur	O
copy	O
.	O

AKVIS	B-ORG
Launches	O
MakeUp	O
Photoshop	B-ORG
Plugin	O
and	O
App	O
for	O
Glamorizing	O
Photos	O
http://ow.ly/5oFNR	O

We	O
get	O
asked	O
alot	O
on	O
additional	O
resources	O
look	O
up	O
young	O
entrepreneur	O
magazine	O

Patriot	O
#FF	O
@txjogger	B-PER
@LawlessKO	B-PER
@hankrearden73	B-PER
@robdiwa	B-PER
@billyhallowell	B-PER
@Dr_Rose	O
@twineim	B-PER
@janicedwhs	B-PER
@JLocher1	B-PER
@macg_og	B-PER
@dominionpundit	B-PER

My	O
Cancer	O
Blog	O
:P	O
lanet	O
C-	O
Veince	B-LOC
,	O
NY	O
Hospital	O
,	O
Biofeedback	O
then	O
Soundgarden-Hope	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
Philly	B-LOC
tonight	O
http://bit.ly/rfGbpw	O

#FF	O
@nubiasnonsense	O
@Fennimas	O
@sammydvintage	O
@Styleamor	O
@fashionjazz	O
@alixrose	O
@CiaoChessa	O
@thestylegent	O
@midtowngirl	O
@nikkicatania	O
@_IFB	O

@jamiezoob	B-PER
Thanks	O
for	O
mentioning	O
me	O
.	O
If	O
want	O
to	O
be	O
updated	O
about	O
upcoming	O
exhibitions	O
,	O
please	O
like	O
my	O
facebook	B-ORG
page	O
http://t.co/13Chm7F	O

Everyone	O
go	O
follow	O
@LucCarl	B-PER
and	O
@preciousweapons	B-PER
because	O
they	O
followed	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
back	O
in	O
09	O
&	O
really	O
love	O
us	O
monsters	O
:)	O
#FF	O

@acarvin	B-PER
nice	O
meeting	O
you	O
!	O

The	O
only	O
thing	O
growing	O
faster	O
than	O
China	B-LOC
's	O
economy	O
is	O
Trump	B-PER
's	O
ego	O
.	O

The	O
Internet	O
Marketing	O
Brand	O
Process	O
http://bit.ly/hRYExC	O

Reading	O
:	O
IBM	B-ORG
analytical	O
Cloud	O
-	O
BusinessCloud9	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/riLiJ1	O

charlie	B-PER
sheen	I-PER
interview	O
|	O
oil	O
prices	O
|	O
2011	O
academy	B-ORG
awards	I-ORG
|	O
dunkin	B-ORG
donuts	I-ORG
|	O
vanity	B-ORG
fair	I-ORG
|	O
kanye	B-PER
west	I-PER
|	O
http://happn.in/ny/28feb11-08am/	O

First	O
Listen	O
Fridays	O
is	O
back	O
!	O
Check	O
out	O
songs	O
from	O
"	O
Duets	O
"	O
NOW	O
only	O
on	O
GleeTheMusic	B-MISC
.	I-MISC
com	I-MISC
http://bit.ly/9RPobr	O
#Glee	O

@eatwholly	O
Congratulations	O
!	O
Your	O
Classic	O
Wholly	O
Guacamole	O
won	O
a	O
2011	O
FITNESS	O
Healthy	O
Food	O
Award	O
!	O
#FITNESSfood	O
http://bit.ly/kt7wJz	O

Hey	O
@MsVirgoDaughter	B-PER
,	O
a	O
little	O
encouragement	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
First	O
blooms	O
on	O
English	B-MISC
Lavender	I-MISC
.	O
#gardening	O
http://twitpic.com/4zo47e	O

@drmrsthmonarch	B-PER
What	O
are	O
you	O
looking	O
for	O
in	O
your	O
new	O
apartment	O
?	O
We	O
have	O
a	O
some	O
awesome	O
listings	O
that	O
came	O
on	O
this	O
week	O

~New	O
Educational	O
Opportunities	O
,	O
New	O
Instructors	O
,	O
and	O
Beautiful	O
New	O
Location	O
for	O
Weekend	O
With	O
the	O
Masters	O
Workshop	O
...	O
http://fb.me/FTCw3ZhI	O

@SandraD	B-PER
Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
advice	O
!	O
I	O
didn't	O
realize	O
eBay	B-ORG
had	O
such	O
high	O
fees	O
...	O

Colorful	O
Works	O
Of	O
Art	O
Painted	O
On	O
Human	O
Bodies	O
http://ow.ly/1dQ8TL	O

Gearfuse	O
Almanac	O
:	O
January	O
17	O
in	O
Science	O
and	O
Technology	O
http://bit.ly/gj1wVo	O

New	O
underwater	O
ride	O
for	O
Navy	B-ORG
SEALs	I-ORG
http://t.co/sLRr7Xb	O
Primer	O
on	O
what	O
it'll	O
replace	O
http://t.co/EATEAC4	O

thank	O
's	O
RT	O
@jennabrom	B-PER
:	O
Wondering	O
what	O
the	O
plural	O
form	O
of	O
that	O
word	O
is	O
?	O
Well	O
,	O
it	O
definitely	O
doesn't	O
involve	O
an	O
apostrophe	O
.	O

Eminem	B-PER
,	O
Royce	O
da	O
5'9	O
"	O
Aiming	O
for	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
on	O
Billboard	B-ORG
200	O
|	O
Billboard	O
...:	O
Eminem	O
,	O
Royce	O
da	O
5'9	O
"	O
Ai	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/k4wyBD	O

How	O
@Starbucks	B-ORG
and	O
@JustinsNutButta	B-ORG
saved	O
my	O
breakfast	O
!	O
:)	O
http://t.co/MCgmAAx	O

TY	O
!	O
RT	O
@rustilyn	B-PER
:	O
the	O
gals	O
rock	O
#FF	O
@babspinfrance	B-PER
@TheKirCorner	B-PER
@ITSMoments	B-PER
@shellthings	B-PER
@DuncanBrandi	B-PER
@jenrambles	B-PER
@PMuffintop	B-PER
@lawmomma77	B-PER

NYC	B-ORG
DA	I-ORG
Charges	O
26	O
People	O
With	O
Using	O
P2P	O
to	O
Swap	O
Child	O
Sex	O
Videos	O
-	O
Wired	B-ORG
News	I-ORG
http://goo.gl/fb/jNy24	O

I	O
will	O
be	O
29	O
on	O
August	O
11th	O
.	O
Sigh	O
,	O
where	O
did	O
time	O
go	O
?	O

Crossword	O
clue	O
:	O
Brand	O
of	O
saltine	O
(	O
5	O
letters	O
)	O
Think	O
you	O
know	O
?	O
Reply	O
with	O
your	O
answer	O
!	O

Chocolate	O
Cheesecake	O
http://bit.ly/oAGFpR	O
.	O

@flargh	O
Wow	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
.	O
So	O
sad	O
.	O

Check	O
out	O
the	O
latest	O
blog	O
post	O
by	O
NIMH	B-ORG
Director	O
Thomas	O
Insel	O
,	O
MD	O
:	O
New	O
Findings	O
Reveal	O
New	O
Worlds	O
In	O
Neuroscience	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/hi7w6P	O

My	O
cat	O
turned	O
1	O
last	O
week	O
.	O
Photo	O
caption	O
:	O
Iz	O
mah	O
birfday	O
?!	O
http://instagr.am/p/IQ2Oc/	O

Watch	O
this	O
video	O
on	O
how	O
produce	O
is	O
harvested	O
from	O
Katchkie	B-LOC
farm	I-LOC
to	O
New	B-ORG
Green	I-ORG
Markets	I-ORG
:)	O
http://bit.ly/hilglv	O

@TheophilusL	B-PER
When	O
you	O
have	O
downtime	O
in	O
NY	B-LOC
...	O
Lets	O
shoot	O

My	O
dad	O
goes	O
"	O
Well	O
can	O
he	O
at	O
least	O
pass	O
for	O
a	O
brotha	O
?"	O
No	O
dad	O
...	O

@MimiImfurst	B-PER
woooooork	O

Im	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
is	O
actually	O
backed	O
by	O
some	O
science	O
http://on.ted.com/8m4F	O

We	O
passed	O
140k	O
fans	O
on	O
Facebook	B-ORG
today	O
!	O
http://t.co/a6dxNPg	O

Teaching	O
today	O
at	O
YogaWorks	B-ORG
Soho	B-LOC
10:00	O
am-	O
11:30	O
am	O
YogaWorks	B-ORG
(	O
2/3	O
)	O
?	O
-	O
Come	O
explore	O
the	O
Ajna	B-MISC
Chakra	I-MISC
and	O
your	O
drishti	O

Break	O
a	O
leg	O
@omgitzfern	B-PER
in	O
@ebeensemble	O
's	O
Much	O
Ado	O
today	O
!!	O

We	O
couldn't	O
be	O
more	O
pumped	O
for	O
TOMORROW	O
!	O
The	O
list	O
will	O
finally	O
be	O
published	O
!	O
Just	O
ONE	O
MORE	O
DAY	O
!	O

$SAVW	O
"	O
It'	O
's	O
hard	O
to	O
tell	O
exactly	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
the	O
"	O
on	O
ADFN	O
InvestorsHub	O
message	O
boards	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/n1J2Em	O

Bring	O
the	O
best	O
dessert	O
to	O
this	O
weekend	O
's	O
party	O
!	O
These	O
cheesecake	O
recipes	O
are	O
all	O
delicious	O
!	O
http://bit.ly/q2Njw5	O

The	O
only	O
weather	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
canceled	O
#ShakespeareinthePark	O
for	O
is	O
rain	O
.	O
But	O
we	O
encourage	O
ppl	O
to	O
take	O
precautions	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
coming	O
out	O
.	O

Less	O
than	O
1	O
week	O
away	O
from	O
Richard	B-PER
Smallwood	I-PER
with	O
Vision	O
"	O
Promises	O
"	O
album	O
listening	O
party	O
7/18	O
8pm	O
Bonnerfide	B-ORG
Radio	I-ORG
.	O
www.getbonnerfide.com	O

I	O
am	O
so	O
lucky	O
to	O
have	O
@marekr	B-PER
as	O
our	O
IT	O
guy	O
for	O
@morris_king	B-PER
!	O
He	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
and	O
always	O
there	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
need	O
him	O
--	O
even	O
holiday	O
weekends	O
!	O

Really	O
,	O
these	O
needed	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
separate	O
shows	O
?	O
#sadTLC	O
http://instagr.am/p/EYM_I/	O

Chi	O
town	O
layover	O
omw	O
to	O
Kansas	O
City	O
!!	O
(@	O
Chicago	O
Midway	O
International	O
Airport	O
(	O
MDW	O
)	O
w/	O
34	O
others	O
)	O
http://4sq.com/kW2bQE	O

#FunFact	O
:	O
Sound	O
at	O
the	O
right	O
vibration	O
can	O
bore	O
holes	O
through	O
a	O
solid	O
object	O
.	O

I	O
feel	O
like	O
this	O
numbering	O
system	O
is	O
like	O
the	O
lottery	O
-	O
watching	O
the	O
board	O
and	O
praying	O
they	O
call	O
mine	O
.	O

Coop	O
for	O
sale	O
in	O
West	B-LOC
Village/Jane	I-LOC
Street	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
2.5	O
BD/2BT/$1650000	O
.	O
No	O
Board	O
approval	O
!	O
www.realty.mx/115a4b	O

Day	O
1	O
in	O
our	O
new	O
40,000	O
sq	O
foot	O
office	O
space	O
@bigfuel	B-ORG
.	O
It	O
's	O
so	O
big	O
we	O
had	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
map	O
!	O
It	O
kinda	O
feels	O
like	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
school	O
!	O

Spike	O
Lee	O
's	O
former	O
office	O
building	O
for	O
sale	O
|	O
The	O
Real	O
Deal	O
|	O
New	B-ORG
York	I-ORG
Real	B-ORG
Estate	I-ORG
News	I-ORG
http://t.co/s4MW6ij	O

Sky	O
I.T.	O
#TurkeyDay	O
feast	O
at	O
our	O
#NYC	B-LOC
headquarters	O
!	O
Can	O
this	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
#Monday	O
or	O
what	O
?!	O
http://bit.ly/bBNXEq	O

JDub	O
to	O
close	O
http://j.mp/nyePhe	O

@EddiesPizzaNY	B-ORG
mmm	O

Kickstart	O
your	O
health	O
this	O
April	O
4th	O
:	O
http://bit.ly/4y6Te	O
.	O
http://fb.me/TaDaxrqC	O

You	O
guys	O
should	O
follow	O
us	O
on	O
Tumblr	B-ORG
;	O
we	O
just	O
posted	O
a	O
"	O
Best	O
Of	O
"	O
clip	O
of	O
Arnold	B-PER
Schwarzenegger	I-PER
as	O
Mr	O
.	O
Freeze	O
.	O
http://villagevoice.tumblr.com/	O

RT	O
:	O
@chislett	O
:	O
Full	O
house	O
here	O
tonight	O
@nwc	O
for	O
@NYSocialMeetup	B-ORG
w/@social_vidar	O
presenting	O
w/organizer	O
@sergeych	B-PER
http://instagr.am/p/gqDv/	O

Scientists	O
discovered	O
that	O
mushrooms	O
growing	O
in	O
Oregon	B-LOC
were	O
genetically	O
identical	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
roots	O
of	O
the	O
...	O
http://fb.me/14nAjnPjN	O

Elliott	O
Lucca	O
Ibiza	O
Double	O
Handle	O
Hobo	O
Spotted	O
in	O
CA	B-LOC
http://fb.me/FTIii4yM	O

@ToyotaEquipment	O
Our	O
pleasure	O
!	O
Have	O
a	O
great	O
weekend	O
!	O

One	O
of	O
our	O
photographers	O
just	O
popped	O
by	O
the	O
office	O
between	O
shoots	O
to	O
say	O
hello	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
always	O
nice	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
!	O

Haven't	O
checked	O
out	O
their	O
page	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
love	O
the	O
logo	O
!	O
http://fb.me/FNA1Rp2w	O

Please	O
give	O
$5	O
to	O
support	O
#opsafe	O
camps	O
this	O
summer	O
in	O
Japan	B-LOC
and	O
China	B-LOC
.	O
http://firstgiving.com/operationsafe	O
#DT	O
@operationSAFE	B-ORG

Only	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
left	O
to	O
vote	O
for	O
the	O
best	O
cardboard	O
creation	O
at	O
http://ow.ly/25qBS	O
!!!	O

Hey	O
friends	O
...	O
I	O
need	O
a	O
FT	O
content	O
strategist	O
to	O
join	O
my	O
team	O
at	O
R/GA	B-ORG
.	O
Please	O
ping	O
me	O
if	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
anyone	O
.	O
Thanks	O
!	O

From	O
earlier	O
tonight	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
subway	O
station	O
at	O
Columbus	B-LOC
Circle	I-LOC
-	O
view	O
of	O
Time	B-ORG
Warner	I-ORG
bldgs	O
http://t.co/p9yZUNa	O

Sunday	B-MISC
May	O
8th	O
,	O
11	O
am	O
.	O
Take	O
Mom	O
on	O
our	O
Lower	B-LOC
East	I-LOC
Side	I-LOC
food	O
tour	O
.	O
Reg	O
.	O
$	O
45.50	O
.	O
Now	O
$30	O
.	O
Call	O
212	O
535	O
8687	O
or	O
...	O
http://fb.me/Zt934ocO	O

Congrats	O
!	O
RT	O
@albertbrooks	B-PER
Amazon	B-ORG
sold	O
out	O
of	O
book	O
,	O
on	O
re-order	O
.	O
Not	O
since	O
Oral	B-ORG
B	I-ORG
electric	O
toothpick	O
has	O
product	O
moved	O
this	O
fast	O
.	O

@FRS	O
@joehodges	B-PER
love	O
the	O
energy	O
fruit	O
chews	O
!	O
They	O
wake	O
me	O
up	O
so	O
well	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
!	O
xoxo	O

Med	O
News	O
:	O
Prolonged	O
Bottle	O
Use	O
Linked	O
to	O
Obesity	O
-	O
http://bit.ly/lOgJlo	O

Los	B-LOC
Angeles	I-LOC
Casting	O
Call	O
for	O
Movie	O
Extras	O
http://t.co/c4rDr9s	O

In	O
the	O
Deathroom	O
(	O
DeathroomFilm	O
)	O
on	O
Twitter	O
http://fb.me/yng3UDyk	O

New	O
blog	O
by	O
Gary	B-PER
Rosenblatt	I-PER
:	O
Bibi	O
's	O
blunder	O
:	O
The	O
Middle	B-LOC
East	I-LOC
's	O
new	O
Mr	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
http://bit.ly/mMSXgs	O

I	O
was	O
JUST	O
thinking	O
that	O
!	O
RT	O
@lmmclane	B-PER
:	O
It	O
's	O
a	O
dirty	O
hare	O
kind	O
of	O
night	O
!	O
@nickyru	B-PER
@el_lornado	O
@HobokenTC	O

@mrisha5	O
Hello	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
a	O
good	O
Question	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
ideas	O
you	O
disagree	O
with	O
and	O
write	O
why	O
you	O
disagree	O
,	O
keep	O
a	O
pad	O
with	O
u	O
always	O
.	O

We're	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
that	O
Temple	B-PER
will	O
be	O
speaking	O
at	O
JCK	O
's	O
conference	O
,	O
"	O
Gold	O
:	O
Substance	O
,	O
Symbol	O
and	O
Significance	O
"	O
-	O
http://bit.ly/fiV4gD	O

Looking	O
for	O
Lessons	O
in	O
Others	O
'	O
Rejection	O
Letters	O
http://nyti.ms/9cmnWF	O

I'm	O
@	O
the	O
morris	O
+	O
king	O
company	O
@sonarme	O

My	O
last	O
night	O
in	O
Toronto	B-LOC
.	O

@leyawn	O
@cbattan	O
#DescribeYourPenisWithAMovie	O
A	O
River	O
Runs	O
Through	O
It	O

This	O
Week	O
With	O
Peak	O
!	O
Tuesday	O
4/5	O
:	O
Catch	O
Peak	O
's	O
own	O
Mike	B-PER
Cadoux	I-PER
on	O
Beer	O
Sessions	O
Radio	O
at	O
5pm	O
!!...	O
http://fb.me/NTvccNpk	O

International	B-ORG
Meetings	I-ORG
Market	I-ORG
Demystified	O
:	O
May	O
10th	O
Summit	O
Meeting	O
on	O
Trends	O
.	O
Details	O
here	O
http://ht.ly/4JLEO	O
#eventprofs	O

Life	O
is	O
short	O
!	O
Try	O
2	O
make	O
everyday	O
productive	O
!	O
@paulrwhitacre	O
:	O
@LewisPoretz	O
@PegFitzpatrick	O
@fredmcclimans	O
@xDeepS	O
@aoadra	O
#usguys	B-MISC

#FF	O
---	O
>	O
@_derekallen	O

Watch	O
a	O
virtual	O
canyon	O
run	O
in	O
a	O
Porsche	B-ORG
GT3	O
RS	O
4.0	O
for	O
NFS	O
:	O
The	O
Run	O
[	O
Video]	O
:	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/qQ32Lo	O

@Twitter	B-ORG
,	O
stop	O
blocking	O
#FuckYouWashington	O
+	O
#FuckYouGOP	O
from	O
TTs	O
if	O
you're	O
letting	O
racist	O
bullshit	O
like	O
#	O
Blame	O
The	O
Muslims	O
trend	O
.	O

Updates	O
on	O
today	O
's	O
bombing	O
and	O
shooting	O
in	O
#Oslo	B-LOC
http://nym.ag/pCXhAM	O

@TheByliner	B-ORG
Aww	O
,	O
now	O
I	O
feel	O
bad	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
growing	O
on	O
me	O
!	O

@GenerationMeh	B-PER
Chihuly	O
is	O
worth	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
closing	O
soon	O
(	O
8/7)	O
!	O
Also	O
see	O
@mfaboston	O
's	O
new	O
wing	O
and	O
the	O
Cuba	O
photo	O
series	O
.	O

@jnolos0708	B-PER
A	O
boy	O
can	O
dream	O
.	O

"	O
Harry	O
Potter	O
"	O
Cast	O
Gets	O
Magical	O
Parting	O
Gifts	O
http://bit.ly/oAhHoR	O

THIRD	B-MISC
REICH	I-MISC
,	O
never-before-seen	O
footage	O
tells	O
the	O
story	O
of	O
the	O
Third	B-MISC
Reich	I-MISC
through	O
the	O
eyes	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
who	O
lived	O
it	O
http://amzn.to/hKHYvY	O

@zoomfergie	O
yes	O
you	O
are	O
right	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
also	O
on	O
RCN	B-ORG
,	O
channel	O
549	O
.	O
Call	O
1.800	O
.	O
RING	O
.	O
RCN	O
to	O
subscribe	O
.	O

Pelosi	B-PER
supports	O
clean	O
vote	O
on	O
debt	O
ceiling	O
increase	O
http://t.co/SAOB8qD	O
via	O
@thinkprogress	O

Google	B-ORG
Maps	O
Tags	O
|	O
Are	O
Google	O
Maps	O
Tags	O
Worth	O
The	O
Fee	O
?	O
http://bit.ly/dcT03k	O
#googlemaps	O

@DarciAlexis	B-PER
@irishgirl	B-PER
Does	O
not	O
need	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
lady	O
!	O
Ping	O
me	O
,	O
thanks	O
muchly	O
!	O
tony	O
at	O
nwc	O
dot	O
co	O

Who	O
will	O
control	O
US	B-LOC
carbon	O
market	O
?	O
http://bit.ly/3OnEkm	O

#Lortels	O
RT	O
@kristenschaaled	B-PER
:	O
Samantha	B-PER
Bee	I-PER
killed	O
so	O
hard	O
at	O
the	O
Lucille	B-MISC
Lortel	I-MISC
Awards	I-MISC
that	O
Bin	B-PER
Laden	I-PER
died	O
.	O
#waronterror	O
#offbroadwaynews	O

really	O
good	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
here	O
@gaynycdad	O
@prbecker	O
@ciaobella50	O
@JeanRubinAZ	O

Just	O
called	O
#11	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
#50	O
.	O
Sigh	O
.	O
(@	O
DiPalo	O
Fine	O
Foods	O
)	O
http://4sq.com/h8ys0w	O

@tashi316	O
thanks	O
.	O
Will	O
do	O
.	O

2010	O
Axing	O
of	O
Helen	B-PER
Thomas	I-PER
,	O
Octavia	B-PER
Nasr	I-PER
,	O
Natl	O
Amer	O
Arab	O
Journalists	O
Assn	O
To	O
Discuss	O
http://www.stinkyjournalism.org/editordetail.php?id=1340	O

via	O
@janelasky	B-PER
:	O
Rebecca	B-PER
Black	I-PER
is	O
not	O
a	O
hack	O
?!?!	O
#VIDEO	O
http://su.pr/26d6Is	O
#friday	O
#music	O
#rebeccablack	B-PER

@escherx	O
you	O
,	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
much	O
fun	O
!	O

China	B-LOC
set	O
to	O
leapfrog	O
US	B-LOC
in	O
race	O
to	O
roll-out	O
electric	O
vehicles	O
-	O
http://bit.ly/gRlxRj	O

My	O
three	O
day	O
"	O
Commercial	O
Real	O
Estate	O
Certificate	O
"	O
course	O
is	O
this	O
weekend	O
,	O
Feb	O
.	O
18-20th	O
at	O
the	O
NY	B-ORG
Real	I-ORG
Estate	B-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
.	O
http://bit.ly/73AtPu	O

LaVie	O
Is	O
that	O
Thursday	O
Spot	O

@bhoonmie	B-PER
>>	O
GET	O
LOOSE	O
>	O
SNIPPET>>DAT	O
FIRE>>	O
http://twiturm.com/x6tvb	O
YOUNGLOVE	O
on	O
Twitpic	O
twitpic.com/2xfywt	O
FOLLOW	O
@KINGYOUNGLOVE	B-PER
[	O
RT	O
]	O

BBC	B-ORG
goes	O
global	O
with	O
iPlayer	O
subs	O
,	O
launching	O
on	O
iPad	O
first	O
.	O
http://bit.ly/f237kC	O

One	O
last	O
tweet	O
for	O
a	O
while	O
.	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Rainbow	B-LOC
City	I-LOC
and	O
play	O
with	O
the	O
inflatable	O
sculptures	O
.	O
Has	O
anyone	O
been	O
!	O
#NYC	B-LOC

There	O
are	O
few	O
differences	O
in	O
what	O
people	O
endure	O
but	O
1	O
main	O
difference	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
succeed-they	O
REFUSE	O
TO	O
GIVE	O
IN	O
&	O
PERSEVERE	O
UNTIL	O
THEY	O
WIN	O

Send	O
me	O
a	O
message	O
with	O
a	O
short	O
story	O
about	O
a	O
decision	O
that	O
you	O
made	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
turning	O
point	O
in	O
your	O
career/life	O
....	O
http://fb.me/TN8YriCi	O

Featured	O
on	O
Personal	O
Branding	O
TV	O
:	O
Gap	B-ORG
:	O
Khaki	O
Soul	O
.	O
What	O
music	O
conveys	O
the	O
essence	O
of	O
your	O
brand	O
?	O
http://bit.ly/bKbDG6	O

What	O
we	O
like	O
to	O
hear	O
:	O
"	O
Midnight	B-MISC
Riot	I-MISC
made	O
me	O
laugh	O
out	O
loud	O
."	O
RT	O
@brownjawa	B-PER
:	O
Review	O
:	O
MIDNIGHT	O
RIOT	O
by	O
@BenAaronovitch	B-PER
http://bit.ly/jgt3iy	O

To	O
be	O
the	O
happiest	O
man	O
in	O
America	B-LOC
,	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
tall	O
,	O
married	O
Asian-American	O
sexagenarian	O
Jew	O
living	O
in	O
Hawaii	B-LOC
.	O
http://nyti.ms/fwS3fl	O

HGTV	B-ORG
making	O
over	O
Hank	O
Steinbrenner	O
's	O
House	O
?	O
http://bit.ly/hZIB4z	O
<	O
Read	O
this	O
.	O
Pictures	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
everything	O
!	O
#yankees	B-ORG

Jailbroken	O
iOS	B-MISC
5	O
gets	O
third-party	O
Notification	O
Center	O
widgets	O
http://dlvr.it/W94dV	O

Super	O
cheap	O
car	O
rental	O
rates	O
($9/day	O
or	O
$62/week	O
incl	O
.	O
taxes	O
and	O
fees	O
!	O
)	O
still	O
available	O
in	O
Chicago	B-LOC
today	O
in	O
Jul	O
&	O
Aug	O
.	O
http://t.co/MGIjWkq	O

SERIOUSLY	O
!	O
NJ	B-LOC
needs	O
to	O
do	O
something	O
about	O
all	O
the	O
potholes	O
in	O
their	O
roads	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
thought	O
FL	B-LOC
was	O
bad	O
.	O

Always	O
great	O
having	O
drinks	O
with	O
@yukikotani	B-PER
:	O
)	O
a	O
wonderful	O
friend	O
!	O
Very	O
stylish	O
too	O
!	O

wow	O
kim	B-PER
k	I-PER
getten	O
married	O
,....	O
shocked	O

@coffeewithian	O
My	O
money	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
bunny	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bunny	O
version	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
.	O
)	O
=P	O

Sexy	O
business	O
meeting	O
term	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
"	O
increased	O
penetration	O
"	O

HOMER'S	B-PER
ODYSSEY	O
,	O
Tonight	O
,	O
8:00	O
pm	O
,	O
the	O
Green	O
Room	O
Theater	O
at	O
45Bleecker	O

@jessmarati	B-PER
Hi	O
Jess	B-PER
!	O
What	O
's	O
your	O
affiliation	O
with	O
this	O
organization	O
?	O

Winning	O
the	O
lottery	O
can	O
be	O
almost	O
impossible	O
...	O
www.lotteryguidebook.com	O
can	O
help	O
,	O
by	O
reducing	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
possible	O
outcomes	O
more	O
than	O
99%	O

Why	O
do	O
people	O
spend	O
so	O
much	O
?	O
http://j.mp/iEcyEK	O

@bythebooks	B-PER
Insane	O
worry	O
of	O
dry	O
socket	O
,	O
infection	O
and	O
possible	O
more	O
money	O
w/o	O
insurance	O
spent	O
...	O

Top	O
Stock	O
searches	O
on	O
message	O
boards	O
and	O
Twitter	B-ORG
:	O
$MIMV	O
$AUGT	O
$SPY	O
$QQQ	O
$DIA	O
(	O
01:30	O
pm	O
)	O
#stocks	O
#finance	O
#stockmarket	O
#StockPicks	O

@steverod78	B-PER
back	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
baby	O
!	O

Food	O
:	O
Japanese	O
Fine	O
Dining	O
at	O
Kin	B-ORG
No	I-ORG
Mizu	I-ORG
,	O
The	O
Intermark	O
KL	O
|	O
http://bit.ly/m9zBv5	O
RT	O
@iamthewitch	B-PER
#travel	O
#foodie	O

@uhmannyg	B-PER
:)	O

100%	O
Pure	O
Strawberry	O
Lemonade	O
Juicy	O
Body	O
Scrub	O
for	O
only	O
$22	O
http://bit.ly/5MxmTY	O

oh	O
wait	O
.	O
just	O
re-read	O
ur	O
timeline	O
.	O
but	O
maybe	O
he	O
was	O
trying	O
to	O
imitate	O
singing	O
versus	O
speech	O
.	O
was	O
there	O
other	O
stuff	O
?	O
@sassycrass	B-PER

PRINCESS	O
playing	O
with	O
with	O
her	O
toys	O
and	O
asking	O
for	O
some	O
love	O
and	O
attention	O
.	O
A	O
regal	O
beauty	O
,	O
for	O
sure	O
.	O
Princess	O
is	O
...	O
http://fb.me/M267jGap	O

@harriettecole	B-PER
just	O
said	O
that	O
Google+	B-ORG
currently	O
is	O
86%	O
male	O
.	O
Time	O
to	O
change	O
those	O
numbers	O
ladies	O
!	O
#wmmulticultural	O

Can	O
someone	O
just	O
drive	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
post	O
office	O
oh	O
my	O
god	O
.	O
Leg	O
hurts	O
,	O
head	O
hurts	O
,	O
sweating	O
into	O
my	O
chair	O
...	O
#RIPJess	O

Ladies	O
don't	O
ever	O
put	O
a	O
guy	O
in	O
a	O
situation	O
where	O
he	O
should	O
feel	O
like	O
he	O
needs	O
to	O
buy	O
you	O
a	O
drink	O
.	O
TACKY	O
!	O

Inequality	O
needs	O
to	O
move	O
up	O
the	O
development	O
agenda	O
http://is.gd/KyrvEE	O
or	O
else	O
growth	O
will	O
prove	O
ineffectual	O
at	O
reducing	O
deprivation	O
.	O

Smiling	B-ORG
Tree	I-ORG
Toys	I-ORG
make	O
a	O
Fantabulous	O
natural	O
timber	O
Playground	O
Set	O
|	O
Inhabitots	O
http://bit.ly/fwKOuO	O

Ladies	O
just	O
cause	O
I'm	O
talking	O
to	O
you	O
you	O
automatically	O
assume	O
I'm	O
hitting	O
on	O
you	O
?	O
...	O
yeah	O
good	O
assumption	O
...	O

The	O
#kellyripa	B-PER
Daily	O
is	O
out	O
!	O
http://bit.ly/h86pOy	O
?	O
Top	O
stories	O
today	O
via	O
@tvdependente	B-ORG
@hannahstiefel	B-PER

I'm	O
sorry	O
people	O
,	O
I	O
can't	O
stand	O
Anne	B-PER
Hathaway	I-PER
.	O
She	O
just	O
reminds	O
me	O
too	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
annoying	O
drama	O
girl	O
that	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
school	O
with	O
.	O

Brooklyn	B-LOC
represents	O
.	O
RT	O
@PaulMalignaggi	B-PER
:	O
Big	O
shout	O
to	O
my	O
boy	O
@SUPERJUDAH	O
Bk	O
got	O
ur	O
back	O
!	O

Do	O
I	O
need	O
NMT	O
apps	O
installed	O
to	O
play	O
full	O
blu	O
ray	O
rips	O
?	O
http://bit.ly/fq3r1	O

@wellowater	O
Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
reply	O
!	O
We	O
will	O
get	O
in	O
touch	O
today	O
.	O
Email	O
me	O
with	O
any	O
specific	O
names	O
if	O
possible	O
:	O
rmohanam@	O
engenderhealth.org	O
.	O

As	O
A	O
Entrepreneur	O
You	O
Must	O
Try	O
To	O
Avoid	O
Money	O
Leaks	O
.	O
Strategize	O
Your	O
Focus	O
More	O
On	O
OPM	O
&	O
Accelerating	O
Assets	O
.	O

This	O
Pill	O
Helps	O
Prevent	O
HIV	O
,	O
But	O
Who	O
Will	O
Have	O
Access	O
To	O
It	O
?	O
http://pulse.me/s/FySl	O

The	O
Gospel	O
According	O
to	O
Josh	O
is	O
in	O
NY	B-LOC
Recession	O
diary	O
http://www.nycrecessiondiary.com/2010/07/gospel-according-to-josh-buy-one-get.html	O

@MattNixTV	B-PER
It	O
makes	O
you	O
a	O
lucky	O
nephew	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
cool	O
uncle	O
like	O
that	O
.	O

#intro	O
@jtretakoff	B-PER
&	O
@TinaHui	B-PER
-	O
meet	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
My	O
work	O
is	O
done	O
!	O
/cc	O
@hashable	O
-	O
Josh	B-PER
get	O
in	O
touch	O
with	O
Tina	B-PER
!	O
http://hb.ly/emHnwT	O

Auditions	O
for	O
@AboveHellsKitch	B-MISC
all	O
day	O
today	O
!	O
So	O
exciting	O
...	O
We're	O
going	O
to	O
rock	O
#NYMF	O
'	O
s	O
proverbial	O
socks	O
.	O

You	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
say	O
you	O
have	O
extreme	O
highs	O
and	O
lows	O
when	O
working	O
on	O
a	O
startup	O
?!	O
This	O
15	O
minutes	O
is	O
a	O
low	O
!	O

It	O
's	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
The	O
Duffers	O
and	O
someone	O
's	O
got	O
the	O
home	O
court	O
advantage	O
.	O
Go	O
vote	O
!	O
http://t.co/hsRbimO	O

Gogol	O
Bordello	O
Non-Stop	O
opens	O
in	O
NYC	B-LOC
@	O
Cinema	O
Village	O
today	O
!	O
http://bit.ly/RlByT	O

Earlier	O
we	O
told	O
u	O
we	O
surprised	O
@LALA	B-PER
for	O
her	O
birthday	O
while	O
we	O
rehearsed	O
in	O
@Ford	O
Social	O
Media	O
Lounge	O
-	O
here	O
's	O
video	O
:	O
http://ow.ly/5qpDN	O

Simply	O
a	O
MUST	O
READ	O
:	O
The	O
Myth	O
of	O
Charter	B-ORG
Schools	I-ORG
http://bit.ly/gIH4QT	O

@EllieTr	B-PER
@NortonSimon	B-PER
How	O
beautiful	O
!	O
Thank	O
you	O
for	O
sharing	O
.	O

Social	O
Media	O
Marketing	O
Magazine	O
:	O
Exclusives	O
:	O
Top	O
CMOs	O
on	O
Twitter	B-ORG
http://t.co/xvWfKvY	O
@social2b	O
http://t.co/gbwNvai	O

Oh	O
,	O
you	O
want	O
me	O
to	O
show	O
up	O
on	O
time	O
.	O
How	O
'	O
bout	O
this	O
:	O
I'll	O
come	O
in	O
on	O
time	O
when	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
that	O
raise	O
.	O
Sound	O
fair	O
?	O

Entire	O
South	B-LOC
Dakota	I-LOC
Town	O
For	O
Sale	O
For	O
$	O
799,000	O
http://sns.mx/9iegy8	O

Bloomberg	B-ORG
LP	O
promotes	O
Dan	B-PER
Doctoroff	I-PER
to	O
CEO	O
from	O
his	O
role	O
as	O
president	O
.	O
@BloombergLP	B-ORG
And	O
!	O
Don't	O
miss	O
his	O
appearance	O
next	O
week	O
at	O
#FutureofNYC	B-LOC

In	O
the	O
neighborhood	O
of	O
@PeanutButterCo	B-ORG
,	O
had	O
to	O
stop	O
!	O
http://lockerz.com/s/120890768	O

@BENJASTYLES	B-PER
Hey	O
!	O
if	O
ur	O
looking	O
for	O
new	O
music	O
,	O
my	O
blog	O
is	O
pretty	O
small	O
,	O
but	O
I'm	O
really	O
picky	O
about	O
quality	O
www.waitingtoexplode.com	O

@_ThatGirlChels	O
Thanks	O
love	O
!	O

#BlissLaser	O
Tip	O
-	O
I'm	O
not	O
only	O
the	O
Bliss	O
Girl	O
,	O
I'm	O
also	O
client	O
.	O
Got	O
lasered	O
2day	O
at	O
lunch	O
.	O
Hamptons	B-LOC
-	O
here	O
I	O
come	O
!	O
#BlissLaser	O

The	O
Year	O
Ahead	O
:	O
2011	O
Predictions	O
for	O
Marketers	O
http://t.co/Ulp8wUv	O
via	O
@adage	O

@jimmyfallon	B-PER
A	O
feelin	O
'	O
deep	O
inside	O
,	O
oh	O
yeah	O
?	O

African	O
Investment	O
:	O
More	O
than	O
Just	O
The	O
Headline	O
Names	O
-	O
http://www.moneywatchafrica.com/2011/04/african-opportunity-more-than-just.html	O

Yet	O
another	O
instance	O
of	O
a	O
casual	O
restaurant	O
allegedly	O
serving	O
alcohol	O
to	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
http://tinyurl.com/3zae45r	O

Interior	O
Design	O
Book	O
Helps	O
Find	O
the	O
Perfect	O
Rug	O
for	O
Your	O
Home	O
http://dld.bz/afAQr	O
@justluxe	O
#design	O

Gier	O
is	O
now	O
conducting	O
our	O
bliss	O
it	O
comes	O
in	O
waves	O
by	O
Jeremy	B-PER
Podgursky	I-PER
.	O
#ESCOread	B-MISC
http://acosoundadvice.blogspot.com/	O

More	O
new	O
books	O
!	O
Exhibiting	O
the	O
new	O
art	O
:	O
'	O
Op	O
losse	O
schroeven	O
'	O
and	O
'	O
When	O
attitudes	O
become	O
form	O
'	O
1969	O
--	O
London	B-LOC
:...	O
http://fb.me/VASniiwV	O

#GMABeyonce	O
http://bit.ly/kiOT9x	O
@GetGlue	O
#GMABeyonce	O

#LAWYERS/#LAW	O
STUDENTS	O
:	O
Need	O
to	O
sharpen	O
your	O
interview	O
skills	O
?	O
The	O
answer	O
is	O
YES	O
!	O
A	O
program	O
for	O
u	O
:	O
10/26	O
6pm	O
@	O
NYCBar	O
http://bit.ly/attyint	O

Shades	O
in	O
the	O
shade	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
sun	O
.	O
#flipflopfriday	O

Crosspost	O
from	O
r/battlestargalactica	O
-	O
Tyrol	B-PER
sighting	O
in	O
Bellingham	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
WA	I-LOC
http://sns.mx/XMevy1	O

Why	O
(	O
as	O
of	O
today	O
)	O
Everyone	O
Loves	O
a	O
Good	O
Wedding	O
...	O
http://bit.ly/pdwLgK	O

This	O
looks	O
amazing	O
:	O
Discount	O
Designer	O
Pop-Up	O
Shop	O
Supports	O
TriBeCa	O
Nonprofit	O
http://bit.ly/mbuxRz	O

I	O
don't	O
know	O
what	O
that	O
means	O
,	O
but	O
love	O
it	O
.	O
RT	O
@Cat_Marnell	B-PER
:	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
shame	O
in	O
sleeping	O
with	O
the	O
chic	O

Persistent	O
people	O
begin	O
their	O
success	O
where	O
others	O
end	O
in	O
failure	O

Thanks	O
@iLookBothWays	O
for	O
awarding	O
@DonrosChoose	B-ORG
your	O
first	O
ever	O
seal	O
of	O
approval	O
!	O
http://t11.me/WVU-4K	O

Microphone	O
Extension	O
Cord	O
for	O
Minolta	B-ORG
XL	O
Sound	O
Movie	O
Cameras	O
http://t.co/mjhhU9n	O
via	O
@AddThis	O

One	B-MISC
Too	I-MISC
Many	B-MISC
Mornings	I-MISC
(	O
Chemical	O
Brothers)	O
:	O
http://youtube.com/watch?v=gSexKNZjJ64	O
http://fb.me/SwPcKLfk	O

@kindafunny	B-PER
yes	O
and	O
apparently	O
in	O
an	O
apt	O
without	O
heat	O
...	O
good	O
that	O
Fish	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
mountain	O
#oltl	O

@purseblog	O
,	O
agreed	O
!!!	O
Like	O
a	O
marathon	O
session	O
.	O

A9	O
:	O
Never	O
been	O
to	O
Maine	B-LOC
,	O
but	O
I'm	O
interested	O
in	O
being	O
stranded	O
with	O
an	O
endless	O
supply	O
of	O
lobster	O
rolls	O
.	O
Or	O
maybe	O
just	O
somewhere	O
warm	O
.	O
#tni	O

Bungie	O
Aerospace	B-ORG
revealed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Mobile	O
experience	O
http://sns.mx/ONc2y1	O

There	O
's	O
been	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
pet	O
food	O
recall	O
recently	O
,	O
please	O
check	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
affects	O
your	O
pets	O
.	O
Hope	O
you	O
and	O
...	O
http://fb.me/xu42Nmw4	O

Hey	O
@USApears	B-PER
-	O
have	O
you	O
ever	O
tried	O
this	O
pear-peanut	O
butter	O
combo	O
??	O
http://t.co/Tu1rSGY	O

Uh	O
,	O
now	O
everyone	O
's	O
throwing	O
a	O
party	O
:	O
Microsoft	B-ORG
to	O
Launch	O
New	O
Social	O
Network	O
Called	O
Tulalip	B-MISC
Via	O
Socl	O
.	O
com	O
:	O
http://ow.ly/5IGfp	O

After	O
looking	O
at	O
roughly	O
200	O
apartments	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
overpopulated	O
by	O
crazy	O
chicks	O
,	O
think	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
place	O
.	O
Stay	O
tuned	O
.	O
#vixnyc	B-LOC

Great	O
to	O
see	O
teens	O
in	O
the	O
ranks	O
of	O
the	O
prepared	O
:	O
Rainbow	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
scouts	O
get	O
emergency	O
response	O
training	O
|	O
GadsdenTimes	O
.	O
com	O
http://ow.ly/2jsRu	O

I'm	O
at	O
Cedar	B-LOC
Lake	I-LOC
-	O
Le	O
Mieux	O
Resort	O
Faribault	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
MN	I-LOC
(	O
Golden	O
Avenue	O
,	O
Cedar	O
Lake	O
Ave	O
,	O
Faribault	O
)	O
[	O
pic]	O
:	O
http://4sq.com/pmYSYZ	O

How	O
important	O
is	O
site	O
load	O
speed	O
?	O
Google	O
Analytics	O
now	O
has	O
a	O
stat	O
for	O
this	O
,	O
hmmm	O
.	O
http://ow.ly/4RopL	O

"	O
Everyone	O
has	O
an	O
excuse	O
.	O
No	O
one	O
wants	O
to	O
hear	O
yours	O
."	O

Any	O
requests	O
on	O
which	O
speaker(s	O
)	O
you'd	O
like	O
to	O
hear	O
most	O
?	O
http://bit.ly/cw6yZa	O
#L2MobileClinic	O

Have	O
some	O
fun	O
with	O
the	O
birther	O
controversy	O
&	O
get	O
a	O
mug	O
featuring	O
the	O
President	B-MISC
's	O
birth	O
certificate	O
today	O
:	O
http://t.co/IQX4w9Y	O

WHOSE	O
jewish	O
state	O
?	O

GQ	B-ORG
certainly	O
isn't.	O
Congrats	O
to	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
RT	O
@swells_	O
:	O
Who	O
says	O
men	O
's	O
fashion	O
is	O
lagging	O
?	O
@GQMagazine	B-ORG
ranks	O
highest	O
amongst	O
fashion	O
...	O

What	O
are	O
the	O
chances	O
that	O
both	O
engines	O
fail	O
due	O
to	O
bird-ingestion	O
?	O
I'd	O
say	O
virtually	O
zero	O
.	O
A	O
malfunction	O
with	O
the	O
plane	O
seems	O
more	O
likely	O
.	O
